<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<tv generator-info-name="ZipWave PTN EPG Generator" generator-info-url="https://github.com/benevenstanciano/zip-epg">
  <channel id="ptn">
    <display-name>Pioneer Network</display-name>
  </channel>
  <programme start="20260608113000 +0000" stop="20260608120000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Joyce Meyer: Enjoying Everyday Life</title>
    <desc>Joyce Meyer, one of the world’s leading practicalBible teachers and New York Times bestselling author, shares encouragement andadvice to help people enjoy daily life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260608120000 +0000" stop="20260608123000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Good Morning LIVE</title>
    <desc>Good Morning LIVE is an engaging 30-minute program designed to inspire, inform, and connect viewers to the heart of meaningful living. Hosted by James Epperly, this dynamic show brings together a unique blend of inspirational devotions, thought-provoking interviews, and discussions on current events that matter most to you. Each episode offers uplifting messages to start your day on a positive note, insightful conversations with special guests, and a closer look at how current events align with faith and personal growth. Whether you're seeking encouragement, knowledge, or a deeper connection to today's world, Good Morning LIVE is your source for faith-filled and relevant content. Join us weekday mornings to experience a fresh perspective, inspired by truth and guided by hope.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260608123000 +0000" stop="20260608130000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Worldview Matters</title>
    <desc>David Fiorazo is an author, ordained pastor, truth proclaimer, media contributor, and podcaster. Since the1990’s David has been working in both TV and radio broadcasting and in Christian ministry. On Worldview Matters, Fiorazo and expert guests tackle current events, demonic agendas &amp;movements, and controversial topics including church &amp; state issues, religious freedom, the culture war, Bible prophecy, education, politics, media&amp; more.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260608130000 +0000" stop="20260608133000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Gospel Truth with Andrew Wommack</title>
    <desc>God called Andrew over 50 years ago toteach the truth of the gospel to the body of Christ with a special emphasis onHis unconditional love and the balance between grace and faith. To fulfil thatcall, Andrew teaches at conferences, in churches, on television, throughpodcasts, and by training people from all walks of life globally at CharisBible College.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260608130000 +0000" stop="20260608133000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Gospel Truth with Andrew Wommack</title>
    <desc>Thirty-two years ago a man had an encounter with God that changed his life forever. Today, he shares that experience with thousands of people all over the world. The goal of Andrew Wommack is to reach as many people as possible with the love of God and message of grace and faith. He doesn’t measure the success of the ministry by the number of tapes distributed, books sold or offerings received. The real rewards, and proof that God is alive and working in people’s lives, are the many testimonies he receives from the people impacted by his teachings. To find out more, please visit our website at: http://www.awmi.net http://www.awmi.net/ www.awmi.net</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260608133000 +0000" stop="20260608140000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Rick Renner</title>
    <desc>Rick Renner is widely known for his interpretation of the Greek New Testament and his engaging teaching style. His teaching is punctuated by a unique ability to draw vividly descriptive word pictures from the Greek that illuminate the Scriptures in a fresh, new way. Rick also distinctively shares Bible principles through contemporary illustrations set against an extensive cultural and historical backdrop of New Testament times. In each episode of “Rick Renner,” Rick teaches in-depth on a passage of Scripture verse by verse, centered around a specific theme that is vitally relevant to the lives of believers who are hungry to dig deeper into the treasures of God’s Word. For more information, visit http://www.renner.org.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260608140000 +0000" stop="20260608143000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Run The Streets with Debra George</title>
    <desc>Debra takes you to the darkest streets of America to win souls.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260608143000 +0000" stop="20260608150000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The James Epperly Show</title>
    <desc>"The James Epperly Show" is a Christian television program that aims to inspire and uplift viewers through faith-based content. Hosted by Pastor James Epperly, the show features insightful sermons, engaging interviews with prominent Christian figures, and heartfelt testimonials from individuals who have experienced life-changing transformations through faith. Each episode is designed to offer spiritual guidance, biblical wisdom, and practical advice for living a Christ-centered life. With its friendly and welcoming vibe, 'The James Epperly Show' aims to support viewers' spiritual development and enhance their connection with God, making it a treasured part of their weekly viewing schedule.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260608150000 +0000" stop="20260608153000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Manna-fest with Perry Stone</title>
    <desc>Manna-fest is the weekly television program of Perry Stone that deals with in-depth prophetic and practical studies of the Word of God. As biblical prophecy continues to unfold, you will find Manna-fest to be a resource to help you better understand where we are now in light of Bible prophecy and what the Bible says about the future. Be sure to tune in each week!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260608153000 +0000" stop="20260608160000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Joyce Meyer: Enjoying Everyday Life</title>
    <desc>Joyce Meyer, one of the world’s leading practicalBible teachers and New York Times bestselling author, shares encouragement andadvice to help people enjoy daily life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260608160000 +0000" stop="20260608163000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The James Epperly Show</title>
    <desc>"The James Epperly Show" is a Christian television program that aims to inspire and uplift viewers through faith-based content. Hosted by Pastor James Epperly, the show features insightful sermons, engaging interviews with prominent Christian figures, and heartfelt testimonials from individuals who have experienced life-changing transformations through faith. Each episode is designed to offer spiritual guidance, biblical wisdom, and practical advice for living a Christ-centered life. With its friendly and welcoming vibe, 'The James Epperly Show' aims to support viewers' spiritual development and enhance their connection with God, making it a treasured part of their weekly viewing schedule.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260608163000 +0000" stop="20260608170000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The Jim Bakker Show</title>
    <desc>The Jim Bakker Show is an hour-long daily Christian broadcast that is aired throughout the United States, Canada, and the entire world through multiple broadcasts on Pioneer Network, Directv, Dish Network and other world wide satellites, and the PTL Television Network. Join Jim and Lori as they bring to the stage today’s greatest prophets, health experts, and leaders of the Christian world to discuss and understand Biblical prophecy and the Revelations of Gods Word.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260608170000 +0000" stop="20260608173000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The Mondo Show</title>
    <desc>The Mondo Show is real, it’s raw, with an organicfeel to the conversation. Sometimes I will be talking directly to you theaudience, and at other times I will place you in the middle of theconversation, so you can experience what is really being said. The subject matter for the conversation and thequestions will be the things people are afraid to ask, even though it is whateveryone is thinking. I want you to meet the men and women who are making adifference in our communities, in our culture, and in our lives. It’s a journeyto understand the misunderstood. It’s The Mondo Show.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260608173000 +0000" stop="20260608180000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>VFI News</title>
    <desc>VFI News with Barry Segal brings you timely, insightful reports on Israel, the Middle East, andglobal events - analysed through a biblical and prophetic lens.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260608180000 +0000" stop="20260608183000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Jentezen Franklin</title>
    <desc>Jentezen Franklin is the Senior Pastor of Free Chapel, a multi-campus church. Each week his television program, Kingdom Connection, is broadcast on major networks all over the world. A New York Times best-selling author, Jentezen has written ten books including his most recent Acres of Diamonds, Love Like You’ve Never Been Hurt, the ground-breaking Fasting and Right People-Right Place-Right Plan.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260608183000 +0000" stop="20260608190000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Christian Music Countdown</title>
    <desc>CMC is a TV showfeaturing contemporary Christian music videos. Each week we count down topmusic videos hand picked from our special guests.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260608190000 +0000" stop="20260608193000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Victory With Paul Daugherty</title>
    <desc>Pastor Paul Daugherty and his wife Ashley lead a new generation with a practical, life-transforming message; a message of love, hope, healing and forgiveness.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260608193000 +0000" stop="20260608200000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Paula Today with Paula White-Cain</title>
    <desc>Paula Today Paula White-Cain along with her husband, Jonathan Cain discuss real life situations and offer practical, Biblical solutions. Down-to-earth, refreshing, sometimes unfiltered and always sharing the life-changing love of Jesus thru Paula’s in-depth teaching or Jon’s anointed music. About Paula Paula White-Cain is the President of Paula White Ministries and City of Destiny headquartered in Apopka, Florida, and the spiritual advisor to President Donald Trump. She hosts Paula Today, a nationally syndicated daily broadcast reaching a potential audience of 5.7 billion people in over 200 countries. She is a leading Pastor, a renowned life coach, bestselling author, and highly sought-after motivational speaker. Paula’s commitment to humanity is felt worldwide as she reaches out through numerous charities and compassion ministries, fulfilling her mission and call to transform lives, heal hearts and win souls. She lives in the Orlando area with her husband, Jonathan Cain.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260608200000 +0000" stop="20260608203000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Focus On The Family</title>
    <desc>Become a champion for your family in the time it takes to enjoy a cup of coffee! Every episode of the Focus on the Family Christian podcast helps you confidently guide your loved ones through the unique challenges faced by today’s Christian families. With over 40 years of trusted, compassionate stories of redemption, hosts Jim Daly and John Fuller connect you to biblically sound marriage and parenting help that is relatable, practical, and interesting. Listen/Learn/Apply/ThriveInChrist!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260608203000 +0000" stop="20260608210000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Life In Christ With Pastor Joe Spence</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260608210000 +0000" stop="20260608213000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Joyce Meyer: Enjoying Everyday Life</title>
    <desc>Joyce Meyer, one of the world’s leading practical Bible teachers and NewYork Times bestselling author, shares encouragement and advice to help peopleenjoy daily life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260608220000 +0000" stop="20260608223000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The Counter Culture Mom Show</title>
    <desc>Former Hollywood actress, pop culture expert, Tina Griffin, left her Wisconsin dairy farm at the age of 20 and headed to Hollywood, CA to earn a BA in Film and Television broadcasting from California State University - Los Angeles. She’s traveled globally for the past 20 years delivering her eye-opening show, Hollywood Exposed https://counterculturemom.com/adult-session/ , explaining the real agenda behind the entertainment industry and its impact on the foundational development of today’s youth. Besides being in countless movies, Tina has worked on TV shows such as Jimmy Kimmel Live!, Young and the Restless, Days of Our Lives, Lizzie McGuire, Drake and Josh, and Malcolm in the Middle, competed in the Miss America pageant and worked at the OSCARS. She was involved with the Film Society as well as Women in Film and an active member of the Screen Actors Guild (SAG) and the American Federation of Television and Radio Artists (AFTRA). She has opened for bands such as Colton Dixon, Third Day, and Jeremy Camp. As host of The Counter Culture Mom Show, Tina gives the latest pop culture news and features experts covering critical topics such as cutting, suicide, bullying, online chat room d</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260608223000 +0000" stop="20260608230000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Believer’s Voice of Victory</title>
    <desc>KCMis committed to keeping the Word of God before your eyes—teaching you how tolive victoriously—so that you are rooted and grounded enough to overcome yourown adversity, reach out to others and share those same principles. We endeavorto bring believers from the milk to the meat of the Word, and into fullmaturity in their walk with God. Oneword from God has transformed the lives of thousands who dared to hear andbelieve. And one word from God will do the same for you.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260608230000 +0000" stop="20260608233000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Manna Fest With Perry Stone</title>
    <desc>Manna-fest is the weekly television program of Perry Stone that deals with in-depth prophetic and practical studies of the Word of God. As biblical prophecy continues to unfold, you will find Manna-fest to be a resource to help you better understand where we are now in light of Bible prophecy and what the Bible says about the future. Be sure to tune in each week!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260608233000 +0000" stop="20260609000000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Desire Of All Nations</title>
    <desc>Nathan Morris of Shake The Nations is a British evangelist who is well know for the Bay of the Holy Spirit Revival. He is known for his passionate messages on the Blood of Jesus and the Cross.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260609000000 +0000" stop="20260609010000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>FlashPoint</title>
    <desc>Live program that addresses current events and issues facing America and the world. Often tackling topics that mainstream media does not, it delivers news and commentary under the anointing—encouraging evidence that God is indeed working to bring about His plans and purposes during these turbulent times. Hosted by Gene Bailey and joined by leaders in government, business, politics and the Church. FlashPoint’s rapidly become a trusted source of truth and hope. Wednesdays and Fridays at 8 p.m. ET/7 p.m. CT.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260609010000 +0000" stop="20260609013000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Paula Today with Paula White-Cain</title>
    <desc>Paula White-Cain along with her husband, Jonathan Cain discuss real life situations and offer practical, Biblical solutions. Down-to-earth, refreshing, sometimes unfiltered and always sharing the life-changing love of Jesus thru Paula’s in-depth teaching or Jon’s anointed music. About Paula Paula White-Cain is the President of Paula White Ministries and City of Destiny headquartered in Apopka, Florida, and the spiritual advisor to President Donald Trump. She hosts Paula Today, a nationally syndicated daily broadcast reaching a potential audience of 5.7 billion people in over 200 countries. She is a leading Pastor, a renowned life coach, bestselling author, and highly sought-after motivational speaker. Paula’s commitment to humanity is felt worldwide as she reaches out through numerous charities and compassion ministries, fulfilling her mission and call to transform lives, heal hearts and win souls. She lives in the Orlando area with her husband, Jonathan Cain.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260609013000 +0000" stop="20260609020000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The James Epperly Show</title>
    <desc>"The James Epperly Show" is a Christian television program that aims to inspire and uplift viewers through faith-based content. Hosted by Pastor James Epperly, the show features insightful sermons, engaging interviews with prominent Christian figures, and heartfelt testimonials from individuals who have experienced life-changing transformations through faith. Each episode is designed to offer spiritual guidance, biblical wisdom, and practical advice for living a Christ-centered life. With its friendly and welcoming vibe, 'The James Epperly Show' aims to support viewers' spiritual development and enhance their connection with God, making it a treasured part of their weekly viewing schedule.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260609020000 +0000" stop="20260609030000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Brian &amp; Bobbie Houston - JesusFollowers.TV</title>
    <desc>"What greater honour and testimony is there than to be a devotedand passionate follower of the Lord Jesus Christ. Bobbie and I believe in the Church, thelocal church and the power and blessing of being planted (Psalm 92). We alsobelieve that in this day and age, God is creating multiple ways to water theseeds and greatness of calling within. Jesusfollowers.TV is here towelcome and extend our table of life and experience to you. This onlineplatform is here to love, encourage, and be a trustworthy voice of hope andinspiration in the days ahead. Our heart is to serve the God-given potentialwithin you and the Body of Christ. As Eph 2:21-22 says, we are all beingbuilt into a holy habitation for the Living God - brick by brick, stone bystone, with Jesus Christ as the Chief Cornerstone. May Jesusfollowers.TV be ablessing to you and those you care for” Brian and Bobbie Houston</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260609030000 +0000" stop="20260609033000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The Jim Bakker Show</title>
    <desc>The Jim Bakker Show is an hour-long daily Christian broadcast that is aired throughout the United States, Canada, and the entire world through multiple broadcasts on Pioneer Network, Directv, Dish Network and other world wide satellites, and the PTL Television Network. Join Jim and Lori as they bring to the stage today’s greatest prophets, health experts, and leaders of the Christian world to discuss and understand Biblical prophecy and the Revelations of Gods Word.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260609033000 +0000" stop="20260609040000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The James Epperly Show</title>
    <desc>"The James Epperly Show" is a Christian television program that aims to inspire and uplift viewers through faith-based content. Hosted by Pastor James Epperly, the show features insightful sermons, engaging interviews with prominent Christian figures, and heartfelt testimonials from individuals who have experienced life-changing transformations through faith. Each episode is designed to offer spiritual guidance, biblical wisdom, and practical advice for living a Christ-centered life. With its friendly and welcoming vibe, 'The James Epperly Show' aims to support viewers' spiritual development and enhance their connection with God, making it a treasured part of their weekly viewing schedule.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260609040000 +0000" stop="20260609060000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Raise The Standard Conference with Rod Parsley</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260609060000 +0000" stop="20260609063000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The Place For Miracles</title>
    <desc>The Place forMiracles is a half-hour broadcast hosted by Richard and Lindsay Roberts. Theprogram focuses on the power of prayer and biblical teaching by Richard andLindsay, plus occasional videos featuring classic sermons from Oral Roberts,praise and worship music, “Living Proof” miracle testimonies, including livecalls and video presentations, and frequent, special guest appearances.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260609063000 +0000" stop="20260609070000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Kingdom Connection with Jentezen Franklin</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260609070000 +0000" stop="20260609073000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Desire Of All Nations</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260609073000 +0000" stop="20260609080000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Samuel Rodriguez</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260609080000 +0000" stop="20260609083000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The Jim Bakker Show</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260609083000 +0000" stop="20260609090000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Believer’s Voice of Victory</title>
    <desc>KCMis committed to keeping the Word of God before your eyes—teaching you how tolive victoriously—so that you are rooted and grounded enough to overcome yourown adversity, reach out to others and share those same principles. We endeavorto bring believers from the milk to the meat of the Word, and into fullmaturity in their walk with God. Oneword from God has transformed the lives of thousands who dared to hear andbelieve. And one word from God will do the same for you.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260609090000 +0000" stop="20260609093000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Paula Today with Paula Whie-Cain</title>
    <desc>Paula White-Cain along with her husband, Jonathan Cain discuss real life situations and offer practical, Biblical solutions. Down-to-earth, refreshing, sometimes unfiltered and always sharing the life-changing love of Jesus thru Paula’s in-depth teaching or Jon’s anointed music.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260609093000 +0000" stop="20260609100000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Christian Music Countdown</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260609100000 +0000" stop="20260609103000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Glory Road with Dr. Candice Smithyman</title>
    <desc>The Glory Road TV show help you connect with heaven and the glory of the Lord to activate the spiritual gifts, purpose and destiny in your life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260609103000 +0000" stop="20260609110000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Believer's Voice of Victory</title>
    <desc>KCM is committed to keeping the Word of God before your eyes—teaching you how to live victoriously—so that you are rooted and grounded enough to overcome your own adversity, reach out to others and share those same principles. We endeavor to bring believers from the milk to the meat of the Word, and into full maturity in their walk with God.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260609110000 +0000" stop="20260609113000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Today with Marilyn &amp; Sarah</title>
    <desc>Marilyn&amp; Sarah Ministries is a global, miracle ministry responding to God's callto cover the earth with the Word and connect every one with the heart of God.For nearly 50 years they have empowered ordinary people to tap into thelife-changing power of the gospel through prayer, Bible teaching, humanitarianand evangelistic outreaches, healing meetings, and their daily TV program,Today with Marilyn &amp; Sarah.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260609113000 +0000" stop="20260609120000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Joyce Meyer: Enjoying Everyday Life</title>
    <desc>Joyce Meyer, one of the world’s leading practicalBible teachers and New York Times bestselling author, shares encouragement andadvice to help people enjoy daily life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260609120000 +0000" stop="20260609123000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Good Morning LIVE</title>
    <desc>Good Morning LIVE is an engaging 30-minute program designed to inspire, inform, and connect viewers to the heart of meaningful living. Hosted by James Epperly, this dynamic show brings together a unique blend of inspirational devotions, thought-provoking interviews, and discussions on current events that matter most to you. Each episode offers uplifting messages to start your day on a positive note, insightful conversations with special guests, and a closer look at how current events align with faith and personal growth. Whether you're seeking encouragement, knowledge, or a deeper connection to today's world, Good Morning LIVE is your source for faith-filled and relevant content. Join us weekday mornings to experience a fresh perspective, inspired by truth and guided by hope.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260609123000 +0000" stop="20260609130000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Faith &amp; Law</title>
    <desc>Faith &amp; Law is a 30 minute variety program that focuses on the intersection of faith and law.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260609130000 +0000" stop="20260609133000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Gospel Truth with Andrew Wommack</title>
    <desc>God called Andrew over 50 years ago toteach the truth of the gospel to the body of Christ with a special emphasis onHis unconditional love and the balance between grace and faith. To fulfil thatcall, Andrew teaches at conferences, in churches, on television, throughpodcasts, and by training people from all walks of life globally at CharisBible College.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260609130000 +0000" stop="20260609133000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Gospel Truth with Andrew Wommack</title>
    <desc>Thirty-two years ago a man had an encounter with God that changed his life forever. Today, he shares that experience with thousands of people all over the world. The goal of Andrew Wommack is to reach as many people as possible with the love of God and message of grace and faith. He doesn’t measure the success of the ministry by the number of tapes distributed, books sold or offerings received. The real rewards, and proof that God is alive and working in people’s lives, are the many testimonies he receives from the people impacted by his teachings. To find out more, please visit our website at: http://www.awmi.net http://www.awmi.net/ www.awmi.net</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260609133000 +0000" stop="20260609140000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Rick Renner</title>
    <desc>Rick Renner is widely known for his interpretation of the Greek New Testament and his engaging teaching style. His teaching is punctuated by a unique ability to draw vividly descriptive word pictures from the Greek that illuminate the Scriptures in a fresh, new way. Rick also distinctively shares Bible principles through contemporary illustrations set against an extensive cultural and historical backdrop of New Testament times. In each episode of “Rick Renner,” Rick teaches in-depth on a passage of Scripture verse by verse, centered around a specific theme that is vitally relevant to the lives of believers who are hungry to dig deeper into the treasures of God’s Word. For more information, visit http://www.renner.org.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260609140000 +0000" stop="20260609143000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Concepts Of Faith with Charles Capps</title>
    <desc>ArkansasFarmer, Charles Capps and family discovered that the spiritual truths Jesustaught could be applied to the everyday circumstances of life and change it!The practical teaching of how to do that is needed and relevant for everyonetoday. Charles, wife Peggy and daughter Annette share life changing truths.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260609143000 +0000" stop="20260609153000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Brian &amp; Bobbie Houston - JesusFollowers.TV</title>
    <desc>"What greater honour and testimony is there than to be a devotedand passionate follower of the Lord Jesus Christ. Bobbie and I believe in the Church, thelocal church and the power and blessing of being planted (Psalm 92). We alsobelieve that in this day and age, God is creating multiple ways to water theseeds and greatness of calling within. Jesusfollowers.TV is here towelcome and extend our table of life and experience to you. This onlineplatform is here to love, encourage, and be a trustworthy voice of hope andinspiration in the days ahead. Our heart is to serve the God-given potentialwithin you and the Body of Christ. As Eph 2:21-22 says, we are all beingbuilt into a holy habitation for the Living God - brick by brick, stone bystone, with Jesus Christ as the Chief Cornerstone. May Jesusfollowers.TV be ablessing to you and those you care for” Brian and Bobbie Houston</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260609153000 +0000" stop="20260609160000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Joyce Meyer: Enjoying Everyday Life</title>
    <desc>Joyce Meyer, one of the world’s leading practicalBible teachers and New York Times bestselling author, shares encouragement andadvice to help people enjoy daily life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260609160000 +0000" stop="20260609163000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The James Epperly Show</title>
    <desc>"The James Epperly Show" is a Christian television program that aims to inspire and uplift viewers through faith-based content. Hosted by Pastor James Epperly, the show features insightful sermons, engaging interviews with prominent Christian figures, and heartfelt testimonials from individuals who have experienced life-changing transformations through faith. Each episode is designed to offer spiritual guidance, biblical wisdom, and practical advice for living a Christ-centered life. With its friendly and welcoming vibe, 'The James Epperly Show' aims to support viewers' spiritual development and enhance their connection with God, making it a treasured part of their weekly viewing schedule.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260609163000 +0000" stop="20260609170000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The Jim Bakker Show</title>
    <desc>The Jim Bakker Show is an hour-long daily Christian broadcast that is aired throughout the United States, Canada, and the entire world through multiple broadcasts on Pioneer Network, Directv, Dish Network and other world wide satellites, and the PTL Television Network. Join Jim and Lori as they bring to the stage today’s greatest prophets, health experts, and leaders of the Christian world to discuss and understand Biblical prophecy and the Revelations of Gods Word.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260609170000 +0000" stop="20260609173000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Kyle Winkler</title>
    <desc>Kyle Winkler is a practical Bible teacher, author of Silence Satan and Activating the Power of God’s Word, and creator of the popular Shut Up, Devil! app. Through his teachings, Kyle is known for using his own story to boast in the power of God’s Word for victorious living.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260609173000 +0000" stop="20260609180000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Samuel Rodriguez</title>
    <desc>New Season with Pastor Sam will usher in a "New Season" where individuals and families will no longer live in failure or merely survive but they will thrive for the glory of Jesus.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260609180000 +0000" stop="20260609183000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Jentezen Franklin</title>
    <desc>Jentezen Franklin is the Senior Pastor of Free Chapel, a multi-campus church. Each week his television program, Kingdom Connection, is broadcast on major networks all over the world. A New York Times best-selling author, Jentezen has written ten books including his most recent Acres of Diamonds, Love Like You’ve Never Been Hurt, the ground-breaking Fasting and Right People-Right Place-Right Plan.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260609183000 +0000" stop="20260609190000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Christian Music Countdown</title>
    <desc>CMC is a TV showfeaturing contemporary Christian music videos. Each week we count down topmusic videos hand picked from our special guests.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260609190000 +0000" stop="20260609193000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Concepts Of Faith with Charles Capps</title>
    <desc>ArkansasFarmer, Charles Capps and family discovered that the spiritual truths Jesustaught could be applied to the everyday circumstances of life and change it!The practical teaching of how to do that is needed and relevant for everyonetoday. Charles, wife Peggy and daughter Annette share life changing truths.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260609193000 +0000" stop="20260609200000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Paula Today with Paula White-Cain</title>
    <desc>Paula Today Paula White-Cain along with her husband, Jonathan Cain discuss real life situations and offer practical, Biblical solutions. Down-to-earth, refreshing, sometimes unfiltered and always sharing the life-changing love of Jesus thru Paula’s in-depth teaching or Jon’s anointed music. About Paula Paula White-Cain is the President of Paula White Ministries and City of Destiny headquartered in Apopka, Florida, and the spiritual advisor to President Donald Trump. She hosts Paula Today, a nationally syndicated daily broadcast reaching a potential audience of 5.7 billion people in over 200 countries. She is a leading Pastor, a renowned life coach, bestselling author, and highly sought-after motivational speaker. Paula’s commitment to humanity is felt worldwide as she reaches out through numerous charities and compassion ministries, fulfilling her mission and call to transform lives, heal hearts and win souls. She lives in the Orlando area with her husband, Jonathan Cain.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260609200000 +0000" stop="20260609203000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Manna Fest with Perry Stone</title>
    <desc>Manna-fest is the weekly television program of Perry Stone that deals with in-depth prophetic and practical studies of the Word of God. As biblical prophecy continues to unfold, you will find Manna-fest to be a resource to help you better understand where we are now in light of Bible prophecy and what the Bible says about the future. Be sure to tune in each week!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260609203000 +0000" stop="20260609210000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The James Epperly Show</title>
    <desc>"The James Epperly Show" is a Christian television program that aims to inspire and uplift viewers through faith-based content. Hosted by Pastor James Epperly, the show features insightful sermons, engaging interviews with prominent Christian figures, and heartfelt testimonials from individuals who have experienced life-changing transformations through faith. Each episode is designed to offer spiritual guidance, biblical wisdom, and practical advice for living a Christ-centered life. With its friendly and welcoming vibe, 'The James Epperly Show' aims to support viewers' spiritual development and enhance their connection with God, making it a treasured part of their weekly viewing schedule.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260609210000 +0000" stop="20260609213000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Joyce Meyer: Enjoying Everyday Life</title>
    <desc>Joyce Meyer, one of the world’s leading practical Bible teachers and NewYork Times bestselling author, shares encouragement and advice to help peopleenjoy daily life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260609213000 +0000" stop="20260609220000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Jentezen Franklin</title>
    <desc>Jentezen Franklin is the Senior Pastor of Free Chapel, a multi-campus church. Each week his television program, Kingdom Connection, is broadcast on major networks all over the world. A New York Times best-selling author, Jentezen has written ten books including his most recent Acres of Diamonds, Love Like You’ve Never Been Hurt, the ground-breaking Fasting and Right People-Right Place-Right Plan.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260609220000 +0000" stop="20260609223000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The Counter Culture Mom Show</title>
    <desc>Former Hollywood actress, pop culture expert, Tina Griffin, left her Wisconsin dairy farm at the age of 20 and headed to Hollywood, CA to earn a BA in Film and Television broadcasting from California State University - Los Angeles. She’s traveled globally for the past 20 years delivering her eye-opening show, Hollywood Exposed https://counterculturemom.com/adult-session/ , explaining the real agenda behind the entertainment industry and its impact on the foundational development of today’s youth. Besides being in countless movies, Tina has worked on TV shows such as Jimmy Kimmel Live!, Young and the Restless, Days of Our Lives, Lizzie McGuire, Drake and Josh, and Malcolm in the Middle, competed in the Miss America pageant and worked at the OSCARS. She was involved with the Film Society as well as Women in Film and an active member of the Screen Actors Guild (SAG) and the American Federation of Television and Radio Artists (AFTRA). She has opened for bands such as Colton Dixon, Third Day, and Jeremy Camp. As host of The Counter Culture Mom Show, Tina gives the latest pop culture news and features experts covering critical topics such as cutting, suicide, bullying, online chat room d</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260609223000 +0000" stop="20260609230000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Believer’s Voice of Victory</title>
    <desc>KCMis committed to keeping the Word of God before your eyes—teaching you how tolive victoriously—so that you are rooted and grounded enough to overcome yourown adversity, reach out to others and share those same principles. We endeavorto bring believers from the milk to the meat of the Word, and into fullmaturity in their walk with God. Oneword from God has transformed the lives of thousands who dared to hear andbelieve. And one word from God will do the same for you.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260609230000 +0000" stop="20260609233000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>God's View</title>
    <desc>Join us around the table as the Holy Spirit moves powerfully touchinglives with signs, wonders, and miracles, healings, salvations, baptisms in theHoly Spirit, etc. as the prayer lines are a reminder weekly of what God isdoing in the lives of the viewers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260609233000 +0000" stop="20260610000000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Samuel Rodriguez</title>
    <desc>New Season with Pastor Sam will usher in a "New Season" where individuals and families will no longer live in failure or merely survive but they will thrive for the glory of Jesus.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260610000000 +0000" stop="20260610010000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>FlashPoint</title>
    <desc>Live program that addresses current events and issues facing America and the world. Often tackling topics that mainstream media does not, it delivers news and commentary under the anointing—encouraging evidence that God is indeed working to bring about His plans and purposes during these turbulent times. Hosted by Gene Bailey and joined by leaders in government, business, politics and the Church. FlashPoint’s rapidly become a trusted source of truth and hope. Wednesdays and Fridays at 8 p.m. ET/7 p.m. CT.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260610010000 +0000" stop="20260610013000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Paula Today with Paula White-Cain</title>
    <desc>Paula White-Cain along with her husband, Jonathan Cain discuss real life situations and offer practical, Biblical solutions. Down-to-earth, refreshing, sometimes unfiltered and always sharing the life-changing love of Jesus thru Paula’s in-depth teaching or Jon’s anointed music. About Paula Paula White-Cain is the President of Paula White Ministries and City of Destiny headquartered in Apopka, Florida, and the spiritual advisor to President Donald Trump. She hosts Paula Today, a nationally syndicated daily broadcast reaching a potential audience of 5.7 billion people in over 200 countries. She is a leading Pastor, a renowned life coach, bestselling author, and highly sought-after motivational speaker. Paula’s commitment to humanity is felt worldwide as she reaches out through numerous charities and compassion ministries, fulfilling her mission and call to transform lives, heal hearts and win souls. She lives in the Orlando area with her husband, Jonathan Cain.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260610013000 +0000" stop="20260610020000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The James Epperly Show</title>
    <desc>"The James Epperly Show" is a Christian television program that aims to inspire and uplift viewers through faith-based content. Hosted by Pastor James Epperly, the show features insightful sermons, engaging interviews with prominent Christian figures, and heartfelt testimonials from individuals who have experienced life-changing transformations through faith. Each episode is designed to offer spiritual guidance, biblical wisdom, and practical advice for living a Christ-centered life. With its friendly and welcoming vibe, 'The James Epperly Show' aims to support viewers' spiritual development and enhance their connection with God, making it a treasured part of their weekly viewing schedule.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260610020000 +0000" stop="20260610023000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The Place For Miracles with Richard &amp; Lindsay Roberts</title>
    <desc>This show, hosted by Richard and Lindsay Roberts, features prayer, miracle testimonies, teaching from the Bible, and praise and worship.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260610023000 +0000" stop="20260610030000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Manna-Fest with Perry Stone</title>
    <desc>Manna-fest is the weekly television program of Perry Stone that deals with in-depth prophetic and practical studies of the Word of God. As biblical prophecy continues to unfold, you will find Manna-fest to be a resource to help you better understand where we are now in light of Bible prophecy and what the Bible says about the future. Be sure to tune in each week!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260610030000 +0000" stop="20260610033000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The Jim Bakker Show</title>
    <desc>The Jim Bakker Show is an hour-long daily Christian broadcast that is aired throughout the United States, Canada, and the entire world through multiple broadcasts on Pioneer Network, Directv, Dish Network and other world wide satellites, and the PTL Television Network. Join Jim and Lori as they bring to the stage today’s greatest prophets, health experts, and leaders of the Christian world to discuss and understand Biblical prophecy and the Revelations of Gods Word.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260610033000 +0000" stop="20260610040000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The James Epperly Show</title>
    <desc>"The James Epperly Show" is a Christian television program that aims to inspire and uplift viewers through faith-based content. Hosted by Pastor James Epperly, the show features insightful sermons, engaging interviews with prominent Christian figures, and heartfelt testimonials from individuals who have experienced life-changing transformations through faith. Each episode is designed to offer spiritual guidance, biblical wisdom, and practical advice for living a Christ-centered life. With its friendly and welcoming vibe, 'The James Epperly Show' aims to support viewers' spiritual development and enhance their connection with God, making it a treasured part of their weekly viewing schedule.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260610040000 +0000" stop="20260610060000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Be Made Whole Worldwide Prayer Cloth Service with Rod Parsley</title>
    <desc>Experience the powerful anointing of our Be Made Whole Worldwide Prayer Cloth Service featuring Harvest Music Live and our outstanding choir. The miracle-working power of God changed multiplied hundreds of thousands, and now you can reserve your anointed prayer cloth from this year’s altar. The tangible transferrable anointing can heal your body, produce deliverance, family restoration, financial breakthrough, whatever you need!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260610060000 +0000" stop="20260610063000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The Place For Miracles</title>
    <desc>The Place forMiracles is a half-hour broadcast hosted by Richard and Lindsay Roberts. Theprogram focuses on the power of prayer and biblical teaching by Richard andLindsay, plus occasional videos featuring classic sermons from Oral Roberts,praise and worship music, “Living Proof” miracle testimonies, including livecalls and video presentations, and frequent, special guest appearances.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260610063000 +0000" stop="20260610070000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Kingdom Connection with Jentezen Franklin</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260610070000 +0000" stop="20260610073000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Desire Of All Nations</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260610073000 +0000" stop="20260610080000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Samuel Rodriguez</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260610080000 +0000" stop="20260610083000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The Jim Bakker Show</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260610083000 +0000" stop="20260610090000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Believer’s Voice of Victory</title>
    <desc>KCMis committed to keeping the Word of God before your eyes—teaching you how tolive victoriously—so that you are rooted and grounded enough to overcome yourown adversity, reach out to others and share those same principles. We endeavorto bring believers from the milk to the meat of the Word, and into fullmaturity in their walk with God. Oneword from God has transformed the lives of thousands who dared to hear andbelieve. And one word from God will do the same for you.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260610090000 +0000" stop="20260610093000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Paula Today with Paula Whie-Cain</title>
    <desc>Paula White-Cain along with her husband, Jonathan Cain discuss real life situations and offer practical, Biblical solutions. Down-to-earth, refreshing, sometimes unfiltered and always sharing the life-changing love of Jesus thru Paula’s in-depth teaching or Jon’s anointed music.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260610093000 +0000" stop="20260610100000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Christian Music Countdown</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260610100000 +0000" stop="20260610103000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Make Your Day Count with Lindsay Roberts</title>
    <desc>Lindsay Roberts hosts an uplifting program geared especially toward encouraging and equipping women through Bible-based teaching and testimonies.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260610103000 +0000" stop="20260610110000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Believer's Voice of Victory</title>
    <desc>KCM is committed to keeping the Word of God before your eyes—teaching you how to live victoriously—so that you are rooted and grounded enough to overcome your own adversity, reach out to others and share those same principles. We endeavor to bring believers from the milk to the meat of the Word, and into full maturity in their walk with God.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260610110000 +0000" stop="20260610113000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Today with Marilyn &amp; Sarah</title>
    <desc>Marilyn&amp; Sarah Ministries is a global, miracle ministry responding to God's callto cover the earth with the Word and connect every one with the heart of God.For nearly 50 years they have empowered ordinary people to tap into thelife-changing power of the gospel through prayer, Bible teaching, humanitarianand evangelistic outreaches, healing meetings, and their daily TV program,Today with Marilyn &amp; Sarah.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260610113000 +0000" stop="20260610120000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Joyce Meyer: Enjoying Everyday Life</title>
    <desc>Joyce Meyer, one of the world’s leading practicalBible teachers and New York Times bestselling author, shares encouragement andadvice to help people enjoy daily life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260610120000 +0000" stop="20260610123000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Good Morning LIVE</title>
    <desc>Good Morning LIVE is an engaging 30-minute program designed to inspire, inform, and connect viewers to the heart of meaningful living. Hosted by James Epperly, this dynamic show brings together a unique blend of inspirational devotions, thought-provoking interviews, and discussions on current events that matter most to you. Each episode offers uplifting messages to start your day on a positive note, insightful conversations with special guests, and a closer look at how current events align with faith and personal growth. Whether you're seeking encouragement, knowledge, or a deeper connection to today's world, Good Morning LIVE is your source for faith-filled and relevant content. Join us weekday mornings to experience a fresh perspective, inspired by truth and guided by hope.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260610123000 +0000" stop="20260610130000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Worldview Matters</title>
    <desc>David Fiorazo is an author, ordained pastor, truth proclaimer, media contributor, and podcaster. Since the1990’s David has been working in both TV and radio broadcasting and in Christian ministry. On Worldview Matters, Fiorazo and expert guests tackle current events, demonic agendas &amp;movements, and controversial topics including church &amp; state issues, religious freedom, the culture war, Bible prophecy, education, politics, media&amp; more.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260610130000 +0000" stop="20260610133000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Gospel Truth with Andrew Wommack</title>
    <desc>God called Andrew over 50 years ago toteach the truth of the gospel to the body of Christ with a special emphasis onHis unconditional love and the balance between grace and faith. To fulfil thatcall, Andrew teaches at conferences, in churches, on television, throughpodcasts, and by training people from all walks of life globally at CharisBible College.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260610130000 +0000" stop="20260610133000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Gospel Truth with Andrew Wommack</title>
    <desc>Thirty-two years ago a man had an encounter with God that changed his life forever. Today, he shares that experience with thousands of people all over the world. The goal of Andrew Wommack is to reach as many people as possible with the love of God and message of grace and faith. He doesn’t measure the success of the ministry by the number of tapes distributed, books sold or offerings received. The real rewards, and proof that God is alive and working in people’s lives, are the many testimonies he receives from the people impacted by his teachings. To find out more, please visit our website at: http://www.awmi.net http://www.awmi.net/ www.awmi.net</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260610133000 +0000" stop="20260610140000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Rick Renner</title>
    <desc>Rick Renner is widely known for his interpretation of the Greek New Testament and his engaging teaching style. His teaching is punctuated by a unique ability to draw vividly descriptive word pictures from the Greek that illuminate the Scriptures in a fresh, new way. Rick also distinctively shares Bible principles through contemporary illustrations set against an extensive cultural and historical backdrop of New Testament times. In each episode of “Rick Renner,” Rick teaches in-depth on a passage of Scripture verse by verse, centered around a specific theme that is vitally relevant to the lives of believers who are hungry to dig deeper into the treasures of God’s Word. For more information, visit http://www.renner.org.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260610140000 +0000" stop="20260610143000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Manna Fest With Perry Stone</title>
    <desc>Manna-fest is the weekly television program of Perry Stone that deals with in-depth prophetic and practical studies of the Word of God. As biblical prophecy continues to unfold, you will find Manna-fest to be a resource to help you better understand where we are now in light of Bible prophecy and what the Bible says about the future. Be sure to tune in each week!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260610143000 +0000" stop="20260610150000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The James Epperly Show</title>
    <desc>"The James Epperly Show" is a Christian television program that aims to inspire and uplift viewers through faith-based content. Hosted by Pastor James Epperly, the show features insightful sermons, engaging interviews with prominent Christian figures, and heartfelt testimonials from individuals who have experienced life-changing transformations through faith. Each episode is designed to offer spiritual guidance, biblical wisdom, and practical advice for living a Christ-centered life. With its friendly and welcoming vibe, 'The James Epperly Show' aims to support viewers' spiritual development and enhance their connection with God, making it a treasured part of their weekly viewing schedule.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260610150000 +0000" stop="20260610153000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Concepts of Faith</title>
    <desc>Arkansas farmer, Charles Capps and family discovered that the spiritual truths Jesustaught could be applied to the everyday circumstances of life and change it!The practical teaching of how to do that is needed and relevant for everyonetoday. Charles, wife Peggy and daughter Annette share life changing truths.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260610153000 +0000" stop="20260610160000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Joyce Meyer: Enjoying Everyday Life</title>
    <desc>Joyce Meyer, one of the world’s leading practicalBible teachers and New York Times bestselling author, shares encouragement andadvice to help people enjoy daily life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260610160000 +0000" stop="20260610163000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The James Epperly Show</title>
    <desc>"The James Epperly Show" is a Christian television program that aims to inspire and uplift viewers through faith-based content. Hosted by Pastor James Epperly, the show features insightful sermons, engaging interviews with prominent Christian figures, and heartfelt testimonials from individuals who have experienced life-changing transformations through faith. Each episode is designed to offer spiritual guidance, biblical wisdom, and practical advice for living a Christ-centered life. With its friendly and welcoming vibe, 'The James Epperly Show' aims to support viewers' spiritual development and enhance their connection with God, making it a treasured part of their weekly viewing schedule.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260610163000 +0000" stop="20260610170000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The Jim Bakker Show</title>
    <desc>The Jim Bakker Show is an hour-long daily Christian broadcast that is aired throughout the United States, Canada, and the entire world through multiple broadcasts on Pioneer Network, Directv, Dish Network and other world wide satellites, and the PTL Television Network. Join Jim and Lori as they bring to the stage today’s greatest prophets, health experts, and leaders of the Christian world to discuss and understand Biblical prophecy and the Revelations of Gods Word.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260610170000 +0000" stop="20260610173000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>World Impact With Dr. Billy Wilson</title>
    <desc>Each week Voice of Salvation Ministries presents World Impact with Dr. Billy Wilson, canvassing the globe with the gospel. The program’s unique, contemporary format offers a clear evangelistic call to a relationship with Jesus Christ. Twenty episodes are recorded yearly, both in the studio facilities and field locations around the world. For more information: WorldImpact.tv http://worldimpact.tv/</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260610173000 +0000" stop="20260610180000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>VFI News</title>
    <desc>VFI News with Barry Segal brings you timely, insightful reports on Israel, the Middle East, andglobal events - analysed through a biblical and prophetic lens.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260610180000 +0000" stop="20260610190000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Brian &amp; Bobbie Houston - JesusFollowers.TV</title>
    <desc>"What greater honour and testimony is there than to be a devotedand passionate follower of the Lord Jesus Christ. Bobbie and I believe in the Church, thelocal church and the power and blessing of being planted (Psalm 92). We alsobelieve that in this day and age, God is creating multiple ways to water theseeds and greatness of calling within. Jesusfollowers.TV is here towelcome and extend our table of life and experience to you. This onlineplatform is here to love, encourage, and be a trustworthy voice of hope andinspiration in the days ahead. Our heart is to serve the God-given potentialwithin you and the Body of Christ. As Eph 2:21-22 says, we are all beingbuilt into a holy habitation for the Living God - brick by brick, stone bystone, with Jesus Christ as the Chief Cornerstone. May Jesusfollowers.TV be ablessing to you and those you care for” Brian and Bobbie Houston</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260610190000 +0000" stop="20260610193000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Victory With Paul Daugherty</title>
    <desc>Pastor Paul Daugherty and his wife Ashley lead a new generation with a practical, life-transforming message; a message of love, hope, healing and forgiveness.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260610193000 +0000" stop="20260610200000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Paula Today with Paula White-Cain</title>
    <desc>Paula Today Paula White-Cain along with her husband, Jonathan Cain discuss real life situations and offer practical, Biblical solutions. Down-to-earth, refreshing, sometimes unfiltered and always sharing the life-changing love of Jesus thru Paula’s in-depth teaching or Jon’s anointed music. About Paula Paula White-Cain is the President of Paula White Ministries and City of Destiny headquartered in Apopka, Florida, and the spiritual advisor to President Donald Trump. She hosts Paula Today, a nationally syndicated daily broadcast reaching a potential audience of 5.7 billion people in over 200 countries. She is a leading Pastor, a renowned life coach, bestselling author, and highly sought-after motivational speaker. Paula’s commitment to humanity is felt worldwide as she reaches out through numerous charities and compassion ministries, fulfilling her mission and call to transform lives, heal hearts and win souls. She lives in the Orlando area with her husband, Jonathan Cain.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260610200000 +0000" stop="20260610203000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Focus On The Family</title>
    <desc>Become a champion for your family in the time it takes to enjoy a cup of coffee! Every episode of the Focus on the Family Christian podcast helps you confidently guide your loved ones through the unique challenges faced by today’s Christian families. With over 40 years of trusted, compassionate stories of redemption, hosts Jim Daly and John Fuller connect you to biblically sound marriage and parenting help that is relatable, practical, and interesting. Listen/Learn/Apply/ThriveInChrist!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260610203000 +0000" stop="20260610210000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Billy Graham TV</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260610210000 +0000" stop="20260610213000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Joyce Meyer: Enjoying Everyday Life</title>
    <desc>Joyce Meyer, one of the world’s leading practical Bible teachers and NewYork Times bestselling author, shares encouragement and advice to help peopleenjoy daily life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260610213000 +0000" stop="20260610220000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Wisdom Speaks</title>
    <desc>Wisdom Speaks has been a beacon of inspiration and empowerment for four years. Our talk show delves into meaningful discussions on biblical teachings, honoring women, motherhood, and parenting. As a ministry for the marketplace, we strive to provide valuable insights and support, fostering a community centered around faith, salvation, and real-life challenges. We celebrate and uplift voices through engaging and heartfelt conversations.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260610220000 +0000" stop="20260610223000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The Counter Culture Mom Show</title>
    <desc>Former Hollywood actress, pop culture expert, Tina Griffin, left her Wisconsin dairy farm at the age of 20 and headed to Hollywood, CA to earn a BA in Film and Television broadcasting from California State University - Los Angeles. She’s traveled globally for the past 20 years delivering her eye-opening show, Hollywood Exposed https://counterculturemom.com/adult-session/ , explaining the real agenda behind the entertainment industry and its impact on the foundational development of today’s youth. Besides being in countless movies, Tina has worked on TV shows such as Jimmy Kimmel Live!, Young and the Restless, Days of Our Lives, Lizzie McGuire, Drake and Josh, and Malcolm in the Middle, competed in the Miss America pageant and worked at the OSCARS. She was involved with the Film Society as well as Women in Film and an active member of the Screen Actors Guild (SAG) and the American Federation of Television and Radio Artists (AFTRA). She has opened for bands such as Colton Dixon, Third Day, and Jeremy Camp. As host of The Counter Culture Mom Show, Tina gives the latest pop culture news and features experts covering critical topics such as cutting, suicide, bullying, online chat room d</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260610223000 +0000" stop="20260610230000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Believer’s Voice of Victory</title>
    <desc>KCMis committed to keeping the Word of God before your eyes—teaching you how tolive victoriously—so that you are rooted and grounded enough to overcome yourown adversity, reach out to others and share those same principles. We endeavorto bring believers from the milk to the meat of the Word, and into fullmaturity in their walk with God. Oneword from God has transformed the lives of thousands who dared to hear andbelieve. And one word from God will do the same for you.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260610230000 +0000" stop="20260610233000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The Mondo Show</title>
    <desc>I am so excited to introduce to you a new show. I would be honored for you to be a part of this brand new and exciting project! My new show is called “Mondo”. It’s a new TV show coming to the PTL Television Network available on ROKU, Apple TV, and Amazon Fire. This show is real, it’s raw, with an organic feel to the conversation. Sometimes I will be talking directly to you the audience, and at other times I will place you in the middle of the conversation, so you can experience what is really being said. The subject matter for the conversation and the questions will be the things people are afraid to ask, even though it is what everyone is thinking. I want you to meet the men and women who are making a difference in our communities, in our culture, and in our lives. It’s a journey to understand the misunderstood. It’s The Mondo Show.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260610233000 +0000" stop="20260611000000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Billy Graham TV</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260611000000 +0000" stop="20260611010000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>ORU Chapel</title>
    <desc>Ranked as one of the Top 50 “Most DiverseColleges in America” and Oklahoma’s #1 university for diversity (Niche 2023),ORU https://oru.edu/ https://www.youtube.com/redirect?event=video_description&amp;redir_token=QUFFLUhqbllUSTZqTUJzVGRzTU90OV82YVVWc1liNEJrZ3xBQ3Jtc0tramk4WUVQcUNabmM5SGlNQklEX2JJSk9kMVJ5MmNJQWFFLWlfTTBULXY3WnF0T3g2LUtiV3JOaW1mR0o2N20tOS04N0ZqUUlNblRNTWhyWkx5QVVzemQ5VDNqNTUzM1BZc2o1S1hFOHVEZEFtYU1mbw&amp;q=https%3A%2F%2Foru.edu%2F&amp;v=rPj4d3Ei0EU is a multicultural, global campus withmore than 4,500 students representing well over 120 nations. And as a Top 10university for Engagement (Wall Street Journal/Times Higher Ed ranked), ORUworks closely with students to develop whole leaders for the whole worldthrough a unique Whole Person approach to college education. If you’re anon-campus student or if you’re seeking an online education, ORU offersbachelors, masters, and doctoral degrees in a global, Spirit-empoweredenvironment. Explore Oral Roberts University https://oru.edu/ https://oru.edu/</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260611010000 +0000" stop="20260611013000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Paula Today with Paula White-Cain</title>
    <desc>Paula White-Cain along with her husband, Jonathan Cain discuss real life situations and offer practical, Biblical solutions. Down-to-earth, refreshing, sometimes unfiltered and always sharing the life-changing love of Jesus thru Paula’s in-depth teaching or Jon’s anointed music. About Paula Paula White-Cain is the President of Paula White Ministries and City of Destiny headquartered in Apopka, Florida, and the spiritual advisor to President Donald Trump. She hosts Paula Today, a nationally syndicated daily broadcast reaching a potential audience of 5.7 billion people in over 200 countries. She is a leading Pastor, a renowned life coach, bestselling author, and highly sought-after motivational speaker. Paula’s commitment to humanity is felt worldwide as she reaches out through numerous charities and compassion ministries, fulfilling her mission and call to transform lives, heal hearts and win souls. She lives in the Orlando area with her husband, Jonathan Cain.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260611013000 +0000" stop="20260611030000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Valor Christian College Chapel</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260611030000 +0000" stop="20260611040000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Brian &amp; Bobbie Houston - JesusFollowers.TV</title>
    <desc>"What greater honour and testimony is there than to be a devotedand passionate follower of the Lord Jesus Christ. Bobbie and I believe in the Church, thelocal church and the power and blessing of being planted (Psalm 92). We alsobelieve that in this day and age, God is creating multiple ways to water theseeds and greatness of calling within. Jesusfollowers.TV is here towelcome and extend our table of life and experience to you. This onlineplatform is here to love, encourage, and be a trustworthy voice of hope andinspiration in the days ahead. Our heart is to serve the God-given potentialwithin you and the Body of Christ. As Eph 2:21-22 says, we are all beingbuilt into a holy habitation for the Living God - brick by brick, stone bystone, with Jesus Christ as the Chief Cornerstone. May Jesusfollowers.TV be ablessing to you and those you care for” Brian and Bobbie Houston</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260611040000 +0000" stop="20260611060000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Raise The Standard Conference with Rod Parsley</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260611060000 +0000" stop="20260611063000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The Place For Miracles</title>
    <desc>The Place forMiracles is a half-hour broadcast hosted by Richard and Lindsay Roberts. Theprogram focuses on the power of prayer and biblical teaching by Richard andLindsay, plus occasional videos featuring classic sermons from Oral Roberts,praise and worship music, “Living Proof” miracle testimonies, including livecalls and video presentations, and frequent, special guest appearances.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260611063000 +0000" stop="20260611070000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Kingdom Connection with Jentezen Franklin</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260611070000 +0000" stop="20260611073000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Desire Of All Nations</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260611073000 +0000" stop="20260611080000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Samuel Rodriguez</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260611080000 +0000" stop="20260611083000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The Jim Bakker Show</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260611083000 +0000" stop="20260611090000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Believer’s Voice of Victory</title>
    <desc>KCMis committed to keeping the Word of God before your eyes—teaching you how tolive victoriously—so that you are rooted and grounded enough to overcome yourown adversity, reach out to others and share those same principles. We endeavorto bring believers from the milk to the meat of the Word, and into fullmaturity in their walk with God. Oneword from God has transformed the lives of thousands who dared to hear andbelieve. And one word from God will do the same for you.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260611090000 +0000" stop="20260611093000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Paula Today with Paula Whie-Cain</title>
    <desc>Paula White-Cain along with her husband, Jonathan Cain discuss real life situations and offer practical, Biblical solutions. Down-to-earth, refreshing, sometimes unfiltered and always sharing the life-changing love of Jesus thru Paula’s in-depth teaching or Jon’s anointed music.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260611093000 +0000" stop="20260611100000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Christian Music Countdown</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260611100000 +0000" stop="20260611103000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Glory Road with Dr. Candice Smithyman</title>
    <desc>The Glory Road TV show help you connect with heaven and the glory of the Lord to activate the spiritual gifts, purpose and destiny in your life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260611103000 +0000" stop="20260611110000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Believer's Voice of Victory</title>
    <desc>KCM is committed to keeping the Word of God before your eyes—teaching you how to live victoriously—so that you are rooted and grounded enough to overcome your own adversity, reach out to others and share those same principles. We endeavor to bring believers from the milk to the meat of the Word, and into full maturity in their walk with God.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260611110000 +0000" stop="20260611113000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Today with Marilyn &amp; Sarah</title>
    <desc>Marilyn&amp; Sarah Ministries is a global, miracle ministry responding to God's callto cover the earth with the Word and connect every one with the heart of God.For nearly 50 years they have empowered ordinary people to tap into thelife-changing power of the gospel through prayer, Bible teaching, humanitarianand evangelistic outreaches, healing meetings, and their daily TV program,Today with Marilyn &amp; Sarah.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260611113000 +0000" stop="20260611120000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Joyce Meyer: Enjoying Everyday Life</title>
    <desc>Joyce Meyer, one of the world’s leading practicalBible teachers and New York Times bestselling author, shares encouragement andadvice to help people enjoy daily life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260611120000 +0000" stop="20260611123000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Good Morning LIVE</title>
    <desc>Good Morning LIVE is an engaging 30-minute program designed to inspire, inform, and connect viewers to the heart of meaningful living. Hosted by James Epperly, this dynamic show brings together a unique blend of inspirational devotions, thought-provoking interviews, and discussions on current events that matter most to you. Each episode offers uplifting messages to start your day on a positive note, insightful conversations with special guests, and a closer look at how current events align with faith and personal growth. Whether you're seeking encouragement, knowledge, or a deeper connection to today's world, Good Morning LIVE is your source for faith-filled and relevant content. Join us weekday mornings to experience a fresh perspective, inspired by truth and guided by hope.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260611123000 +0000" stop="20260611130000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Jentezen Franklin</title>
    <desc>Jentezen Franklin is the Senior Pastor of Free Chapel, a multi-campus church. Each week his television program, Kingdom Connection, is broadcast on major networks all over the world. A New York Times best-selling author, Jentezen has written ten books including his most recent Acres of Diamonds, Love Like You’ve Never Been Hurt, the ground-breaking Fasting and Right People-Right Place-Right Plan.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260611130000 +0000" stop="20260611133000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Gospel Truth with Andrew Wommack</title>
    <desc>God called Andrew over 50 years ago toteach the truth of the gospel to the body of Christ with a special emphasis onHis unconditional love and the balance between grace and faith. To fulfil thatcall, Andrew teaches at conferences, in churches, on television, throughpodcasts, and by training people from all walks of life globally at CharisBible College.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260611130000 +0000" stop="20260611133000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Gospel Truth with Andrew Wommack</title>
    <desc>Thirty-two years ago a man had an encounter with God that changed his life forever. Today, he shares that experience with thousands of people all over the world. The goal of Andrew Wommack is to reach as many people as possible with the love of God and message of grace and faith. He doesn’t measure the success of the ministry by the number of tapes distributed, books sold or offerings received. The real rewards, and proof that God is alive and working in people’s lives, are the many testimonies he receives from the people impacted by his teachings. To find out more, please visit our website at: http://www.awmi.net http://www.awmi.net/ www.awmi.net</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260611133000 +0000" stop="20260611140000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Rick Renner</title>
    <desc>Rick Renner is widely known for his interpretation of the Greek New Testament and his engaging teaching style. His teaching is punctuated by a unique ability to draw vividly descriptive word pictures from the Greek that illuminate the Scriptures in a fresh, new way. Rick also distinctively shares Bible principles through contemporary illustrations set against an extensive cultural and historical backdrop of New Testament times. In each episode of “Rick Renner,” Rick teaches in-depth on a passage of Scripture verse by verse, centered around a specific theme that is vitally relevant to the lives of believers who are hungry to dig deeper into the treasures of God’s Word. For more information, visit http://www.renner.org.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260611140000 +0000" stop="20260611143000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Sid Roth's It's Supernatural</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260611143000 +0000" stop="20260611150000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The Elena &amp; Natalia Show</title>
    <desc>We're twins, Elena &amp; Natalia Maranian, and are passionate about sharing the love of Jesus through media. Together, we host and produce our talk show, The Elena &amp; Natalia Show in which we have conversations about Jesus, life, and love centered on the beauty and truth of God’s Word. We are also honored to serve at our family's TV network and media ministry, International Christian Family Network, Inc. where we hosted our former talk show, New Generation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260611150000 +0000" stop="20260611153000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The Winners Way with Mac Hammond</title>
    <desc>As our faith, courage, and discipline strengthen, we become vessels through which God can bring blessings to others. Discover more about this transformative journey—and our journey to plant fifty churches in five years—on The Winner's Way with Mac Hammond.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260611153000 +0000" stop="20260611160000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Joyce Meyer: Enjoying Everyday Life</title>
    <desc>Joyce Meyer, one of the world’s leading practicalBible teachers and New York Times bestselling author, shares encouragement andadvice to help people enjoy daily life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260611160000 +0000" stop="20260611163000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The James Epperly Show</title>
    <desc>"The James Epperly Show" is a Christian television program that aims to inspire and uplift viewers through faith-based content. Hosted by Pastor James Epperly, the show features insightful sermons, engaging interviews with prominent Christian figures, and heartfelt testimonials from individuals who have experienced life-changing transformations through faith. Each episode is designed to offer spiritual guidance, biblical wisdom, and practical advice for living a Christ-centered life. With its friendly and welcoming vibe, 'The James Epperly Show' aims to support viewers' spiritual development and enhance their connection with God, making it a treasured part of their weekly viewing schedule.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260611163000 +0000" stop="20260611170000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The Jim Bakker Show</title>
    <desc>The Jim Bakker Show is an hour-long daily Christian broadcast that is aired throughout the United States, Canada, and the entire world through multiple broadcasts on Pioneer Network, Directv, Dish Network and other world wide satellites, and the PTL Television Network. Join Jim and Lori as they bring to the stage today’s greatest prophets, health experts, and leaders of the Christian world to discuss and understand Biblical prophecy and the Revelations of Gods Word.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260611170000 +0000" stop="20260611173000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Kyle Winkler</title>
    <desc>Kyle Winkler is a practical Bible teacher, author of Silence Satan and Activating the Power of God’s Word, and creator of the popular Shut Up, Devil! app. Through his teachings, Kyle is known for using his own story to boast in the power of God’s Word for victorious living.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260611173000 +0000" stop="20260611180000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Samuel Rodriguez</title>
    <desc>New Season with Pastor Sam will usher in a "New Season" where individuals and families will no longer live in failure or merely survive but they will thrive for the glory of Jesus.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260611180000 +0000" stop="20260611183000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The James Epperly Show</title>
    <desc>"The James Epperly Show" is a Christian television program that aims to inspire and uplift viewers through faith-based content. Hosted by Pastor James Epperly, the show features insightful sermons, engaging interviews with prominent Christian figures, and heartfelt testimonials from individuals who have experienced life-changing transformations through faith. Each episode is designed to offer spiritual guidance, biblical wisdom, and practical advice for living a Christ-centered life. With its friendly and welcoming vibe, 'The James Epperly Show' aims to support viewers' spiritual development and enhance their connection with God, making it a treasured part of their weekly viewing schedule.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260611183000 +0000" stop="20260611190000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Christian Music Countdown</title>
    <desc>CMC is a TV showfeaturing contemporary Christian music videos. Each week we count down topmusic videos hand picked from our special guests.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260611190000 +0000" stop="20260611193000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Concepts Of Faith with Charles Capps</title>
    <desc>ArkansasFarmer, Charles Capps and family discovered that the spiritual truths Jesustaught could be applied to the everyday circumstances of life and change it!The practical teaching of how to do that is needed and relevant for everyonetoday. Charles, wife Peggy and daughter Annette share life changing truths.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260611193000 +0000" stop="20260611200000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Paula Today with Paula White-Cain</title>
    <desc>Paula Today Paula White-Cain along with her husband, Jonathan Cain discuss real life situations and offer practical, Biblical solutions. Down-to-earth, refreshing, sometimes unfiltered and always sharing the life-changing love of Jesus thru Paula’s in-depth teaching or Jon’s anointed music. About Paula Paula White-Cain is the President of Paula White Ministries and City of Destiny headquartered in Apopka, Florida, and the spiritual advisor to President Donald Trump. She hosts Paula Today, a nationally syndicated daily broadcast reaching a potential audience of 5.7 billion people in over 200 countries. She is a leading Pastor, a renowned life coach, bestselling author, and highly sought-after motivational speaker. Paula’s commitment to humanity is felt worldwide as she reaches out through numerous charities and compassion ministries, fulfilling her mission and call to transform lives, heal hearts and win souls. She lives in the Orlando area with her husband, Jonathan Cain.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260611200000 +0000" stop="20260611203000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Manna Fest with Perry Stone</title>
    <desc>Manna-fest is the weekly television program of Perry Stone that deals with in-depth prophetic and practical studies of the Word of God. As biblical prophecy continues to unfold, you will find Manna-fest to be a resource to help you better understand where we are now in light of Bible prophecy and what the Bible says about the future. Be sure to tune in each week!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260611203000 +0000" stop="20260611210000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Life In Christ With Pastor Joe Spence</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260611210000 +0000" stop="20260611213000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Joyce Meyer: Enjoying Everyday Life</title>
    <desc>Joyce Meyer, one of the world’s leading practical Bible teachers and NewYork Times bestselling author, shares encouragement and advice to help peopleenjoy daily life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260611220000 +0000" stop="20260611223000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The Counter Culture Mom Show</title>
    <desc>Former Hollywood actress, pop culture expert, Tina Griffin, left her Wisconsin dairy farm at the age of 20 and headed to Hollywood, CA to earn a BA in Film and Television broadcasting from California State University - Los Angeles. She’s traveled globally for the past 20 years delivering her eye-opening show, Hollywood Exposed https://counterculturemom.com/adult-session/ , explaining the real agenda behind the entertainment industry and its impact on the foundational development of today’s youth. Besides being in countless movies, Tina has worked on TV shows such as Jimmy Kimmel Live!, Young and the Restless, Days of Our Lives, Lizzie McGuire, Drake and Josh, and Malcolm in the Middle, competed in the Miss America pageant and worked at the OSCARS. She was involved with the Film Society as well as Women in Film and an active member of the Screen Actors Guild (SAG) and the American Federation of Television and Radio Artists (AFTRA). She has opened for bands such as Colton Dixon, Third Day, and Jeremy Camp. As host of The Counter Culture Mom Show, Tina gives the latest pop culture news and features experts covering critical topics such as cutting, suicide, bullying, online chat room d</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260611223000 +0000" stop="20260611230000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Believer’s Voice of Victory</title>
    <desc>KCMis committed to keeping the Word of God before your eyes—teaching you how tolive victoriously—so that you are rooted and grounded enough to overcome yourown adversity, reach out to others and share those same principles. We endeavorto bring believers from the milk to the meat of the Word, and into fullmaturity in their walk with God. Oneword from God has transformed the lives of thousands who dared to hear andbelieve. And one word from God will do the same for you.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260611230000 +0000" stop="20260611233000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>On The Path with Cheryl Nembhard</title>
    <desc>Join host Cheryl Nembhard On The Path, along with notable guests as theyshare their stories of triumph, tragedy, and the big lessons they've learnedalong their journey of faith.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260611233000 +0000" stop="20260612000000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Samuel Rodriguez</title>
    <desc>New Season with Pastor Sam will usher in a "New Season" where individuals and families will no longer live in failure or merely survive but they will thrive for the glory of Jesus.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260612000000 +0000" stop="20260612010000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>FlashPoint</title>
    <desc>Live program that addresses current events and issues facing America and the world. Often tackling topics that mainstream media does not, it delivers news and commentary under the anointing—encouraging evidence that God is indeed working to bring about His plans and purposes during these turbulent times. Hosted by Gene Bailey and joined by leaders in government, business, politics and the Church. FlashPoint’s rapidly become a trusted source of truth and hope. Wednesdays and Fridays at 8 p.m. ET/7 p.m. CT.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260612010000 +0000" stop="20260612013000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Paula Today with Paula White-Cain</title>
    <desc>Paula White-Cain along with her husband, Jonathan Cain discuss real life situations and offer practical, Biblical solutions. Down-to-earth, refreshing, sometimes unfiltered and always sharing the life-changing love of Jesus thru Paula’s in-depth teaching or Jon’s anointed music. About Paula Paula White-Cain is the President of Paula White Ministries and City of Destiny headquartered in Apopka, Florida, and the spiritual advisor to President Donald Trump. She hosts Paula Today, a nationally syndicated daily broadcast reaching a potential audience of 5.7 billion people in over 200 countries. She is a leading Pastor, a renowned life coach, bestselling author, and highly sought-after motivational speaker. Paula’s commitment to humanity is felt worldwide as she reaches out through numerous charities and compassion ministries, fulfilling her mission and call to transform lives, heal hearts and win souls. She lives in the Orlando area with her husband, Jonathan Cain.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260612013000 +0000" stop="20260612020000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The James Epperly Show</title>
    <desc>"The James Epperly Show" is a Christian television program that aims to inspire and uplift viewers through faith-based content. Hosted by Pastor James Epperly, the show features insightful sermons, engaging interviews with prominent Christian figures, and heartfelt testimonials from individuals who have experienced life-changing transformations through faith. Each episode is designed to offer spiritual guidance, biblical wisdom, and practical advice for living a Christ-centered life. With its friendly and welcoming vibe, 'The James Epperly Show' aims to support viewers' spiritual development and enhance their connection with God, making it a treasured part of their weekly viewing schedule.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260612020000 +0000" stop="20260612023000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The Place For Miracles with Richard &amp; Lindsay Roberts</title>
    <desc>This show, hosted by Richard and Lindsay Roberts, features prayer, miracle testimonies, teaching from the Bible, and praise and worship.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260612023000 +0000" stop="20260612030000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Manna-Fest with Perry Stone</title>
    <desc>Manna-fest is the weekly television program of Perry Stone that deals with in-depth prophetic and practical studies of the Word of God. As biblical prophecy continues to unfold, you will find Manna-fest to be a resource to help you better understand where we are now in light of Bible prophecy and what the Bible says about the future. Be sure to tune in each week!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260612030000 +0000" stop="20260612033000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The Jim Bakker Show</title>
    <desc>The Jim Bakker Show is an hour-long daily Christian broadcast that is aired throughout the United States, Canada, and the entire world through multiple broadcasts on Pioneer Network, Directv, Dish Network and other world wide satellites, and the PTL Television Network. Join Jim and Lori as they bring to the stage today’s greatest prophets, health experts, and leaders of the Christian world to discuss and understand Biblical prophecy and the Revelations of Gods Word.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260612033000 +0000" stop="20260612040000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The James Epperly Show</title>
    <desc>"The James Epperly Show" is a Christian television program that aims to inspire and uplift viewers through faith-based content. Hosted by Pastor James Epperly, the show features insightful sermons, engaging interviews with prominent Christian figures, and heartfelt testimonials from individuals who have experienced life-changing transformations through faith. Each episode is designed to offer spiritual guidance, biblical wisdom, and practical advice for living a Christ-centered life. With its friendly and welcoming vibe, 'The James Epperly Show' aims to support viewers' spiritual development and enhance their connection with God, making it a treasured part of their weekly viewing schedule.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260612040000 +0000" stop="20260612060000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Be Made Whole Worldwide Prayer Cloth Service with Rod Parsley</title>
    <desc>Experience the powerful anointing of our Be Made Whole Worldwide Prayer Cloth Service featuring Harvest Music Live and our outstanding choir. The miracle-working power of God changed multiplied hundreds of thousands, and now you can reserve your anointed prayer cloth from this year’s altar. The tangible transferrable anointing can heal your body, produce deliverance, family restoration, financial breakthrough, whatever you need!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260612060000 +0000" stop="20260612063000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The Place For Miracles</title>
    <desc>The Place forMiracles is a half-hour broadcast hosted by Richard and Lindsay Roberts. Theprogram focuses on the power of prayer and biblical teaching by Richard andLindsay, plus occasional videos featuring classic sermons from Oral Roberts,praise and worship music, “Living Proof” miracle testimonies, including livecalls and video presentations, and frequent, special guest appearances.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260612063000 +0000" stop="20260612070000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Kingdom Connection with Jentezen Franklin</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260612070000 +0000" stop="20260612073000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Desire Of All Nations</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260612073000 +0000" stop="20260612080000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Samuel Rodriguez</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260612080000 +0000" stop="20260612083000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The Jim Bakker Show</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260612083000 +0000" stop="20260612090000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Believer’s Voice of Victory</title>
    <desc>KCMis committed to keeping the Word of God before your eyes—teaching you how tolive victoriously—so that you are rooted and grounded enough to overcome yourown adversity, reach out to others and share those same principles. We endeavorto bring believers from the milk to the meat of the Word, and into fullmaturity in their walk with God. Oneword from God has transformed the lives of thousands who dared to hear andbelieve. And one word from God will do the same for you.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260612090000 +0000" stop="20260612093000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Paula Today with Paula Whie-Cain</title>
    <desc>Paula White-Cain along with her husband, Jonathan Cain discuss real life situations and offer practical, Biblical solutions. Down-to-earth, refreshing, sometimes unfiltered and always sharing the life-changing love of Jesus thru Paula’s in-depth teaching or Jon’s anointed music.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260612093000 +0000" stop="20260612100000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Christian Music Countdown</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260612100000 +0000" stop="20260612103000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Make Your Day Count with Lindsay Roberts</title>
    <desc>Lindsay Roberts hosts an uplifting program geared especially toward encouraging and equipping women through Bible-based teaching and testimonies.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260612103000 +0000" stop="20260612110000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Believer's Voice of Victory</title>
    <desc>KCM is committed to keeping the Word of God before your eyes—teaching you how to live victoriously—so that you are rooted and grounded enough to overcome your own adversity, reach out to others and share those same principles. We endeavor to bring believers from the milk to the meat of the Word, and into full maturity in their walk with God.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260612110000 +0000" stop="20260612113000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Today with Marilyn &amp; Sarah</title>
    <desc>Marilyn&amp; Sarah Ministries is a global, miracle ministry responding to God's callto cover the earth with the Word and connect every one with the heart of God.For nearly 50 years they have empowered ordinary people to tap into thelife-changing power of the gospel through prayer, Bible teaching, humanitarianand evangelistic outreaches, healing meetings, and their daily TV program,Today with Marilyn &amp; Sarah.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260612113000 +0000" stop="20260612120000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Joyce Meyer: Enjoying Everyday Life</title>
    <desc>Joyce Meyer, one of the world’s leading practicalBible teachers and New York Times bestselling author, shares encouragement andadvice to help people enjoy daily life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260612120000 +0000" stop="20260612123000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Good Morning LIVE</title>
    <desc>Good Morning LIVE is an engaging 30-minute program designed to inspire, inform, and connect viewers to the heart of meaningful living. Hosted by James Epperly, this dynamic show brings together a unique blend of inspirational devotions, thought-provoking interviews, and discussions on current events that matter most to you. Each episode offers uplifting messages to start your day on a positive note, insightful conversations with special guests, and a closer look at how current events align with faith and personal growth. Whether you're seeking encouragement, knowledge, or a deeper connection to today's world, Good Morning LIVE is your source for faith-filled and relevant content. Join us weekday mornings to experience a fresh perspective, inspired by truth and guided by hope.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260612123000 +0000" stop="20260612130000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Worldview Matters</title>
    <desc>David Fiorazo is an author,ordained pastor, truth proclaimer, media contributor, and podcaster. Since the1990’s David has been working in both TV and radio broadcasting and inChristian ministry. On Worldview Matters,Fiorazo and expert guests tackle current events, demonic agendas &amp;movements, and controversial topics including church &amp; state issues,religious freedom, the culture war, Bible prophecy, education, politics, media&amp; more.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260612130000 +0000" stop="20260612133000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Gospel Truth with Andrew Wommack</title>
    <desc>God called Andrew over 50 years ago toteach the truth of the gospel to the body of Christ with a special emphasis onHis unconditional love and the balance between grace and faith. To fulfil thatcall, Andrew teaches at conferences, in churches, on television, throughpodcasts, and by training people from all walks of life globally at CharisBible College.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260612130000 +0000" stop="20260612133000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Gospel Truth with Andrew Wommack</title>
    <desc>Thirty-two years ago a man had an encounter with God that changed his life forever. Today, he shares that experience with thousands of people all over the world. The goal of Andrew Wommack is to reach as many people as possible with the love of God and message of grace and faith. He doesn’t measure the success of the ministry by the number of tapes distributed, books sold or offerings received. The real rewards, and proof that God is alive and working in people’s lives, are the many testimonies he receives from the people impacted by his teachings. To find out more, please visit our website at: http://www.awmi.net http://www.awmi.net/ www.awmi.net</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260612133000 +0000" stop="20260612140000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Rick Renner</title>
    <desc>Rick Renner is widely known for his interpretation of the Greek New Testament and his engaging teaching style. His teaching is punctuated by a unique ability to draw vividly descriptive word pictures from the Greek that illuminate the Scriptures in a fresh, new way. Rick also distinctively shares Bible principles through contemporary illustrations set against an extensive cultural and historical backdrop of New Testament times. In each episode of “Rick Renner,” Rick teaches in-depth on a passage of Scripture verse by verse, centered around a specific theme that is vitally relevant to the lives of believers who are hungry to dig deeper into the treasures of God’s Word. For more information, visit http://www.renner.org.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260612140000 +0000" stop="20260612143000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Manna Fest With Perry Stone</title>
    <desc>Manna-fest is the weekly television program of Perry Stone that deals with in-depth prophetic and practical studies of the Word of God. As biblical prophecy continues to unfold, you will find Manna-fest to be a resource to help you better understand where we are now in light of Bible prophecy and what the Bible says about the future. Be sure to tune in each week!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260612143000 +0000" stop="20260612150000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The James Epperly Show</title>
    <desc>"The James Epperly Show" is a Christian television program that aims to inspire and uplift viewers through faith-based content. Hosted by Pastor James Epperly, the show features insightful sermons, engaging interviews with prominent Christian figures, and heartfelt testimonials from individuals who have experienced life-changing transformations through faith. Each episode is designed to offer spiritual guidance, biblical wisdom, and practical advice for living a Christ-centered life. With its friendly and welcoming vibe, 'The James Epperly Show' aims to support viewers' spiritual development and enhance their connection with God, making it a treasured part of their weekly viewing schedule.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260612150000 +0000" stop="20260612153000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The Winners Way with Mac Hammond</title>
    <desc>As our faith, courage, and discipline strengthen, we become vessels through which God can bring blessings to others. Discover more about this transformative journey—and our journey to plant fifty churches in five years—on The Winner's Way with Mac Hammond.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260612153000 +0000" stop="20260612160000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Joyce Meyer: Enjoying Everyday Life</title>
    <desc>Joyce Meyer, one of the world’s leading practicalBible teachers and New York Times bestselling author, shares encouragement andadvice to help people enjoy daily life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260612160000 +0000" stop="20260612163000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The James Epperly Show</title>
    <desc>"The James Epperly Show" is a Christian television program that aims to inspire and uplift viewers through faith-based content. Hosted by Pastor James Epperly, the show features insightful sermons, engaging interviews with prominent Christian figures, and heartfelt testimonials from individuals who have experienced life-changing transformations through faith. Each episode is designed to offer spiritual guidance, biblical wisdom, and practical advice for living a Christ-centered life. With its friendly and welcoming vibe, 'The James Epperly Show' aims to support viewers' spiritual development and enhance their connection with God, making it a treasured part of their weekly viewing schedule.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260612163000 +0000" stop="20260612170000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The Jim Bakker Show</title>
    <desc>The Jim Bakker Show is an hour-long daily Christian broadcast that is aired throughout the United States, Canada, and the entire world through multiple broadcasts on Pioneer Network, Directv, Dish Network and other world wide satellites, and the PTL Television Network. Join Jim and Lori as they bring to the stage today’s greatest prophets, health experts, and leaders of the Christian world to discuss and understand Biblical prophecy and the Revelations of Gods Word.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260612170000 +0000" stop="20260612173000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The Mondo Show</title>
    <desc>The Mondo Show is real, it’s raw, with an organicfeel to the conversation. Sometimes I will be talking directly to you theaudience, and at other times I will place you in the middle of theconversation, so you can experience what is really being said. The subject matter for the conversation and thequestions will be the things people are afraid to ask, even though it is whateveryone is thinking. I want you to meet the men and women who are making adifference in our communities, in our culture, and in our lives. It’s a journeyto understand the misunderstood. It’s The Mondo Show.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260612173000 +0000" stop="20260612180000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Samuel Rodriguez</title>
    <desc>New Season with Pastor Sam will usher in a "New Season" where individuals and families will no longer live in failure or merely survive but they will thrive for the glory of Jesus.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260612180000 +0000" stop="20260612190000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Great Awakening With Rodney Howard-Brown</title>
    <desc>Dr. Rodney Howard-Browne is the founder and pastor of Revival Ministries International in Tampa, Florida. In 1983, he pioneered a church in the Northeastern Cape and pastored there for two years. After that, Rodney taught classes in a leading Bible School for another two years. Rodney and his wife Adonica pastor a church in Tampa, Florida, The River at Tampa Bay, which they founded in 1996 and which now has 3000 members. These three things have remained constant since the church’s inception…dynamic praise and worship, anointed preaching and teaching of the Word, and powerful demonstrations of the Holy Spirit and power.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260612190000 +0000" stop="20260612193000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Victory With Paul Daugherty</title>
    <desc>Pastor Paul Daugherty and his wife Ashley lead a new generation with a practical, life-transforming message; a message of love, hope, healing and forgiveness.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260612193000 +0000" stop="20260612200000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Paula Today with Paula White-Cain</title>
    <desc>Paula Today Paula White-Cain along with her husband, Jonathan Cain discuss real life situations and offer practical, Biblical solutions. Down-to-earth, refreshing, sometimes unfiltered and always sharing the life-changing love of Jesus thru Paula’s in-depth teaching or Jon’s anointed music. About Paula Paula White-Cain is the President of Paula White Ministries and City of Destiny headquartered in Apopka, Florida, and the spiritual advisor to President Donald Trump. She hosts Paula Today, a nationally syndicated daily broadcast reaching a potential audience of 5.7 billion people in over 200 countries. She is a leading Pastor, a renowned life coach, bestselling author, and highly sought-after motivational speaker. Paula’s commitment to humanity is felt worldwide as she reaches out through numerous charities and compassion ministries, fulfilling her mission and call to transform lives, heal hearts and win souls. She lives in the Orlando area with her husband, Jonathan Cain.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260612200000 +0000" stop="20260612203000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Focus On The Family</title>
    <desc>Become a champion for your family in the time it takes to enjoy a cup of coffee! Every episode of the Focus on the Family Christian podcast helps you confidently guide your loved ones through the unique challenges faced by today’s Christian families. With over 40 years of trusted, compassionate stories of redemption, hosts Jim Daly and John Fuller connect you to biblically sound marriage and parenting help that is relatable, practical, and interesting. Listen/Learn/Apply/ThriveInChrist!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260612203000 +0000" stop="20260612210000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Coffee With Kim</title>
    <desc>COFFEE - Conversations of Friends of Faith to Encourage and Equip﻿﻿﻿ Do you know what happens when a few imperfect people gather around a table for real conversation? They discover they have the same questions about http://life...believe the same http://lies...and hide the same longings. They also discover that though they don't have all the answers, together they have so many more…and their wisdom is worth sharing. So come to our table for "COFFEE with Kim." Join us for conversations that are real…relevant…and right on time!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260612210000 +0000" stop="20260612213000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Joyce Meyer: Enjoying Everyday Life</title>
    <desc>Joyce Meyer, one of the world’s leading practical Bible teachers and NewYork Times bestselling author, shares encouragement and advice to help peopleenjoy daily life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260612213000 +0000" stop="20260612220000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Faith &amp; Law</title>
    <desc>Faith &amp; Law is a 30 minute variety program that focuses on the intersection of faith and law.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260612220000 +0000" stop="20260612223000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The Counter Culture Mom Show</title>
    <desc>Former Hollywood actress, pop culture expert, Tina Griffin, left her Wisconsin dairy farm at the age of 20 and headed to Hollywood, CA to earn a BA in Film and Television broadcasting from California State University - Los Angeles. She’s traveled globally for the past 20 years delivering her eye-opening show, Hollywood Exposed https://counterculturemom.com/adult-session/ , explaining the real agenda behind the entertainment industry and its impact on the foundational development of today’s youth. Besides being in countless movies, Tina has worked on TV shows such as Jimmy Kimmel Live!, Young and the Restless, Days of Our Lives, Lizzie McGuire, Drake and Josh, and Malcolm in the Middle, competed in the Miss America pageant and worked at the OSCARS. She was involved with the Film Society as well as Women in Film and an active member of the Screen Actors Guild (SAG) and the American Federation of Television and Radio Artists (AFTRA). She has opened for bands such as Colton Dixon, Third Day, and Jeremy Camp. As host of The Counter Culture Mom Show, Tina gives the latest pop culture news and features experts covering critical topics such as cutting, suicide, bullying, online chat room d</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260612223000 +0000" stop="20260612230000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Believer’s Voice of Victory</title>
    <desc>KCMis committed to keeping the Word of God before your eyes—teaching you how tolive victoriously—so that you are rooted and grounded enough to overcome yourown adversity, reach out to others and share those same principles. We endeavorto bring believers from the milk to the meat of the Word, and into fullmaturity in their walk with God. Oneword from God has transformed the lives of thousands who dared to hear andbelieve. And one word from God will do the same for you.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260612230000 +0000" stop="20260613000000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>ORU Chapel</title>
    <desc>Ranked as one of the Top 50 “Most DiverseColleges in America” and Oklahoma’s #1 university for diversity (Niche 2023),ORU https://oru.edu/ https://www.youtube.com/redirect?event=video_description&amp;redir_token=QUFFLUhqbllUSTZqTUJzVGRzTU90OV82YVVWc1liNEJrZ3xBQ3Jtc0tramk4WUVQcUNabmM5SGlNQklEX2JJSk9kMVJ5MmNJQWFFLWlfTTBULXY3WnF0T3g2LUtiV3JOaW1mR0o2N20tOS04N0ZqUUlNblRNTWhyWkx5QVVzemQ5VDNqNTUzM1BZc2o1S1hFOHVEZEFtYU1mbw&amp;q=https%3A%2F%2Foru.edu%2F&amp;v=rPj4d3Ei0EU is a multicultural, global campus withmore than 4,500 students representing well over 120 nations. And as a Top 10university for Engagement (Wall Street Journal/Times Higher Ed ranked), ORUworks closely with students to develop whole leaders for the whole worldthrough a unique Whole Person approach to college education. If you’re anon-campus student or if you’re seeking an online education, ORU offersbachelors, masters, and doctoral degrees in a global, Spirit-empoweredenvironment. Explore Oral Roberts University https://oru.edu/ https://oru.edu/</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260613000000 +0000" stop="20260613010000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>FlashPoint</title>
    <desc>Live program that addresses current events and issues facing America and the world. Often tackling topics that mainstream media does not, it delivers news and commentary under the anointing—encouraging evidence that God is indeed working to bring about His plans and purposes during these turbulent times. Hosted by Gene Bailey and joined by leaders in government, business, politics and the Church. FlashPoint’s rapidly become a trusted source of truth and hope. Wednesdays and Fridays at 8 p.m. ET/7 p.m. CT.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260613010000 +0000" stop="20260613013000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Paula Today with Paula White-Cain</title>
    <desc>Paula White-Cain along with her husband, Jonathan Cain discuss real life situations and offer practical, Biblical solutions. Down-to-earth, refreshing, sometimes unfiltered and always sharing the life-changing love of Jesus thru Paula’s in-depth teaching or Jon’s anointed music. About Paula Paula White-Cain is the President of Paula White Ministries and City of Destiny headquartered in Apopka, Florida, and the spiritual advisor to President Donald Trump. She hosts Paula Today, a nationally syndicated daily broadcast reaching a potential audience of 5.7 billion people in over 200 countries. She is a leading Pastor, a renowned life coach, bestselling author, and highly sought-after motivational speaker. Paula’s commitment to humanity is felt worldwide as she reaches out through numerous charities and compassion ministries, fulfilling her mission and call to transform lives, heal hearts and win souls. She lives in the Orlando area with her husband, Jonathan Cain.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260613013000 +0000" stop="20260613030000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Valor Christian College Chapel</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260613030000 +0000" stop="20260613040000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Brian &amp; Bobbie Houston - JesusFollowers.TV</title>
    <desc>"What greater honour and testimony is there than to be a devotedand passionate follower of the Lord Jesus Christ. Bobbie and I believe in the Church, thelocal church and the power and blessing of being planted (Psalm 92). We alsobelieve that in this day and age, God is creating multiple ways to water theseeds and greatness of calling within. Jesusfollowers.TV is here towelcome and extend our table of life and experience to you. This onlineplatform is here to love, encourage, and be a trustworthy voice of hope andinspiration in the days ahead. Our heart is to serve the God-given potentialwithin you and the Body of Christ. As Eph 2:21-22 says, we are all beingbuilt into a holy habitation for the Living God - brick by brick, stone bystone, with Jesus Christ as the Chief Cornerstone. May Jesusfollowers.TV be ablessing to you and those you care for” Brian and Bobbie Houston</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260613040000 +0000" stop="20260613060000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Raise The Standard Conference with Rod Parsley</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260613060000 +0000" stop="20260613063000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The Place For Miracles</title>
    <desc>The Place forMiracles is a half-hour broadcast hosted by Richard and Lindsay Roberts. Theprogram focuses on the power of prayer and biblical teaching by Richard andLindsay, plus occasional videos featuring classic sermons from Oral Roberts,praise and worship music, “Living Proof” miracle testimonies, including livecalls and video presentations, and frequent, special guest appearances.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260613063000 +0000" stop="20260613070000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Kingdom Connection with Jentezen Franklin</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260613070000 +0000" stop="20260613073000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Desire Of All Nations</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260613073000 +0000" stop="20260613080000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Samuel Rodriguez</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260613080000 +0000" stop="20260613100000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Valor Christian College Chapel</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260613100000 +0000" stop="20260613103000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Faithville</title>
    <desc>Fun-filled, action-packed 30-minute comedy set in the 1940's to teach God's Word! Something taught with pleasure is learned full measure!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260613103000 +0000" stop="20260613110000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Miss Charity's Diner</title>
    <desc>Miss Charity welcomes kids into her diner to learn about Friendship, Patience, Faithfulness, Creativity and more! Stop in to hear a story with Miss Geranium, visit with Farmer Shalom and Dusty the dog, or learn safety and responsibility from Constable Howie. A fun-filled lesson teaching God's Word in every show.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260613110000 +0000" stop="20260613113000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Seasons</title>
    <desc>Follow the journey of young Josh and sister Lexie who go to live with the grandparents when life becomes difficult for single mother Debbie. See that God is faithful even in the most difficult of circumstances and discover a show that gives hope to every generation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260613113000 +0000" stop="20260613120000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Gospel Time Square</title>
    <desc>Friends meet at Gospel Time Square, the corner of 7th St. and Narrow Way. Join Melody and the rest as they learn about some of life's biggest lessons! Respect, Family, Serving and more!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260613120000 +0000" stop="20260613123000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Lessons From The Bible, with Pastor Doug</title>
    <desc>Join Pastor Doug, Dusty, Amelia and all the characters as they learn about the Bible and how it applies to daily life. Games, songs, and some silly puppets will inspire kids to follow along and get into God's Word!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260613123000 +0000" stop="20260613130000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Faithville</title>
    <desc>Fun-filled, action-packed 30-minute comedy set in the 1940's to teach God's Word! Something taught with pleasure is learned full measure!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260613130000 +0000" stop="20260613133000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Miss Charity's Diner</title>
    <desc>Miss Charity welcomes kids into her diner to learn about Friendship, Patience, Faithfulness, Creativity and more! Stop in to hear a story with Miss Geranium, visit with Farmer Shalom and Dusty the dog, or learn safety and responsibility from Constable Howie. A fun-filled lesson teaching God's Word in every show.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260613133000 +0000" stop="20260613140000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Seasons</title>
    <desc>Follow the journey of young Josh and sister Lexie who go to live with the grandparents when life becomes difficult for single mother Debbie. See that God is faithful even in the most difficult of circumstances and discover a show that gives hope to every generation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260613140000 +0000" stop="20260613143000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Gospel Time Square</title>
    <desc>Friends meet at Gospel Time Square, the corner of 7th St. and Narrow Way. Join Melody and the rest as they learn about some of life's biggest lessons! Respect, Family, Serving and more!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260613143000 +0000" stop="20260613150000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Lessons From The Bible, with Pastor Doug</title>
    <desc>Join Pastor Doug, Dusty, Amelia and all the characters as they learn about the Bible and how it applies to daily life. Games, songs, and some silly puppets will inspire kids to follow along and get into God's Word!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260613150000 +0000" stop="20260613160000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>ORU Chapel</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260613160000 +0000" stop="20260613163000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The James Epperly Show</title>
    <desc>"The James Epperly Show" is a Christian television program that aims to inspire and uplift viewers through faith-based content. Hosted by Pastor James Epperly, the show features insightful sermons, engaging interviews with prominent Christian figures, and heartfelt testimonials from individuals who have experienced life-changing transformations through faith. Each episode is designed to offer spiritual guidance, biblical wisdom, and practical advice for living a Christ-centered life. With its friendly and welcoming vibe, 'The James Epperly Show' aims to support viewers' spiritual development and enhance their connection with God, making it a treasured part of their weekly viewing schedule.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260613163000 +0000" stop="20260613170000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Faith &amp; Law</title>
    <desc>Faith &amp; Law is a 30-minute variety program that focuses on theintersection of faith and law.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260613170000 +0000" stop="20260613190000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Valor Christian College Chapel</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260613190000 +0000" stop="20260613193000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Christian Music Countdown</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260613193000 +0000" stop="20260613200000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Worldview Matters</title>
    <desc>On Worldview Matters, Fiorazo and expert guests tackle currentevents, demonic agendas &amp; movements, and controversial topics includingchurch &amp; state issues, religious freedom, the culture war, Bible prophecy,education, politics, media &amp; more.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260613200000 +0000" stop="20260613203000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The James Epperly Show</title>
    <desc>"The James Epperly Show" is a Christian television program that aims to inspire and uplift viewers through faith-based content. Hosted by Pastor James Epperly, the show features insightful sermons, engaging interviews with prominent Christian figures, and heartfelt testimonials from individuals who have experienced life-changing transformations through faith. Each episode is designed to offer spiritual guidance, biblical wisdom, and practical advice for living a Christ-centered life. With its friendly and welcoming vibe, 'The James Epperly Show' aims to support viewers' spiritual development and enhance their connection with God, making it a treasured part of their weekly viewing schedule.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260613203000 +0000" stop="20260613210000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>VFI News</title>
    <desc>VFI News with Barry Segal brings you timely, insightful reports on Israel, the Middle East, andglobal events - analysed through a biblical and prophetic lens.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260613210000 +0000" stop="20260613213000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The Jim Bakker Show</title>
    <desc>The Jim Bakker Show is an hour-long dailyChristian broadcast that is aired throughout the United States, Canada, and theentire world through multiple broadcasts on Directv, Dish Network and otherworld wide satellites, PTL Television Network, and the Pioneer Network. Join Jim and Lori Bakker as they bring tothe stage today’s greatest prophets, health experts, and leaders of theChristian world to discuss and understand Biblical prophecy and the Revelationsof God’s Word.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260613213000 +0000" stop="20260613230000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Hope City Church</title>
    <desc>Join Pastor James Epperly and the congregation of Hope City Church for inspirational teaching and ministry.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260613230000 +0000" stop="20260614000000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>ORU Chapel</title>
    <desc>Ranked as one of the Top 50 “Most DiverseColleges in America” and Oklahoma’s #1 university for diversity (Niche 2023),ORU https://oru.edu/ https://www.youtube.com/redirect?event=video_description&amp;redir_token=QUFFLUhqbllUSTZqTUJzVGRzTU90OV82YVVWc1liNEJrZ3xBQ3Jtc0tramk4WUVQcUNabmM5SGlNQklEX2JJSk9kMVJ5MmNJQWFFLWlfTTBULXY3WnF0T3g2LUtiV3JOaW1mR0o2N20tOS04N0ZqUUlNblRNTWhyWkx5QVVzemQ5VDNqNTUzM1BZc2o1S1hFOHVEZEFtYU1mbw&amp;q=https%3A%2F%2Foru.edu%2F&amp;v=rPj4d3Ei0EU is a multicultural, global campus withmore than 4,500 students representing well over 120 nations. And as a Top 10university for Engagement (Wall Street Journal/Times Higher Ed ranked), ORUworks closely with students to develop whole leaders for the whole worldthrough a unique Whole Person approach to college education. If you’re anon-campus student or if you’re seeking an online education, ORU offersbachelors, masters, and doctoral degrees in a global, Spirit-empoweredenvironment. Explore Oral Roberts University https://oru.edu/</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260614000000 +0000" stop="20260614003000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The James Epperly Show</title>
    <desc>"The James Epperly Show" is a Christian television program that aims to inspire and uplift viewers through faith-based content. Hosted by Pastor James Epperly, the show features insightful sermons, engaging interviews with prominent Christian figures, and heartfelt testimonials from individuals who have experienced life-changing transformations through faith. Each episode is designed to offer spiritual guidance, biblical wisdom, and practical advice for living a Christ-centered life. With its friendly and welcoming vibe, 'The James Epperly Show' aims to support viewers' spiritual development and enhance their connection with God, making it a treasured part of their weekly viewing schedule.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260614003000 +0000" stop="20260614010000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Life In Christ With Pastor Joe Spence</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260614010000 +0000" stop="20260614013000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Christian Music Countdown</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260614013000 +0000" stop="20260614020000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Manna Fest with Perry Stone</title>
    <desc>Manna-fest is the weekly television program of Perry Stone that deals with in-depth prophetic and practical studies of the Word of God. As biblical prophecy continues to unfold, you will find Manna-fest to be a resource to help you better understand where we are now in light of Bible prophecy and what the Bible says about the future. Be sure to tune in each week!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260614020000 +0000" stop="20260614040000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Valor Christian College Chapel</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260614040000 +0000" stop="20260614060000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Be Made Whole Worldwide Prayer Cloth Service with Rod Parsley</title>
    <desc>Experience the powerful anointing of our Be Made Whole Worldwide Prayer Cloth Service featuring Harvest Music Live and our outstanding choir. The miracle-working power of God changed multiplied hundreds of thousands, and now you can reserve your anointed prayer cloth from this year’s altar. The tangible transferrable anointing can heal your body, produce deliverance, family restoration, financial breakthrough, whatever you need!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260614060000 +0000" stop="20260614063000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The Place For Miracles</title>
    <desc>The Place forMiracles is a half-hour broadcast hosted by Richard and Lindsay Roberts. Theprogram focuses on the power of prayer and biblical teaching by Richard andLindsay, plus occasional videos featuring classic sermons from Oral Roberts,praise and worship music, “Living Proof” miracle testimonies, including livecalls and video presentations, and frequent, special guest appearances.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260614063000 +0000" stop="20260614070000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Kingdom Connection with Jentezen Franklin</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260614070000 +0000" stop="20260614073000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Desire Of All Nations</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260614073000 +0000" stop="20260614080000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Samuel Rodriguez</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260614080000 +0000" stop="20260614100000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Valor Christian College Chapel</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260614100000 +0000" stop="20260614103000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Faithville</title>
    <desc>Fun-filled, action-packed 30-minute comedy set in the 1940's to teach God's Word! Something taught with pleasure is learned full measure!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260614103000 +0000" stop="20260614110000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Miss Charity's Diner</title>
    <desc>Miss Charity welcomes kids into her diner to learn about Friendship, Patience, Faithfulness, Creativity and more! Stop in to hear a story with Miss Geranium, visit with Farmer Shalom and Dusty the dog, or learn safety and responsibility from Constable Howie. A fun-filled lesson teaching God's Word in every show.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260614110000 +0000" stop="20260614113000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Seasons</title>
    <desc>Follow the journey of young Josh and sister Lexie who go to live with the grandparents when life becomes difficult for single mother Debbie. See that God is faithful even in the most difficult of circumstances and discover a show that gives hope to every generation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260614113000 +0000" stop="20260614130000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Valor Christian College Chapel</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260614130000 +0000" stop="20260614140000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>ORU Chapel</title>
    <desc>Ranked as one of the Top 50 “Most DiverseColleges in America” and Oklahoma’s #1 university for diversity (Niche 2023),ORU https://oru.edu/ https://www.youtube.com/redirect?event=video_description&amp;redir_token=QUFFLUhqbllUSTZqTUJzVGRzTU90OV82YVVWc1liNEJrZ3xBQ3Jtc0tramk4WUVQcUNabmM5SGlNQklEX2JJSk9kMVJ5MmNJQWFFLWlfTTBULXY3WnF0T3g2LUtiV3JOaW1mR0o2N20tOS04N0ZqUUlNblRNTWhyWkx5QVVzemQ5VDNqNTUzM1BZc2o1S1hFOHVEZEFtYU1mbw&amp;q=https%3A%2F%2Foru.edu%2F&amp;v=rPj4d3Ei0EU is a multicultural, global campus withmore than 4,500 students representing well over 120 nations. And as a Top 10university for Engagement (Wall Street Journal/Times Higher Ed ranked), ORUworks closely with students to develop whole leaders for the whole worldthrough a unique Whole Person approach to college education. If you’re anon-campus student or if you’re seeking an online education, ORU offersbachelors, masters, and doctoral degrees in a global, Spirit-empoweredenvironment. Explore Oral Roberts University https://oru.edu/ https://oru.edu/</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260614140000 +0000" stop="20260614153000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Hope City Church LIVE</title>
    <desc>Join Pastor James Epperly and the congregation of Hope City Church for LIVE inspirational teaching and ministry.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260614153000 +0000" stop="20260614163000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Brian &amp; Bobbie Houston - JesusFollowers.TV</title>
    <desc>"What greater honour and testimony is there than to be a devotedand passionate follower of the Lord Jesus Christ. Bobbie and I believe in the Church, thelocal church and the power and blessing of being planted (Psalm 92). We alsobelieve that in this day and age, God is creating multiple ways to water theseeds and greatness of calling within. Jesusfollowers.TV is here towelcome and extend our table of life and experience to you. This onlineplatform is here to love, encourage, and be a trustworthy voice of hope andinspiration in the days ahead. Our heart is to serve the God-given potentialwithin you and the Body of Christ. As Eph 2:21-22 says, we are all beingbuilt into a holy habitation for the Living God - brick by brick, stone bystone, with Jesus Christ as the Chief Cornerstone. May Jesusfollowers.TV be ablessing to you and those you care for” Brian and Bobbie Houston</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260614163000 +0000" stop="20260614170000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Christian Music Countdown</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260614170000 +0000" stop="20260614173000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Jentezen Franklin</title>
    <desc>Jentezen Franklin is the Senior Pastor of Free Chapel, a multi-campus church. Each week his television program, Kingdom Connection, is broadcast on major networks all over the world. A New York Times best-selling author, Jentezen has written ten books including his most recent Acres of Diamonds, Love Like You’ve Never Been Hurt, the ground-breaking Fasting and Right People-Right Place-Right Plan.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260614173000 +0000" stop="20260614180000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The James Epperly Show</title>
    <desc>"The James Epperly Show" is a Christian television program that aims to inspire and uplift viewers through faith-based content. Hosted by Pastor James Epperly, the show features insightful sermons, engaging interviews with prominent Christian figures, and heartfelt testimonials from individuals who have experienced life-changing transformations through faith. Each episode is designed to offer spiritual guidance, biblical wisdom, and practical advice for living a Christ-centered life. With its friendly and welcoming vibe, 'The James Epperly Show' aims to support viewers' spiritual development and enhance their connection with God, making it a treasured part of their weekly viewing schedule.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260614180000 +0000" stop="20260614183000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Joyce Meyer: Enjoying Everyday Life</title>
    <desc>Joyce Meyer, one of the world’s leading practical Bible teachers and NewYork Times bestselling author, shares encouragement and advice to help peopleenjoy daily life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260614183000 +0000" stop="20260614190000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Worldview Matters</title>
    <desc>On Worldview Matters, Fiorazo and expert guests tackle currentevents, demonic agendas &amp; movements, and controversial topics includingchurch &amp; state issues, religious freedom, the culture war, Bible prophecy,education, politics, media &amp; more.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260614190000 +0000" stop="20260614193000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Victory with Paul Dougherty</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260614193000 +0000" stop="20260614200000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The James Epperly Show</title>
    <desc>"The James Epperly Show" is a Christian television program that aims to inspire and uplift viewers through faith-based content. Hosted by Pastor James Epperly, the show features insightful sermons, engaging interviews with prominent Christian figures, and heartfelt testimonials from individuals who have experienced life-changing transformations through faith. Each episode is designed to offer spiritual guidance, biblical wisdom, and practical advice for living a Christ-centered life. With its friendly and welcoming vibe, 'The James Epperly Show' aims to support viewers' spiritual development and enhance their connection with God, making it a treasured part of their weekly viewing schedule.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260614200000 +0000" stop="20260614203000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Joyce Meyer: Enjoying Everyday Life</title>
    <desc>Joyce Meyer, one of the world’s leading practical Bible teachers and NewYork Times bestselling author, shares encouragement and advice to help peopleenjoy daily life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260614203000 +0000" stop="20260614210000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Kyle Winkler</title>
    <desc>Kyle Winkler is a practical Bible teacher, author of Silence Satan and Activating the Power of God’s Word, and creator of the popular Shut Up, Devil! app. Through his teachings, Kyle is known for using his own story to boast in the power of God’s Word for victorious living.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260614210000 +0000" stop="20260614213000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Christian Music Countdown</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260614213000 +0000" stop="20260614220000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Faith &amp; Law</title>
    <desc>Faith &amp; Law is a 30-minute variety program that focuses on the intersection of faith and law.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260614220000 +0000" stop="20260614223000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>On The Path with Cheryl Nembhard</title>
    <desc>Join host Cheryl Nembhard On The Path, along with notable guests as they share their stories of triumph, tragedy, and the big lessons they've learned along their journey of faith.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260614223000 +0000" stop="20260614230000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Life In Christ With Pastor Joe Spence</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260614230000 +0000" stop="20260615003000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Hope City Church</title>
    <desc>Join Pastor James Epperly and the congregation of Hope City Church for inspirational teaching and ministry.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260615003000 +0000" stop="20260615010000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Run The Streets with Debra George</title>
    <desc>Debra takes you to the darkest streets of America to win souls.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260615010000 +0000" stop="20260615013000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Christian Music Countdown</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260615013000 +0000" stop="20260615020000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The James Epperly Show</title>
    <desc>"The James Epperly Show" is a Christian television program that aims to inspire and uplift viewers through faith-based content. Hosted by Pastor James Epperly, the show features insightful sermons, engaging interviews with prominent Christian figures, and heartfelt testimonials from individuals who have experienced life-changing transformations through faith. Each episode is designed to offer spiritual guidance, biblical wisdom, and practical advice for living a Christ-centered life. With its friendly and welcoming vibe, 'The James Epperly Show' aims to support viewers' spiritual development and enhance their connection with God, making it a treasured part of their weekly viewing schedule.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260615020000 +0000" stop="20260615040000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Valor Christian College Chapel</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260615040000 +0000" stop="20260615060000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Be Made Whole Worldwide Prayer Cloth Service with Rod Parsley</title>
    <desc>Experience the powerful anointing of our Be Made Whole Worldwide Prayer Cloth Service featuring Harvest Music Live and our outstanding choir. The miracle-working power of God changed multiplied hundreds of thousands, and now you can reserve your anointed prayer cloth from this year’s altar. The tangible transferrable anointing can heal your body, produce deliverance, family restoration, financial breakthrough, whatever you need!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260615060000 +0000" stop="20260615063000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The Place For Miracles</title>
    <desc>The Place forMiracles is a half-hour broadcast hosted by Richard and Lindsay Roberts. Theprogram focuses on the power of prayer and biblical teaching by Richard andLindsay, plus occasional videos featuring classic sermons from Oral Roberts,praise and worship music, “Living Proof” miracle testimonies, including livecalls and video presentations, and frequent, special guest appearances.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260615063000 +0000" stop="20260615070000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Kingdom Connection with Jentezen Franklin</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260615070000 +0000" stop="20260615073000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Desire Of All Nations</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260615073000 +0000" stop="20260615080000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Samuel Rodriguez</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260615080000 +0000" stop="20260615083000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The Jim Bakker Show</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260615083000 +0000" stop="20260615090000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Believer’s Voice of Victory</title>
    <desc>KCMis committed to keeping the Word of God before your eyes—teaching you how tolive victoriously—so that you are rooted and grounded enough to overcome yourown adversity, reach out to others and share those same principles. We endeavorto bring believers from the milk to the meat of the Word, and into fullmaturity in their walk with God. Oneword from God has transformed the lives of thousands who dared to hear andbelieve. And one word from God will do the same for you.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260615090000 +0000" stop="20260615093000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Paula Today with Paula Whie-Cain</title>
    <desc>Paula White-Cain along with her husband, Jonathan Cain discuss real life situations and offer practical, Biblical solutions. Down-to-earth, refreshing, sometimes unfiltered and always sharing the life-changing love of Jesus thru Paula’s in-depth teaching or Jon’s anointed music.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260615093000 +0000" stop="20260615100000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Christian Music Countdown</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260615100000 +0000" stop="20260615103000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Make Your Day Count with Lindsay Roberts</title>
    <desc>Lindsay Roberts hosts an uplifting program geared especially toward encouraging and equipping women through Bible-based teaching and testimonies.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260615103000 +0000" stop="20260615110000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Believer's Voice of Victory</title>
    <desc>KCM is committed to keeping the Word of God before your eyes—teaching you how to live victoriously—so that you are rooted and grounded enough to overcome your own adversity, reach out to others and share those same principles. We endeavor to bring believers from the milk to the meat of the Word, and into full maturity in their walk with God.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260615110000 +0000" stop="20260615113000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Today with Marilyn &amp; Sarah</title>
    <desc>Marilyn&amp; Sarah Ministries is a global, miracle ministry responding to God's callto cover the earth with the Word and connect every one with the heart of God.For nearly 50 years they have empowered ordinary people to tap into thelife-changing power of the gospel through prayer, Bible teaching, humanitarianand evangelistic outreaches, healing meetings, and their daily TV program,Today with Marilyn &amp; Sarah.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260615113000 +0000" stop="20260615120000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Joyce Meyer: Enjoying Everyday Life</title>
    <desc>Joyce Meyer, one of the world’s leading practicalBible teachers and New York Times bestselling author, shares encouragement andadvice to help people enjoy daily life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260615120000 +0000" stop="20260615123000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Good Morning LIVE</title>
    <desc>Good Morning LIVE is an engaging 30-minute program designed to inspire, inform, and connect viewers to the heart of meaningful living. Hosted by James Epperly, this dynamic show brings together a unique blend of inspirational devotions, thought-provoking interviews, and discussions on current events that matter most to you. Each episode offers uplifting messages to start your day on a positive note, insightful conversations with special guests, and a closer look at how current events align with faith and personal growth. Whether you're seeking encouragement, knowledge, or a deeper connection to today's world, Good Morning LIVE is your source for faith-filled and relevant content. Join us weekday mornings to experience a fresh perspective, inspired by truth and guided by hope.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260615123000 +0000" stop="20260615130000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Worldview Matters</title>
    <desc>David Fiorazo is an author, ordained pastor, truth proclaimer, media contributor, and podcaster. Since the1990’s David has been working in both TV and radio broadcasting and in Christian ministry. On Worldview Matters, Fiorazo and expert guests tackle current events, demonic agendas &amp;movements, and controversial topics including church &amp; state issues, religious freedom, the culture war, Bible prophecy, education, politics, media&amp; more.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260615130000 +0000" stop="20260615133000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Gospel Truth with Andrew Wommack</title>
    <desc>God called Andrew over 50 years ago toteach the truth of the gospel to the body of Christ with a special emphasis onHis unconditional love and the balance between grace and faith. To fulfil thatcall, Andrew teaches at conferences, in churches, on television, throughpodcasts, and by training people from all walks of life globally at CharisBible College.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260615130000 +0000" stop="20260615133000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Gospel Truth with Andrew Wommack</title>
    <desc>Thirty-two years ago a man had an encounter with God that changed his life forever. Today, he shares that experience with thousands of people all over the world. The goal of Andrew Wommack is to reach as many people as possible with the love of God and message of grace and faith. He doesn’t measure the success of the ministry by the number of tapes distributed, books sold or offerings received. The real rewards, and proof that God is alive and working in people’s lives, are the many testimonies he receives from the people impacted by his teachings. To find out more, please visit our website at: http://www.awmi.net http://www.awmi.net/ www.awmi.net</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260615133000 +0000" stop="20260615140000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Rick Renner</title>
    <desc>Rick Renner is widely known for his interpretation of the Greek New Testament and his engaging teaching style. His teaching is punctuated by a unique ability to draw vividly descriptive word pictures from the Greek that illuminate the Scriptures in a fresh, new way. Rick also distinctively shares Bible principles through contemporary illustrations set against an extensive cultural and historical backdrop of New Testament times. In each episode of “Rick Renner,” Rick teaches in-depth on a passage of Scripture verse by verse, centered around a specific theme that is vitally relevant to the lives of believers who are hungry to dig deeper into the treasures of God’s Word. For more information, visit http://www.renner.org.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260615140000 +0000" stop="20260615143000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Run The Streets with Debra George</title>
    <desc>Debra takes you to the darkest streets of America to win souls.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260615143000 +0000" stop="20260615150000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The James Epperly Show</title>
    <desc>"The James Epperly Show" is a Christian television program that aims to inspire and uplift viewers through faith-based content. Hosted by Pastor James Epperly, the show features insightful sermons, engaging interviews with prominent Christian figures, and heartfelt testimonials from individuals who have experienced life-changing transformations through faith. Each episode is designed to offer spiritual guidance, biblical wisdom, and practical advice for living a Christ-centered life. With its friendly and welcoming vibe, 'The James Epperly Show' aims to support viewers' spiritual development and enhance their connection with God, making it a treasured part of their weekly viewing schedule.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260615150000 +0000" stop="20260615153000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Manna-fest with Perry Stone</title>
    <desc>Manna-fest is the weekly television program of Perry Stone that deals with in-depth prophetic and practical studies of the Word of God. As biblical prophecy continues to unfold, you will find Manna-fest to be a resource to help you better understand where we are now in light of Bible prophecy and what the Bible says about the future. Be sure to tune in each week!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260615153000 +0000" stop="20260615160000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Joyce Meyer: Enjoying Everyday Life</title>
    <desc>Joyce Meyer, one of the world’s leading practicalBible teachers and New York Times bestselling author, shares encouragement andadvice to help people enjoy daily life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260615160000 +0000" stop="20260615163000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The James Epperly Show</title>
    <desc>"The James Epperly Show" is a Christian television program that aims to inspire and uplift viewers through faith-based content. Hosted by Pastor James Epperly, the show features insightful sermons, engaging interviews with prominent Christian figures, and heartfelt testimonials from individuals who have experienced life-changing transformations through faith. Each episode is designed to offer spiritual guidance, biblical wisdom, and practical advice for living a Christ-centered life. With its friendly and welcoming vibe, 'The James Epperly Show' aims to support viewers' spiritual development and enhance their connection with God, making it a treasured part of their weekly viewing schedule.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260615163000 +0000" stop="20260615170000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The Jim Bakker Show</title>
    <desc>The Jim Bakker Show is an hour-long daily Christian broadcast that is aired throughout the United States, Canada, and the entire world through multiple broadcasts on Pioneer Network, Directv, Dish Network and other world wide satellites, and the PTL Television Network. Join Jim and Lori as they bring to the stage today’s greatest prophets, health experts, and leaders of the Christian world to discuss and understand Biblical prophecy and the Revelations of Gods Word.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260615170000 +0000" stop="20260615173000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The Mondo Show</title>
    <desc>The Mondo Show is real, it’s raw, with an organicfeel to the conversation. Sometimes I will be talking directly to you theaudience, and at other times I will place you in the middle of theconversation, so you can experience what is really being said. The subject matter for the conversation and thequestions will be the things people are afraid to ask, even though it is whateveryone is thinking. I want you to meet the men and women who are making adifference in our communities, in our culture, and in our lives. It’s a journeyto understand the misunderstood. It’s The Mondo Show.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260615173000 +0000" stop="20260615180000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>VFI News</title>
    <desc>VFI News with Barry Segal brings you timely, insightful reports on Israel, the Middle East, andglobal events - analysed through a biblical and prophetic lens.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260615180000 +0000" stop="20260615183000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Jentezen Franklin</title>
    <desc>Jentezen Franklin is the Senior Pastor of Free Chapel, a multi-campus church. Each week his television program, Kingdom Connection, is broadcast on major networks all over the world. A New York Times best-selling author, Jentezen has written ten books including his most recent Acres of Diamonds, Love Like You’ve Never Been Hurt, the ground-breaking Fasting and Right People-Right Place-Right Plan.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260615183000 +0000" stop="20260615190000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Christian Music Countdown</title>
    <desc>CMC is a TV showfeaturing contemporary Christian music videos. Each week we count down topmusic videos hand picked from our special guests.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260615190000 +0000" stop="20260615193000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Victory With Paul Daugherty</title>
    <desc>Pastor Paul Daugherty and his wife Ashley lead a new generation with a practical, life-transforming message; a message of love, hope, healing and forgiveness.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260615193000 +0000" stop="20260615200000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Paula Today with Paula White-Cain</title>
    <desc>Paula Today Paula White-Cain along with her husband, Jonathan Cain discuss real life situations and offer practical, Biblical solutions. Down-to-earth, refreshing, sometimes unfiltered and always sharing the life-changing love of Jesus thru Paula’s in-depth teaching or Jon’s anointed music. About Paula Paula White-Cain is the President of Paula White Ministries and City of Destiny headquartered in Apopka, Florida, and the spiritual advisor to President Donald Trump. She hosts Paula Today, a nationally syndicated daily broadcast reaching a potential audience of 5.7 billion people in over 200 countries. She is a leading Pastor, a renowned life coach, bestselling author, and highly sought-after motivational speaker. Paula’s commitment to humanity is felt worldwide as she reaches out through numerous charities and compassion ministries, fulfilling her mission and call to transform lives, heal hearts and win souls. She lives in the Orlando area with her husband, Jonathan Cain.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260615200000 +0000" stop="20260615203000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Focus On The Family</title>
    <desc>Become a champion for your family in the time it takes to enjoy a cup of coffee! Every episode of the Focus on the Family Christian podcast helps you confidently guide your loved ones through the unique challenges faced by today’s Christian families. With over 40 years of trusted, compassionate stories of redemption, hosts Jim Daly and John Fuller connect you to biblically sound marriage and parenting help that is relatable, practical, and interesting. Listen/Learn/Apply/ThriveInChrist!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260615203000 +0000" stop="20260615210000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Life In Christ With Pastor Joe Spence</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260615210000 +0000" stop="20260615213000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Joyce Meyer: Enjoying Everyday Life</title>
    <desc>Joyce Meyer, one of the world’s leading practical Bible teachers and NewYork Times bestselling author, shares encouragement and advice to help peopleenjoy daily life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260615220000 +0000" stop="20260615223000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The Counter Culture Mom Show</title>
    <desc>Former Hollywood actress, pop culture expert, Tina Griffin, left her Wisconsin dairy farm at the age of 20 and headed to Hollywood, CA to earn a BA in Film and Television broadcasting from California State University - Los Angeles. She’s traveled globally for the past 20 years delivering her eye-opening show, Hollywood Exposed https://counterculturemom.com/adult-session/ , explaining the real agenda behind the entertainment industry and its impact on the foundational development of today’s youth. Besides being in countless movies, Tina has worked on TV shows such as Jimmy Kimmel Live!, Young and the Restless, Days of Our Lives, Lizzie McGuire, Drake and Josh, and Malcolm in the Middle, competed in the Miss America pageant and worked at the OSCARS. She was involved with the Film Society as well as Women in Film and an active member of the Screen Actors Guild (SAG) and the American Federation of Television and Radio Artists (AFTRA). She has opened for bands such as Colton Dixon, Third Day, and Jeremy Camp. As host of The Counter Culture Mom Show, Tina gives the latest pop culture news and features experts covering critical topics such as cutting, suicide, bullying, online chat room d</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260615223000 +0000" stop="20260615230000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Believer’s Voice of Victory</title>
    <desc>KCMis committed to keeping the Word of God before your eyes—teaching you how tolive victoriously—so that you are rooted and grounded enough to overcome yourown adversity, reach out to others and share those same principles. We endeavorto bring believers from the milk to the meat of the Word, and into fullmaturity in their walk with God. Oneword from God has transformed the lives of thousands who dared to hear andbelieve. And one word from God will do the same for you.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260615230000 +0000" stop="20260615233000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Manna Fest With Perry Stone</title>
    <desc>Manna-fest is the weekly television program of Perry Stone that deals with in-depth prophetic and practical studies of the Word of God. As biblical prophecy continues to unfold, you will find Manna-fest to be a resource to help you better understand where we are now in light of Bible prophecy and what the Bible says about the future. Be sure to tune in each week!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260615233000 +0000" stop="20260616000000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Desire Of All Nations</title>
    <desc>Nathan Morris of Shake The Nations is a British evangelist who is well know for the Bay of the Holy Spirit Revival. He is known for his passionate messages on the Blood of Jesus and the Cross.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260616000000 +0000" stop="20260616010000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>FlashPoint</title>
    <desc>Live program that addresses current events and issues facing America and the world. Often tackling topics that mainstream media does not, it delivers news and commentary under the anointing—encouraging evidence that God is indeed working to bring about His plans and purposes during these turbulent times. Hosted by Gene Bailey and joined by leaders in government, business, politics and the Church. FlashPoint’s rapidly become a trusted source of truth and hope. Wednesdays and Fridays at 8 p.m. ET/7 p.m. CT.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260616010000 +0000" stop="20260616013000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Paula Today with Paula White-Cain</title>
    <desc>Paula White-Cain along with her husband, Jonathan Cain discuss real life situations and offer practical, Biblical solutions. Down-to-earth, refreshing, sometimes unfiltered and always sharing the life-changing love of Jesus thru Paula’s in-depth teaching or Jon’s anointed music. About Paula Paula White-Cain is the President of Paula White Ministries and City of Destiny headquartered in Apopka, Florida, and the spiritual advisor to President Donald Trump. She hosts Paula Today, a nationally syndicated daily broadcast reaching a potential audience of 5.7 billion people in over 200 countries. She is a leading Pastor, a renowned life coach, bestselling author, and highly sought-after motivational speaker. Paula’s commitment to humanity is felt worldwide as she reaches out through numerous charities and compassion ministries, fulfilling her mission and call to transform lives, heal hearts and win souls. She lives in the Orlando area with her husband, Jonathan Cain.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260616013000 +0000" stop="20260616020000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The James Epperly Show</title>
    <desc>"The James Epperly Show" is a Christian television program that aims to inspire and uplift viewers through faith-based content. Hosted by Pastor James Epperly, the show features insightful sermons, engaging interviews with prominent Christian figures, and heartfelt testimonials from individuals who have experienced life-changing transformations through faith. Each episode is designed to offer spiritual guidance, biblical wisdom, and practical advice for living a Christ-centered life. With its friendly and welcoming vibe, 'The James Epperly Show' aims to support viewers' spiritual development and enhance their connection with God, making it a treasured part of their weekly viewing schedule.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260616020000 +0000" stop="20260616030000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Brian &amp; Bobbie Houston - JesusFollowers.TV</title>
    <desc>"What greater honour and testimony is there than to be a devotedand passionate follower of the Lord Jesus Christ. Bobbie and I believe in the Church, thelocal church and the power and blessing of being planted (Psalm 92). We alsobelieve that in this day and age, God is creating multiple ways to water theseeds and greatness of calling within. Jesusfollowers.TV is here towelcome and extend our table of life and experience to you. This onlineplatform is here to love, encourage, and be a trustworthy voice of hope andinspiration in the days ahead. Our heart is to serve the God-given potentialwithin you and the Body of Christ. As Eph 2:21-22 says, we are all beingbuilt into a holy habitation for the Living God - brick by brick, stone bystone, with Jesus Christ as the Chief Cornerstone. May Jesusfollowers.TV be ablessing to you and those you care for” Brian and Bobbie Houston</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260616030000 +0000" stop="20260616033000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The Jim Bakker Show</title>
    <desc>The Jim Bakker Show is an hour-long daily Christian broadcast that is aired throughout the United States, Canada, and the entire world through multiple broadcasts on Pioneer Network, Directv, Dish Network and other world wide satellites, and the PTL Television Network. Join Jim and Lori as they bring to the stage today’s greatest prophets, health experts, and leaders of the Christian world to discuss and understand Biblical prophecy and the Revelations of Gods Word.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260616033000 +0000" stop="20260616040000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The James Epperly Show</title>
    <desc>"The James Epperly Show" is a Christian television program that aims to inspire and uplift viewers through faith-based content. Hosted by Pastor James Epperly, the show features insightful sermons, engaging interviews with prominent Christian figures, and heartfelt testimonials from individuals who have experienced life-changing transformations through faith. Each episode is designed to offer spiritual guidance, biblical wisdom, and practical advice for living a Christ-centered life. With its friendly and welcoming vibe, 'The James Epperly Show' aims to support viewers' spiritual development and enhance their connection with God, making it a treasured part of their weekly viewing schedule.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260616040000 +0000" stop="20260616060000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Raise The Standard Conference with Rod Parsley</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260616060000 +0000" stop="20260616063000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The Place For Miracles</title>
    <desc>The Place forMiracles is a half-hour broadcast hosted by Richard and Lindsay Roberts. Theprogram focuses on the power of prayer and biblical teaching by Richard andLindsay, plus occasional videos featuring classic sermons from Oral Roberts,praise and worship music, “Living Proof” miracle testimonies, including livecalls and video presentations, and frequent, special guest appearances.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260616063000 +0000" stop="20260616070000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Kingdom Connection with Jentezen Franklin</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260616070000 +0000" stop="20260616073000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Desire Of All Nations</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260616073000 +0000" stop="20260616080000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Samuel Rodriguez</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260616080000 +0000" stop="20260616083000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The Jim Bakker Show</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260616083000 +0000" stop="20260616090000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Believer’s Voice of Victory</title>
    <desc>KCMis committed to keeping the Word of God before your eyes—teaching you how tolive victoriously—so that you are rooted and grounded enough to overcome yourown adversity, reach out to others and share those same principles. We endeavorto bring believers from the milk to the meat of the Word, and into fullmaturity in their walk with God. Oneword from God has transformed the lives of thousands who dared to hear andbelieve. And one word from God will do the same for you.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260616090000 +0000" stop="20260616093000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Paula Today with Paula Whie-Cain</title>
    <desc>Paula White-Cain along with her husband, Jonathan Cain discuss real life situations and offer practical, Biblical solutions. Down-to-earth, refreshing, sometimes unfiltered and always sharing the life-changing love of Jesus thru Paula’s in-depth teaching or Jon’s anointed music.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260616093000 +0000" stop="20260616100000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Christian Music Countdown</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260616100000 +0000" stop="20260616103000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Glory Road with Dr. Candice Smithyman</title>
    <desc>The Glory Road TV show help you connect with heaven and the glory of the Lord to activate the spiritual gifts, purpose and destiny in your life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260616103000 +0000" stop="20260616110000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Believer's Voice of Victory</title>
    <desc>KCM is committed to keeping the Word of God before your eyes—teaching you how to live victoriously—so that you are rooted and grounded enough to overcome your own adversity, reach out to others and share those same principles. We endeavor to bring believers from the milk to the meat of the Word, and into full maturity in their walk with God.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260616110000 +0000" stop="20260616113000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Today with Marilyn &amp; Sarah</title>
    <desc>Marilyn&amp; Sarah Ministries is a global, miracle ministry responding to God's callto cover the earth with the Word and connect every one with the heart of God.For nearly 50 years they have empowered ordinary people to tap into thelife-changing power of the gospel through prayer, Bible teaching, humanitarianand evangelistic outreaches, healing meetings, and their daily TV program,Today with Marilyn &amp; Sarah.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260616113000 +0000" stop="20260616120000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Joyce Meyer: Enjoying Everyday Life</title>
    <desc>Joyce Meyer, one of the world’s leading practicalBible teachers and New York Times bestselling author, shares encouragement andadvice to help people enjoy daily life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260616120000 +0000" stop="20260616123000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Good Morning LIVE</title>
    <desc>Good Morning LIVE is an engaging 30-minute program designed to inspire, inform, and connect viewers to the heart of meaningful living. Hosted by James Epperly, this dynamic show brings together a unique blend of inspirational devotions, thought-provoking interviews, and discussions on current events that matter most to you. Each episode offers uplifting messages to start your day on a positive note, insightful conversations with special guests, and a closer look at how current events align with faith and personal growth. Whether you're seeking encouragement, knowledge, or a deeper connection to today's world, Good Morning LIVE is your source for faith-filled and relevant content. Join us weekday mornings to experience a fresh perspective, inspired by truth and guided by hope.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260616123000 +0000" stop="20260616130000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Faith &amp; Law</title>
    <desc>Faith &amp; Law is a 30 minute variety program that focuses on the intersection of faith and law.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260616130000 +0000" stop="20260616133000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Gospel Truth with Andrew Wommack</title>
    <desc>God called Andrew over 50 years ago toteach the truth of the gospel to the body of Christ with a special emphasis onHis unconditional love and the balance between grace and faith. To fulfil thatcall, Andrew teaches at conferences, in churches, on television, throughpodcasts, and by training people from all walks of life globally at CharisBible College.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260616130000 +0000" stop="20260616133000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Gospel Truth with Andrew Wommack</title>
    <desc>Thirty-two years ago a man had an encounter with God that changed his life forever. Today, he shares that experience with thousands of people all over the world. The goal of Andrew Wommack is to reach as many people as possible with the love of God and message of grace and faith. He doesn’t measure the success of the ministry by the number of tapes distributed, books sold or offerings received. The real rewards, and proof that God is alive and working in people’s lives, are the many testimonies he receives from the people impacted by his teachings. To find out more, please visit our website at: http://www.awmi.net http://www.awmi.net/ www.awmi.net</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260616133000 +0000" stop="20260616140000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Rick Renner</title>
    <desc>Rick Renner is widely known for his interpretation of the Greek New Testament and his engaging teaching style. His teaching is punctuated by a unique ability to draw vividly descriptive word pictures from the Greek that illuminate the Scriptures in a fresh, new way. Rick also distinctively shares Bible principles through contemporary illustrations set against an extensive cultural and historical backdrop of New Testament times. In each episode of “Rick Renner,” Rick teaches in-depth on a passage of Scripture verse by verse, centered around a specific theme that is vitally relevant to the lives of believers who are hungry to dig deeper into the treasures of God’s Word. For more information, visit http://www.renner.org.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260616140000 +0000" stop="20260616143000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Concepts Of Faith with Charles Capps</title>
    <desc>ArkansasFarmer, Charles Capps and family discovered that the spiritual truths Jesustaught could be applied to the everyday circumstances of life and change it!The practical teaching of how to do that is needed and relevant for everyonetoday. Charles, wife Peggy and daughter Annette share life changing truths.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260616143000 +0000" stop="20260616153000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Brian &amp; Bobbie Houston - JesusFollowers.TV</title>
    <desc>"What greater honour and testimony is there than to be a devotedand passionate follower of the Lord Jesus Christ. Bobbie and I believe in the Church, thelocal church and the power and blessing of being planted (Psalm 92). We alsobelieve that in this day and age, God is creating multiple ways to water theseeds and greatness of calling within. Jesusfollowers.TV is here towelcome and extend our table of life and experience to you. This onlineplatform is here to love, encourage, and be a trustworthy voice of hope andinspiration in the days ahead. Our heart is to serve the God-given potentialwithin you and the Body of Christ. As Eph 2:21-22 says, we are all beingbuilt into a holy habitation for the Living God - brick by brick, stone bystone, with Jesus Christ as the Chief Cornerstone. May Jesusfollowers.TV be ablessing to you and those you care for” Brian and Bobbie Houston</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260616153000 +0000" stop="20260616160000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Joyce Meyer: Enjoying Everyday Life</title>
    <desc>Joyce Meyer, one of the world’s leading practicalBible teachers and New York Times bestselling author, shares encouragement andadvice to help people enjoy daily life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260616160000 +0000" stop="20260616163000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The James Epperly Show</title>
    <desc>"The James Epperly Show" is a Christian television program that aims to inspire and uplift viewers through faith-based content. Hosted by Pastor James Epperly, the show features insightful sermons, engaging interviews with prominent Christian figures, and heartfelt testimonials from individuals who have experienced life-changing transformations through faith. Each episode is designed to offer spiritual guidance, biblical wisdom, and practical advice for living a Christ-centered life. With its friendly and welcoming vibe, 'The James Epperly Show' aims to support viewers' spiritual development and enhance their connection with God, making it a treasured part of their weekly viewing schedule.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260616163000 +0000" stop="20260616170000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The Jim Bakker Show</title>
    <desc>The Jim Bakker Show is an hour-long daily Christian broadcast that is aired throughout the United States, Canada, and the entire world through multiple broadcasts on Pioneer Network, Directv, Dish Network and other world wide satellites, and the PTL Television Network. Join Jim and Lori as they bring to the stage today’s greatest prophets, health experts, and leaders of the Christian world to discuss and understand Biblical prophecy and the Revelations of Gods Word.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260616170000 +0000" stop="20260616173000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Kyle Winkler</title>
    <desc>Kyle Winkler is a practical Bible teacher, author of Silence Satan and Activating the Power of God’s Word, and creator of the popular Shut Up, Devil! app. Through his teachings, Kyle is known for using his own story to boast in the power of God’s Word for victorious living.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260616173000 +0000" stop="20260616180000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Samuel Rodriguez</title>
    <desc>New Season with Pastor Sam will usher in a "New Season" where individuals and families will no longer live in failure or merely survive but they will thrive for the glory of Jesus.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260616180000 +0000" stop="20260616183000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Jentezen Franklin</title>
    <desc>Jentezen Franklin is the Senior Pastor of Free Chapel, a multi-campus church. Each week his television program, Kingdom Connection, is broadcast on major networks all over the world. A New York Times best-selling author, Jentezen has written ten books including his most recent Acres of Diamonds, Love Like You’ve Never Been Hurt, the ground-breaking Fasting and Right People-Right Place-Right Plan.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260616183000 +0000" stop="20260616190000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Christian Music Countdown</title>
    <desc>CMC is a TV showfeaturing contemporary Christian music videos. Each week we count down topmusic videos hand picked from our special guests.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260616190000 +0000" stop="20260616193000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Concepts Of Faith with Charles Capps</title>
    <desc>ArkansasFarmer, Charles Capps and family discovered that the spiritual truths Jesustaught could be applied to the everyday circumstances of life and change it!The practical teaching of how to do that is needed and relevant for everyonetoday. Charles, wife Peggy and daughter Annette share life changing truths.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260616193000 +0000" stop="20260616200000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Paula Today with Paula White-Cain</title>
    <desc>Paula Today Paula White-Cain along with her husband, Jonathan Cain discuss real life situations and offer practical, Biblical solutions. Down-to-earth, refreshing, sometimes unfiltered and always sharing the life-changing love of Jesus thru Paula’s in-depth teaching or Jon’s anointed music. About Paula Paula White-Cain is the President of Paula White Ministries and City of Destiny headquartered in Apopka, Florida, and the spiritual advisor to President Donald Trump. She hosts Paula Today, a nationally syndicated daily broadcast reaching a potential audience of 5.7 billion people in over 200 countries. She is a leading Pastor, a renowned life coach, bestselling author, and highly sought-after motivational speaker. Paula’s commitment to humanity is felt worldwide as she reaches out through numerous charities and compassion ministries, fulfilling her mission and call to transform lives, heal hearts and win souls. She lives in the Orlando area with her husband, Jonathan Cain.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260616200000 +0000" stop="20260616203000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Manna Fest with Perry Stone</title>
    <desc>Manna-fest is the weekly television program of Perry Stone that deals with in-depth prophetic and practical studies of the Word of God. As biblical prophecy continues to unfold, you will find Manna-fest to be a resource to help you better understand where we are now in light of Bible prophecy and what the Bible says about the future. Be sure to tune in each week!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260616203000 +0000" stop="20260616210000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The James Epperly Show</title>
    <desc>"The James Epperly Show" is a Christian television program that aims to inspire and uplift viewers through faith-based content. Hosted by Pastor James Epperly, the show features insightful sermons, engaging interviews with prominent Christian figures, and heartfelt testimonials from individuals who have experienced life-changing transformations through faith. Each episode is designed to offer spiritual guidance, biblical wisdom, and practical advice for living a Christ-centered life. With its friendly and welcoming vibe, 'The James Epperly Show' aims to support viewers' spiritual development and enhance their connection with God, making it a treasured part of their weekly viewing schedule.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260616210000 +0000" stop="20260616213000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Joyce Meyer: Enjoying Everyday Life</title>
    <desc>Joyce Meyer, one of the world’s leading practical Bible teachers and NewYork Times bestselling author, shares encouragement and advice to help peopleenjoy daily life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260616213000 +0000" stop="20260616220000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Jentezen Franklin</title>
    <desc>Jentezen Franklin is the Senior Pastor of Free Chapel, a multi-campus church. Each week his television program, Kingdom Connection, is broadcast on major networks all over the world. A New York Times best-selling author, Jentezen has written ten books including his most recent Acres of Diamonds, Love Like You’ve Never Been Hurt, the ground-breaking Fasting and Right People-Right Place-Right Plan.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260616220000 +0000" stop="20260616223000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The Counter Culture Mom Show</title>
    <desc>Former Hollywood actress, pop culture expert, Tina Griffin, left her Wisconsin dairy farm at the age of 20 and headed to Hollywood, CA to earn a BA in Film and Television broadcasting from California State University - Los Angeles. She’s traveled globally for the past 20 years delivering her eye-opening show, Hollywood Exposed https://counterculturemom.com/adult-session/ , explaining the real agenda behind the entertainment industry and its impact on the foundational development of today’s youth. Besides being in countless movies, Tina has worked on TV shows such as Jimmy Kimmel Live!, Young and the Restless, Days of Our Lives, Lizzie McGuire, Drake and Josh, and Malcolm in the Middle, competed in the Miss America pageant and worked at the OSCARS. She was involved with the Film Society as well as Women in Film and an active member of the Screen Actors Guild (SAG) and the American Federation of Television and Radio Artists (AFTRA). She has opened for bands such as Colton Dixon, Third Day, and Jeremy Camp. As host of The Counter Culture Mom Show, Tina gives the latest pop culture news and features experts covering critical topics such as cutting, suicide, bullying, online chat room d</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260616223000 +0000" stop="20260616230000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Believer’s Voice of Victory</title>
    <desc>KCMis committed to keeping the Word of God before your eyes—teaching you how tolive victoriously—so that you are rooted and grounded enough to overcome yourown adversity, reach out to others and share those same principles. We endeavorto bring believers from the milk to the meat of the Word, and into fullmaturity in their walk with God. Oneword from God has transformed the lives of thousands who dared to hear andbelieve. And one word from God will do the same for you.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260616230000 +0000" stop="20260616233000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>God's View</title>
    <desc>Join us around the table as the Holy Spirit moves powerfully touchinglives with signs, wonders, and miracles, healings, salvations, baptisms in theHoly Spirit, etc. as the prayer lines are a reminder weekly of what God isdoing in the lives of the viewers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260616233000 +0000" stop="20260617000000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Samuel Rodriguez</title>
    <desc>New Season with Pastor Sam will usher in a "New Season" where individuals and families will no longer live in failure or merely survive but they will thrive for the glory of Jesus.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260617000000 +0000" stop="20260617010000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>FlashPoint</title>
    <desc>Live program that addresses current events and issues facing America and the world. Often tackling topics that mainstream media does not, it delivers news and commentary under the anointing—encouraging evidence that God is indeed working to bring about His plans and purposes during these turbulent times. Hosted by Gene Bailey and joined by leaders in government, business, politics and the Church. FlashPoint’s rapidly become a trusted source of truth and hope. Wednesdays and Fridays at 8 p.m. ET/7 p.m. CT.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260617010000 +0000" stop="20260617013000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Paula Today with Paula White-Cain</title>
    <desc>Paula White-Cain along with her husband, Jonathan Cain discuss real life situations and offer practical, Biblical solutions. Down-to-earth, refreshing, sometimes unfiltered and always sharing the life-changing love of Jesus thru Paula’s in-depth teaching or Jon’s anointed music. About Paula Paula White-Cain is the President of Paula White Ministries and City of Destiny headquartered in Apopka, Florida, and the spiritual advisor to President Donald Trump. She hosts Paula Today, a nationally syndicated daily broadcast reaching a potential audience of 5.7 billion people in over 200 countries. She is a leading Pastor, a renowned life coach, bestselling author, and highly sought-after motivational speaker. Paula’s commitment to humanity is felt worldwide as she reaches out through numerous charities and compassion ministries, fulfilling her mission and call to transform lives, heal hearts and win souls. She lives in the Orlando area with her husband, Jonathan Cain.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260617013000 +0000" stop="20260617020000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The James Epperly Show</title>
    <desc>"The James Epperly Show" is a Christian television program that aims to inspire and uplift viewers through faith-based content. Hosted by Pastor James Epperly, the show features insightful sermons, engaging interviews with prominent Christian figures, and heartfelt testimonials from individuals who have experienced life-changing transformations through faith. Each episode is designed to offer spiritual guidance, biblical wisdom, and practical advice for living a Christ-centered life. With its friendly and welcoming vibe, 'The James Epperly Show' aims to support viewers' spiritual development and enhance their connection with God, making it a treasured part of their weekly viewing schedule.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260617020000 +0000" stop="20260617023000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The Place For Miracles with Richard &amp; Lindsay Roberts</title>
    <desc>This show, hosted by Richard and Lindsay Roberts, features prayer, miracle testimonies, teaching from the Bible, and praise and worship.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260617023000 +0000" stop="20260617030000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Manna-Fest with Perry Stone</title>
    <desc>Manna-fest is the weekly television program of Perry Stone that deals with in-depth prophetic and practical studies of the Word of God. As biblical prophecy continues to unfold, you will find Manna-fest to be a resource to help you better understand where we are now in light of Bible prophecy and what the Bible says about the future. Be sure to tune in each week!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260617030000 +0000" stop="20260617033000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The Jim Bakker Show</title>
    <desc>The Jim Bakker Show is an hour-long daily Christian broadcast that is aired throughout the United States, Canada, and the entire world through multiple broadcasts on Pioneer Network, Directv, Dish Network and other world wide satellites, and the PTL Television Network. Join Jim and Lori as they bring to the stage today’s greatest prophets, health experts, and leaders of the Christian world to discuss and understand Biblical prophecy and the Revelations of Gods Word.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260617033000 +0000" stop="20260617040000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The James Epperly Show</title>
    <desc>"The James Epperly Show" is a Christian television program that aims to inspire and uplift viewers through faith-based content. Hosted by Pastor James Epperly, the show features insightful sermons, engaging interviews with prominent Christian figures, and heartfelt testimonials from individuals who have experienced life-changing transformations through faith. Each episode is designed to offer spiritual guidance, biblical wisdom, and practical advice for living a Christ-centered life. With its friendly and welcoming vibe, 'The James Epperly Show' aims to support viewers' spiritual development and enhance their connection with God, making it a treasured part of their weekly viewing schedule.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260617040000 +0000" stop="20260617060000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Be Made Whole Worldwide Prayer Cloth Service with Rod Parsley</title>
    <desc>Experience the powerful anointing of our Be Made Whole Worldwide Prayer Cloth Service featuring Harvest Music Live and our outstanding choir. The miracle-working power of God changed multiplied hundreds of thousands, and now you can reserve your anointed prayer cloth from this year’s altar. The tangible transferrable anointing can heal your body, produce deliverance, family restoration, financial breakthrough, whatever you need!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260617060000 +0000" stop="20260617063000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The Place For Miracles</title>
    <desc>The Place forMiracles is a half-hour broadcast hosted by Richard and Lindsay Roberts. Theprogram focuses on the power of prayer and biblical teaching by Richard andLindsay, plus occasional videos featuring classic sermons from Oral Roberts,praise and worship music, “Living Proof” miracle testimonies, including livecalls and video presentations, and frequent, special guest appearances.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260617063000 +0000" stop="20260617070000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Kingdom Connection with Jentezen Franklin</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260617070000 +0000" stop="20260617073000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Desire Of All Nations</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260617073000 +0000" stop="20260617080000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Samuel Rodriguez</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260617080000 +0000" stop="20260617083000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The Jim Bakker Show</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260617083000 +0000" stop="20260617090000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Believer’s Voice of Victory</title>
    <desc>KCMis committed to keeping the Word of God before your eyes—teaching you how tolive victoriously—so that you are rooted and grounded enough to overcome yourown adversity, reach out to others and share those same principles. We endeavorto bring believers from the milk to the meat of the Word, and into fullmaturity in their walk with God. Oneword from God has transformed the lives of thousands who dared to hear andbelieve. And one word from God will do the same for you.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260617090000 +0000" stop="20260617093000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Paula Today with Paula Whie-Cain</title>
    <desc>Paula White-Cain along with her husband, Jonathan Cain discuss real life situations and offer practical, Biblical solutions. Down-to-earth, refreshing, sometimes unfiltered and always sharing the life-changing love of Jesus thru Paula’s in-depth teaching or Jon’s anointed music.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260617093000 +0000" stop="20260617100000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Christian Music Countdown</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260617100000 +0000" stop="20260617103000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Make Your Day Count with Lindsay Roberts</title>
    <desc>Lindsay Roberts hosts an uplifting program geared especially toward encouraging and equipping women through Bible-based teaching and testimonies.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260617103000 +0000" stop="20260617110000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Believer's Voice of Victory</title>
    <desc>KCM is committed to keeping the Word of God before your eyes—teaching you how to live victoriously—so that you are rooted and grounded enough to overcome your own adversity, reach out to others and share those same principles. We endeavor to bring believers from the milk to the meat of the Word, and into full maturity in their walk with God.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260617110000 +0000" stop="20260617113000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Today with Marilyn &amp; Sarah</title>
    <desc>Marilyn&amp; Sarah Ministries is a global, miracle ministry responding to God's callto cover the earth with the Word and connect every one with the heart of God.For nearly 50 years they have empowered ordinary people to tap into thelife-changing power of the gospel through prayer, Bible teaching, humanitarianand evangelistic outreaches, healing meetings, and their daily TV program,Today with Marilyn &amp; Sarah.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260617113000 +0000" stop="20260617120000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Joyce Meyer: Enjoying Everyday Life</title>
    <desc>Joyce Meyer, one of the world’s leading practicalBible teachers and New York Times bestselling author, shares encouragement andadvice to help people enjoy daily life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260617120000 +0000" stop="20260617123000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Good Morning LIVE</title>
    <desc>Good Morning LIVE is an engaging 30-minute program designed to inspire, inform, and connect viewers to the heart of meaningful living. Hosted by James Epperly, this dynamic show brings together a unique blend of inspirational devotions, thought-provoking interviews, and discussions on current events that matter most to you. Each episode offers uplifting messages to start your day on a positive note, insightful conversations with special guests, and a closer look at how current events align with faith and personal growth. Whether you're seeking encouragement, knowledge, or a deeper connection to today's world, Good Morning LIVE is your source for faith-filled and relevant content. Join us weekday mornings to experience a fresh perspective, inspired by truth and guided by hope.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260617123000 +0000" stop="20260617130000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Worldview Matters</title>
    <desc>David Fiorazo is an author, ordained pastor, truth proclaimer, media contributor, and podcaster. Since the1990’s David has been working in both TV and radio broadcasting and in Christian ministry. On Worldview Matters, Fiorazo and expert guests tackle current events, demonic agendas &amp;movements, and controversial topics including church &amp; state issues, religious freedom, the culture war, Bible prophecy, education, politics, media&amp; more.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260617130000 +0000" stop="20260617133000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Gospel Truth with Andrew Wommack</title>
    <desc>God called Andrew over 50 years ago toteach the truth of the gospel to the body of Christ with a special emphasis onHis unconditional love and the balance between grace and faith. To fulfil thatcall, Andrew teaches at conferences, in churches, on television, throughpodcasts, and by training people from all walks of life globally at CharisBible College.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260617130000 +0000" stop="20260617133000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Gospel Truth with Andrew Wommack</title>
    <desc>Thirty-two years ago a man had an encounter with God that changed his life forever. Today, he shares that experience with thousands of people all over the world. The goal of Andrew Wommack is to reach as many people as possible with the love of God and message of grace and faith. He doesn’t measure the success of the ministry by the number of tapes distributed, books sold or offerings received. The real rewards, and proof that God is alive and working in people’s lives, are the many testimonies he receives from the people impacted by his teachings. To find out more, please visit our website at: http://www.awmi.net http://www.awmi.net/ www.awmi.net</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260617133000 +0000" stop="20260617140000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Rick Renner</title>
    <desc>Rick Renner is widely known for his interpretation of the Greek New Testament and his engaging teaching style. His teaching is punctuated by a unique ability to draw vividly descriptive word pictures from the Greek that illuminate the Scriptures in a fresh, new way. Rick also distinctively shares Bible principles through contemporary illustrations set against an extensive cultural and historical backdrop of New Testament times. In each episode of “Rick Renner,” Rick teaches in-depth on a passage of Scripture verse by verse, centered around a specific theme that is vitally relevant to the lives of believers who are hungry to dig deeper into the treasures of God’s Word. For more information, visit http://www.renner.org.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260617140000 +0000" stop="20260617143000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Manna Fest With Perry Stone</title>
    <desc>Manna-fest is the weekly television program of Perry Stone that deals with in-depth prophetic and practical studies of the Word of God. As biblical prophecy continues to unfold, you will find Manna-fest to be a resource to help you better understand where we are now in light of Bible prophecy and what the Bible says about the future. Be sure to tune in each week!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260617143000 +0000" stop="20260617150000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The James Epperly Show</title>
    <desc>"The James Epperly Show" is a Christian television program that aims to inspire and uplift viewers through faith-based content. Hosted by Pastor James Epperly, the show features insightful sermons, engaging interviews with prominent Christian figures, and heartfelt testimonials from individuals who have experienced life-changing transformations through faith. Each episode is designed to offer spiritual guidance, biblical wisdom, and practical advice for living a Christ-centered life. With its friendly and welcoming vibe, 'The James Epperly Show' aims to support viewers' spiritual development and enhance their connection with God, making it a treasured part of their weekly viewing schedule.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260617150000 +0000" stop="20260617153000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Concepts of Faith</title>
    <desc>Arkansas farmer, Charles Capps and family discovered that the spiritual truths Jesustaught could be applied to the everyday circumstances of life and change it!The practical teaching of how to do that is needed and relevant for everyonetoday. Charles, wife Peggy and daughter Annette share life changing truths.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260617153000 +0000" stop="20260617160000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Joyce Meyer: Enjoying Everyday Life</title>
    <desc>Joyce Meyer, one of the world’s leading practicalBible teachers and New York Times bestselling author, shares encouragement andadvice to help people enjoy daily life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260617160000 +0000" stop="20260617163000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The James Epperly Show</title>
    <desc>"The James Epperly Show" is a Christian television program that aims to inspire and uplift viewers through faith-based content. Hosted by Pastor James Epperly, the show features insightful sermons, engaging interviews with prominent Christian figures, and heartfelt testimonials from individuals who have experienced life-changing transformations through faith. Each episode is designed to offer spiritual guidance, biblical wisdom, and practical advice for living a Christ-centered life. With its friendly and welcoming vibe, 'The James Epperly Show' aims to support viewers' spiritual development and enhance their connection with God, making it a treasured part of their weekly viewing schedule.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260617163000 +0000" stop="20260617170000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The Jim Bakker Show</title>
    <desc>The Jim Bakker Show is an hour-long daily Christian broadcast that is aired throughout the United States, Canada, and the entire world through multiple broadcasts on Pioneer Network, Directv, Dish Network and other world wide satellites, and the PTL Television Network. Join Jim and Lori as they bring to the stage today’s greatest prophets, health experts, and leaders of the Christian world to discuss and understand Biblical prophecy and the Revelations of Gods Word.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260617170000 +0000" stop="20260617173000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>World Impact With Dr. Billy Wilson</title>
    <desc>Each week Voice of Salvation Ministries presents World Impact with Dr. Billy Wilson, canvassing the globe with the gospel. The program’s unique, contemporary format offers a clear evangelistic call to a relationship with Jesus Christ. Twenty episodes are recorded yearly, both in the studio facilities and field locations around the world. For more information: WorldImpact.tv http://worldimpact.tv/</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260617173000 +0000" stop="20260617180000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>VFI News</title>
    <desc>VFI News with Barry Segal brings you timely, insightful reports on Israel, the Middle East, andglobal events - analysed through a biblical and prophetic lens.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260617180000 +0000" stop="20260617190000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Brian &amp; Bobbie Houston - JesusFollowers.TV</title>
    <desc>"What greater honour and testimony is there than to be a devotedand passionate follower of the Lord Jesus Christ. Bobbie and I believe in the Church, thelocal church and the power and blessing of being planted (Psalm 92). We alsobelieve that in this day and age, God is creating multiple ways to water theseeds and greatness of calling within. Jesusfollowers.TV is here towelcome and extend our table of life and experience to you. This onlineplatform is here to love, encourage, and be a trustworthy voice of hope andinspiration in the days ahead. Our heart is to serve the God-given potentialwithin you and the Body of Christ. As Eph 2:21-22 says, we are all beingbuilt into a holy habitation for the Living God - brick by brick, stone bystone, with Jesus Christ as the Chief Cornerstone. May Jesusfollowers.TV be ablessing to you and those you care for” Brian and Bobbie Houston</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260617190000 +0000" stop="20260617193000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Victory With Paul Daugherty</title>
    <desc>Pastor Paul Daugherty and his wife Ashley lead a new generation with a practical, life-transforming message; a message of love, hope, healing and forgiveness.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260617193000 +0000" stop="20260617200000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Paula Today with Paula White-Cain</title>
    <desc>Paula Today Paula White-Cain along with her husband, Jonathan Cain discuss real life situations and offer practical, Biblical solutions. Down-to-earth, refreshing, sometimes unfiltered and always sharing the life-changing love of Jesus thru Paula’s in-depth teaching or Jon’s anointed music. About Paula Paula White-Cain is the President of Paula White Ministries and City of Destiny headquartered in Apopka, Florida, and the spiritual advisor to President Donald Trump. She hosts Paula Today, a nationally syndicated daily broadcast reaching a potential audience of 5.7 billion people in over 200 countries. She is a leading Pastor, a renowned life coach, bestselling author, and highly sought-after motivational speaker. Paula’s commitment to humanity is felt worldwide as she reaches out through numerous charities and compassion ministries, fulfilling her mission and call to transform lives, heal hearts and win souls. She lives in the Orlando area with her husband, Jonathan Cain.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260617200000 +0000" stop="20260617203000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Focus On The Family</title>
    <desc>Become a champion for your family in the time it takes to enjoy a cup of coffee! Every episode of the Focus on the Family Christian podcast helps you confidently guide your loved ones through the unique challenges faced by today’s Christian families. With over 40 years of trusted, compassionate stories of redemption, hosts Jim Daly and John Fuller connect you to biblically sound marriage and parenting help that is relatable, practical, and interesting. Listen/Learn/Apply/ThriveInChrist!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260617203000 +0000" stop="20260617210000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Billy Graham TV</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260617210000 +0000" stop="20260617213000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Joyce Meyer: Enjoying Everyday Life</title>
    <desc>Joyce Meyer, one of the world’s leading practical Bible teachers and NewYork Times bestselling author, shares encouragement and advice to help peopleenjoy daily life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260617213000 +0000" stop="20260617220000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Wisdom Speaks</title>
    <desc>Wisdom Speaks has been a beacon of inspiration and empowerment for four years. Our talk show delves into meaningful discussions on biblical teachings, honoring women, motherhood, and parenting. As a ministry for the marketplace, we strive to provide valuable insights and support, fostering a community centered around faith, salvation, and real-life challenges. We celebrate and uplift voices through engaging and heartfelt conversations.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260617220000 +0000" stop="20260617223000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The Counter Culture Mom Show</title>
    <desc>Former Hollywood actress, pop culture expert, Tina Griffin, left her Wisconsin dairy farm at the age of 20 and headed to Hollywood, CA to earn a BA in Film and Television broadcasting from California State University - Los Angeles. She’s traveled globally for the past 20 years delivering her eye-opening show, Hollywood Exposed https://counterculturemom.com/adult-session/ , explaining the real agenda behind the entertainment industry and its impact on the foundational development of today’s youth. Besides being in countless movies, Tina has worked on TV shows such as Jimmy Kimmel Live!, Young and the Restless, Days of Our Lives, Lizzie McGuire, Drake and Josh, and Malcolm in the Middle, competed in the Miss America pageant and worked at the OSCARS. She was involved with the Film Society as well as Women in Film and an active member of the Screen Actors Guild (SAG) and the American Federation of Television and Radio Artists (AFTRA). She has opened for bands such as Colton Dixon, Third Day, and Jeremy Camp. As host of The Counter Culture Mom Show, Tina gives the latest pop culture news and features experts covering critical topics such as cutting, suicide, bullying, online chat room d</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260617223000 +0000" stop="20260617230000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Believer’s Voice of Victory</title>
    <desc>KCMis committed to keeping the Word of God before your eyes—teaching you how tolive victoriously—so that you are rooted and grounded enough to overcome yourown adversity, reach out to others and share those same principles. We endeavorto bring believers from the milk to the meat of the Word, and into fullmaturity in their walk with God. Oneword from God has transformed the lives of thousands who dared to hear andbelieve. And one word from God will do the same for you.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260617230000 +0000" stop="20260617233000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The Mondo Show</title>
    <desc>I am so excited to introduce to you a new show. I would be honored for you to be a part of this brand new and exciting project! My new show is called “Mondo”. It’s a new TV show coming to the PTL Television Network available on ROKU, Apple TV, and Amazon Fire. This show is real, it’s raw, with an organic feel to the conversation. Sometimes I will be talking directly to you the audience, and at other times I will place you in the middle of the conversation, so you can experience what is really being said. The subject matter for the conversation and the questions will be the things people are afraid to ask, even though it is what everyone is thinking. I want you to meet the men and women who are making a difference in our communities, in our culture, and in our lives. It’s a journey to understand the misunderstood. It’s The Mondo Show.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260617233000 +0000" stop="20260618000000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Billy Graham TV</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260618000000 +0000" stop="20260618010000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>ORU Chapel</title>
    <desc>Ranked as one of the Top 50 “Most DiverseColleges in America” and Oklahoma’s #1 university for diversity (Niche 2023),ORU https://oru.edu/ https://www.youtube.com/redirect?event=video_description&amp;redir_token=QUFFLUhqbllUSTZqTUJzVGRzTU90OV82YVVWc1liNEJrZ3xBQ3Jtc0tramk4WUVQcUNabmM5SGlNQklEX2JJSk9kMVJ5MmNJQWFFLWlfTTBULXY3WnF0T3g2LUtiV3JOaW1mR0o2N20tOS04N0ZqUUlNblRNTWhyWkx5QVVzemQ5VDNqNTUzM1BZc2o1S1hFOHVEZEFtYU1mbw&amp;q=https%3A%2F%2Foru.edu%2F&amp;v=rPj4d3Ei0EU is a multicultural, global campus withmore than 4,500 students representing well over 120 nations. And as a Top 10university for Engagement (Wall Street Journal/Times Higher Ed ranked), ORUworks closely with students to develop whole leaders for the whole worldthrough a unique Whole Person approach to college education. If you’re anon-campus student or if you’re seeking an online education, ORU offersbachelors, masters, and doctoral degrees in a global, Spirit-empoweredenvironment. Explore Oral Roberts University https://oru.edu/ https://oru.edu/</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260618010000 +0000" stop="20260618013000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Paula Today with Paula White-Cain</title>
    <desc>Paula White-Cain along with her husband, Jonathan Cain discuss real life situations and offer practical, Biblical solutions. Down-to-earth, refreshing, sometimes unfiltered and always sharing the life-changing love of Jesus thru Paula’s in-depth teaching or Jon’s anointed music. About Paula Paula White-Cain is the President of Paula White Ministries and City of Destiny headquartered in Apopka, Florida, and the spiritual advisor to President Donald Trump. She hosts Paula Today, a nationally syndicated daily broadcast reaching a potential audience of 5.7 billion people in over 200 countries. She is a leading Pastor, a renowned life coach, bestselling author, and highly sought-after motivational speaker. Paula’s commitment to humanity is felt worldwide as she reaches out through numerous charities and compassion ministries, fulfilling her mission and call to transform lives, heal hearts and win souls. She lives in the Orlando area with her husband, Jonathan Cain.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260618013000 +0000" stop="20260618030000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Valor Christian College Chapel</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260618030000 +0000" stop="20260618040000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Brian &amp; Bobbie Houston - JesusFollowers.TV</title>
    <desc>"What greater honour and testimony is there than to be a devotedand passionate follower of the Lord Jesus Christ. Bobbie and I believe in the Church, thelocal church and the power and blessing of being planted (Psalm 92). We alsobelieve that in this day and age, God is creating multiple ways to water theseeds and greatness of calling within. Jesusfollowers.TV is here towelcome and extend our table of life and experience to you. This onlineplatform is here to love, encourage, and be a trustworthy voice of hope andinspiration in the days ahead. Our heart is to serve the God-given potentialwithin you and the Body of Christ. As Eph 2:21-22 says, we are all beingbuilt into a holy habitation for the Living God - brick by brick, stone bystone, with Jesus Christ as the Chief Cornerstone. May Jesusfollowers.TV be ablessing to you and those you care for” Brian and Bobbie Houston</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260618040000 +0000" stop="20260618060000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Raise The Standard Conference with Rod Parsley</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260618060000 +0000" stop="20260618063000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The Place For Miracles</title>
    <desc>The Place forMiracles is a half-hour broadcast hosted by Richard and Lindsay Roberts. Theprogram focuses on the power of prayer and biblical teaching by Richard andLindsay, plus occasional videos featuring classic sermons from Oral Roberts,praise and worship music, “Living Proof” miracle testimonies, including livecalls and video presentations, and frequent, special guest appearances.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260618063000 +0000" stop="20260618070000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Kingdom Connection with Jentezen Franklin</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260618070000 +0000" stop="20260618073000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Desire Of All Nations</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260618073000 +0000" stop="20260618080000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Samuel Rodriguez</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260618080000 +0000" stop="20260618083000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The Jim Bakker Show</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260618083000 +0000" stop="20260618090000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Believer’s Voice of Victory</title>
    <desc>KCMis committed to keeping the Word of God before your eyes—teaching you how tolive victoriously—so that you are rooted and grounded enough to overcome yourown adversity, reach out to others and share those same principles. We endeavorto bring believers from the milk to the meat of the Word, and into fullmaturity in their walk with God. Oneword from God has transformed the lives of thousands who dared to hear andbelieve. And one word from God will do the same for you.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260618090000 +0000" stop="20260618093000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Paula Today with Paula Whie-Cain</title>
    <desc>Paula White-Cain along with her husband, Jonathan Cain discuss real life situations and offer practical, Biblical solutions. Down-to-earth, refreshing, sometimes unfiltered and always sharing the life-changing love of Jesus thru Paula’s in-depth teaching or Jon’s anointed music.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260618093000 +0000" stop="20260618100000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Christian Music Countdown</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260618100000 +0000" stop="20260618103000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Glory Road with Dr. Candice Smithyman</title>
    <desc>The Glory Road TV show help you connect with heaven and the glory of the Lord to activate the spiritual gifts, purpose and destiny in your life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260618103000 +0000" stop="20260618110000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Believer's Voice of Victory</title>
    <desc>KCM is committed to keeping the Word of God before your eyes—teaching you how to live victoriously—so that you are rooted and grounded enough to overcome your own adversity, reach out to others and share those same principles. We endeavor to bring believers from the milk to the meat of the Word, and into full maturity in their walk with God.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260618110000 +0000" stop="20260618113000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Today with Marilyn &amp; Sarah</title>
    <desc>Marilyn&amp; Sarah Ministries is a global, miracle ministry responding to God's callto cover the earth with the Word and connect every one with the heart of God.For nearly 50 years they have empowered ordinary people to tap into thelife-changing power of the gospel through prayer, Bible teaching, humanitarianand evangelistic outreaches, healing meetings, and their daily TV program,Today with Marilyn &amp; Sarah.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260618113000 +0000" stop="20260618120000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Joyce Meyer: Enjoying Everyday Life</title>
    <desc>Joyce Meyer, one of the world’s leading practicalBible teachers and New York Times bestselling author, shares encouragement andadvice to help people enjoy daily life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260618120000 +0000" stop="20260618123000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Good Morning LIVE</title>
    <desc>Good Morning LIVE is an engaging 30-minute program designed to inspire, inform, and connect viewers to the heart of meaningful living. Hosted by James Epperly, this dynamic show brings together a unique blend of inspirational devotions, thought-provoking interviews, and discussions on current events that matter most to you. Each episode offers uplifting messages to start your day on a positive note, insightful conversations with special guests, and a closer look at how current events align with faith and personal growth. Whether you're seeking encouragement, knowledge, or a deeper connection to today's world, Good Morning LIVE is your source for faith-filled and relevant content. Join us weekday mornings to experience a fresh perspective, inspired by truth and guided by hope.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260618123000 +0000" stop="20260618130000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Jentezen Franklin</title>
    <desc>Jentezen Franklin is the Senior Pastor of Free Chapel, a multi-campus church. Each week his television program, Kingdom Connection, is broadcast on major networks all over the world. A New York Times best-selling author, Jentezen has written ten books including his most recent Acres of Diamonds, Love Like You’ve Never Been Hurt, the ground-breaking Fasting and Right People-Right Place-Right Plan.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260618130000 +0000" stop="20260618133000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Gospel Truth with Andrew Wommack</title>
    <desc>God called Andrew over 50 years ago toteach the truth of the gospel to the body of Christ with a special emphasis onHis unconditional love and the balance between grace and faith. To fulfil thatcall, Andrew teaches at conferences, in churches, on television, throughpodcasts, and by training people from all walks of life globally at CharisBible College.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260618130000 +0000" stop="20260618133000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Gospel Truth with Andrew Wommack</title>
    <desc>Thirty-two years ago a man had an encounter with God that changed his life forever. Today, he shares that experience with thousands of people all over the world. The goal of Andrew Wommack is to reach as many people as possible with the love of God and message of grace and faith. He doesn’t measure the success of the ministry by the number of tapes distributed, books sold or offerings received. The real rewards, and proof that God is alive and working in people’s lives, are the many testimonies he receives from the people impacted by his teachings. To find out more, please visit our website at: http://www.awmi.net http://www.awmi.net/ www.awmi.net</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260618133000 +0000" stop="20260618140000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Rick Renner</title>
    <desc>Rick Renner is widely known for his interpretation of the Greek New Testament and his engaging teaching style. His teaching is punctuated by a unique ability to draw vividly descriptive word pictures from the Greek that illuminate the Scriptures in a fresh, new way. Rick also distinctively shares Bible principles through contemporary illustrations set against an extensive cultural and historical backdrop of New Testament times. In each episode of “Rick Renner,” Rick teaches in-depth on a passage of Scripture verse by verse, centered around a specific theme that is vitally relevant to the lives of believers who are hungry to dig deeper into the treasures of God’s Word. For more information, visit http://www.renner.org.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260618140000 +0000" stop="20260618143000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Sid Roth's It's Supernatural</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260618143000 +0000" stop="20260618150000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The Elena &amp; Natalia Show</title>
    <desc>We're twins, Elena &amp; Natalia Maranian, and are passionate about sharing the love of Jesus through media. Together, we host and produce our talk show, The Elena &amp; Natalia Show in which we have conversations about Jesus, life, and love centered on the beauty and truth of God’s Word. We are also honored to serve at our family's TV network and media ministry, International Christian Family Network, Inc. where we hosted our former talk show, New Generation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260618150000 +0000" stop="20260618153000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The Winners Way with Mac Hammond</title>
    <desc>As our faith, courage, and discipline strengthen, we become vessels through which God can bring blessings to others. Discover more about this transformative journey—and our journey to plant fifty churches in five years—on The Winner's Way with Mac Hammond.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260618153000 +0000" stop="20260618160000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Joyce Meyer: Enjoying Everyday Life</title>
    <desc>Joyce Meyer, one of the world’s leading practicalBible teachers and New York Times bestselling author, shares encouragement andadvice to help people enjoy daily life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260618160000 +0000" stop="20260618163000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The James Epperly Show</title>
    <desc>"The James Epperly Show" is a Christian television program that aims to inspire and uplift viewers through faith-based content. Hosted by Pastor James Epperly, the show features insightful sermons, engaging interviews with prominent Christian figures, and heartfelt testimonials from individuals who have experienced life-changing transformations through faith. Each episode is designed to offer spiritual guidance, biblical wisdom, and practical advice for living a Christ-centered life. With its friendly and welcoming vibe, 'The James Epperly Show' aims to support viewers' spiritual development and enhance their connection with God, making it a treasured part of their weekly viewing schedule.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260618163000 +0000" stop="20260618170000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The Jim Bakker Show</title>
    <desc>The Jim Bakker Show is an hour-long daily Christian broadcast that is aired throughout the United States, Canada, and the entire world through multiple broadcasts on Pioneer Network, Directv, Dish Network and other world wide satellites, and the PTL Television Network. Join Jim and Lori as they bring to the stage today’s greatest prophets, health experts, and leaders of the Christian world to discuss and understand Biblical prophecy and the Revelations of Gods Word.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260618170000 +0000" stop="20260618173000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Kyle Winkler</title>
    <desc>Kyle Winkler is a practical Bible teacher, author of Silence Satan and Activating the Power of God’s Word, and creator of the popular Shut Up, Devil! app. Through his teachings, Kyle is known for using his own story to boast in the power of God’s Word for victorious living.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260618173000 +0000" stop="20260618180000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Samuel Rodriguez</title>
    <desc>New Season with Pastor Sam will usher in a "New Season" where individuals and families will no longer live in failure or merely survive but they will thrive for the glory of Jesus.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260618180000 +0000" stop="20260618183000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The James Epperly Show</title>
    <desc>"The James Epperly Show" is a Christian television program that aims to inspire and uplift viewers through faith-based content. Hosted by Pastor James Epperly, the show features insightful sermons, engaging interviews with prominent Christian figures, and heartfelt testimonials from individuals who have experienced life-changing transformations through faith. Each episode is designed to offer spiritual guidance, biblical wisdom, and practical advice for living a Christ-centered life. With its friendly and welcoming vibe, 'The James Epperly Show' aims to support viewers' spiritual development and enhance their connection with God, making it a treasured part of their weekly viewing schedule.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260618183000 +0000" stop="20260618190000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Christian Music Countdown</title>
    <desc>CMC is a TV showfeaturing contemporary Christian music videos. Each week we count down topmusic videos hand picked from our special guests.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260618190000 +0000" stop="20260618193000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Concepts Of Faith with Charles Capps</title>
    <desc>ArkansasFarmer, Charles Capps and family discovered that the spiritual truths Jesustaught could be applied to the everyday circumstances of life and change it!The practical teaching of how to do that is needed and relevant for everyonetoday. Charles, wife Peggy and daughter Annette share life changing truths.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260618193000 +0000" stop="20260618200000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Paula Today with Paula White-Cain</title>
    <desc>Paula Today Paula White-Cain along with her husband, Jonathan Cain discuss real life situations and offer practical, Biblical solutions. Down-to-earth, refreshing, sometimes unfiltered and always sharing the life-changing love of Jesus thru Paula’s in-depth teaching or Jon’s anointed music. About Paula Paula White-Cain is the President of Paula White Ministries and City of Destiny headquartered in Apopka, Florida, and the spiritual advisor to President Donald Trump. She hosts Paula Today, a nationally syndicated daily broadcast reaching a potential audience of 5.7 billion people in over 200 countries. She is a leading Pastor, a renowned life coach, bestselling author, and highly sought-after motivational speaker. Paula’s commitment to humanity is felt worldwide as she reaches out through numerous charities and compassion ministries, fulfilling her mission and call to transform lives, heal hearts and win souls. She lives in the Orlando area with her husband, Jonathan Cain.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260618200000 +0000" stop="20260618203000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Manna Fest with Perry Stone</title>
    <desc>Manna-fest is the weekly television program of Perry Stone that deals with in-depth prophetic and practical studies of the Word of God. As biblical prophecy continues to unfold, you will find Manna-fest to be a resource to help you better understand where we are now in light of Bible prophecy and what the Bible says about the future. Be sure to tune in each week!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260618203000 +0000" stop="20260618210000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Life In Christ With Pastor Joe Spence</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260618210000 +0000" stop="20260618213000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Joyce Meyer: Enjoying Everyday Life</title>
    <desc>Joyce Meyer, one of the world’s leading practical Bible teachers and NewYork Times bestselling author, shares encouragement and advice to help peopleenjoy daily life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260618220000 +0000" stop="20260618223000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The Counter Culture Mom Show</title>
    <desc>Former Hollywood actress, pop culture expert, Tina Griffin, left her Wisconsin dairy farm at the age of 20 and headed to Hollywood, CA to earn a BA in Film and Television broadcasting from California State University - Los Angeles. She’s traveled globally for the past 20 years delivering her eye-opening show, Hollywood Exposed https://counterculturemom.com/adult-session/ , explaining the real agenda behind the entertainment industry and its impact on the foundational development of today’s youth. Besides being in countless movies, Tina has worked on TV shows such as Jimmy Kimmel Live!, Young and the Restless, Days of Our Lives, Lizzie McGuire, Drake and Josh, and Malcolm in the Middle, competed in the Miss America pageant and worked at the OSCARS. She was involved with the Film Society as well as Women in Film and an active member of the Screen Actors Guild (SAG) and the American Federation of Television and Radio Artists (AFTRA). She has opened for bands such as Colton Dixon, Third Day, and Jeremy Camp. As host of The Counter Culture Mom Show, Tina gives the latest pop culture news and features experts covering critical topics such as cutting, suicide, bullying, online chat room d</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260618223000 +0000" stop="20260618230000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Believer’s Voice of Victory</title>
    <desc>KCMis committed to keeping the Word of God before your eyes—teaching you how tolive victoriously—so that you are rooted and grounded enough to overcome yourown adversity, reach out to others and share those same principles. We endeavorto bring believers from the milk to the meat of the Word, and into fullmaturity in their walk with God. Oneword from God has transformed the lives of thousands who dared to hear andbelieve. And one word from God will do the same for you.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260618230000 +0000" stop="20260618233000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>On The Path with Cheryl Nembhard</title>
    <desc>Join host Cheryl Nembhard On The Path, along with notable guests as theyshare their stories of triumph, tragedy, and the big lessons they've learnedalong their journey of faith.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260618233000 +0000" stop="20260619000000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Samuel Rodriguez</title>
    <desc>New Season with Pastor Sam will usher in a "New Season" where individuals and families will no longer live in failure or merely survive but they will thrive for the glory of Jesus.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260619000000 +0000" stop="20260619010000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>FlashPoint</title>
    <desc>Live program that addresses current events and issues facing America and the world. Often tackling topics that mainstream media does not, it delivers news and commentary under the anointing—encouraging evidence that God is indeed working to bring about His plans and purposes during these turbulent times. Hosted by Gene Bailey and joined by leaders in government, business, politics and the Church. FlashPoint’s rapidly become a trusted source of truth and hope. Wednesdays and Fridays at 8 p.m. ET/7 p.m. CT.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260619010000 +0000" stop="20260619013000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Paula Today with Paula White-Cain</title>
    <desc>Paula White-Cain along with her husband, Jonathan Cain discuss real life situations and offer practical, Biblical solutions. Down-to-earth, refreshing, sometimes unfiltered and always sharing the life-changing love of Jesus thru Paula’s in-depth teaching or Jon’s anointed music. About Paula Paula White-Cain is the President of Paula White Ministries and City of Destiny headquartered in Apopka, Florida, and the spiritual advisor to President Donald Trump. She hosts Paula Today, a nationally syndicated daily broadcast reaching a potential audience of 5.7 billion people in over 200 countries. She is a leading Pastor, a renowned life coach, bestselling author, and highly sought-after motivational speaker. Paula’s commitment to humanity is felt worldwide as she reaches out through numerous charities and compassion ministries, fulfilling her mission and call to transform lives, heal hearts and win souls. She lives in the Orlando area with her husband, Jonathan Cain.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260619013000 +0000" stop="20260619020000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The James Epperly Show</title>
    <desc>"The James Epperly Show" is a Christian television program that aims to inspire and uplift viewers through faith-based content. Hosted by Pastor James Epperly, the show features insightful sermons, engaging interviews with prominent Christian figures, and heartfelt testimonials from individuals who have experienced life-changing transformations through faith. Each episode is designed to offer spiritual guidance, biblical wisdom, and practical advice for living a Christ-centered life. With its friendly and welcoming vibe, 'The James Epperly Show' aims to support viewers' spiritual development and enhance their connection with God, making it a treasured part of their weekly viewing schedule.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260619020000 +0000" stop="20260619023000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The Place For Miracles with Richard &amp; Lindsay Roberts</title>
    <desc>This show, hosted by Richard and Lindsay Roberts, features prayer, miracle testimonies, teaching from the Bible, and praise and worship.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260619023000 +0000" stop="20260619030000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Manna-Fest with Perry Stone</title>
    <desc>Manna-fest is the weekly television program of Perry Stone that deals with in-depth prophetic and practical studies of the Word of God. As biblical prophecy continues to unfold, you will find Manna-fest to be a resource to help you better understand where we are now in light of Bible prophecy and what the Bible says about the future. Be sure to tune in each week!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260619030000 +0000" stop="20260619033000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The Jim Bakker Show</title>
    <desc>The Jim Bakker Show is an hour-long daily Christian broadcast that is aired throughout the United States, Canada, and the entire world through multiple broadcasts on Pioneer Network, Directv, Dish Network and other world wide satellites, and the PTL Television Network. Join Jim and Lori as they bring to the stage today’s greatest prophets, health experts, and leaders of the Christian world to discuss and understand Biblical prophecy and the Revelations of Gods Word.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260619033000 +0000" stop="20260619040000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The James Epperly Show</title>
    <desc>"The James Epperly Show" is a Christian television program that aims to inspire and uplift viewers through faith-based content. Hosted by Pastor James Epperly, the show features insightful sermons, engaging interviews with prominent Christian figures, and heartfelt testimonials from individuals who have experienced life-changing transformations through faith. Each episode is designed to offer spiritual guidance, biblical wisdom, and practical advice for living a Christ-centered life. With its friendly and welcoming vibe, 'The James Epperly Show' aims to support viewers' spiritual development and enhance their connection with God, making it a treasured part of their weekly viewing schedule.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260619040000 +0000" stop="20260619060000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Be Made Whole Worldwide Prayer Cloth Service with Rod Parsley</title>
    <desc>Experience the powerful anointing of our Be Made Whole Worldwide Prayer Cloth Service featuring Harvest Music Live and our outstanding choir. The miracle-working power of God changed multiplied hundreds of thousands, and now you can reserve your anointed prayer cloth from this year’s altar. The tangible transferrable anointing can heal your body, produce deliverance, family restoration, financial breakthrough, whatever you need!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260619060000 +0000" stop="20260619063000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The Place For Miracles</title>
    <desc>The Place forMiracles is a half-hour broadcast hosted by Richard and Lindsay Roberts. Theprogram focuses on the power of prayer and biblical teaching by Richard andLindsay, plus occasional videos featuring classic sermons from Oral Roberts,praise and worship music, “Living Proof” miracle testimonies, including livecalls and video presentations, and frequent, special guest appearances.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260619063000 +0000" stop="20260619070000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Kingdom Connection with Jentezen Franklin</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260619070000 +0000" stop="20260619073000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Desire Of All Nations</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260619073000 +0000" stop="20260619080000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Samuel Rodriguez</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260619080000 +0000" stop="20260619083000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The Jim Bakker Show</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260619083000 +0000" stop="20260619090000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Believer’s Voice of Victory</title>
    <desc>KCMis committed to keeping the Word of God before your eyes—teaching you how tolive victoriously—so that you are rooted and grounded enough to overcome yourown adversity, reach out to others and share those same principles. We endeavorto bring believers from the milk to the meat of the Word, and into fullmaturity in their walk with God. Oneword from God has transformed the lives of thousands who dared to hear andbelieve. And one word from God will do the same for you.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260619090000 +0000" stop="20260619093000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Paula Today with Paula Whie-Cain</title>
    <desc>Paula White-Cain along with her husband, Jonathan Cain discuss real life situations and offer practical, Biblical solutions. Down-to-earth, refreshing, sometimes unfiltered and always sharing the life-changing love of Jesus thru Paula’s in-depth teaching or Jon’s anointed music.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260619093000 +0000" stop="20260619100000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Christian Music Countdown</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260619100000 +0000" stop="20260619103000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Make Your Day Count with Lindsay Roberts</title>
    <desc>Lindsay Roberts hosts an uplifting program geared especially toward encouraging and equipping women through Bible-based teaching and testimonies.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260619103000 +0000" stop="20260619110000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Believer's Voice of Victory</title>
    <desc>KCM is committed to keeping the Word of God before your eyes—teaching you how to live victoriously—so that you are rooted and grounded enough to overcome your own adversity, reach out to others and share those same principles. We endeavor to bring believers from the milk to the meat of the Word, and into full maturity in their walk with God.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260619110000 +0000" stop="20260619113000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Today with Marilyn &amp; Sarah</title>
    <desc>Marilyn&amp; Sarah Ministries is a global, miracle ministry responding to God's callto cover the earth with the Word and connect every one with the heart of God.For nearly 50 years they have empowered ordinary people to tap into thelife-changing power of the gospel through prayer, Bible teaching, humanitarianand evangelistic outreaches, healing meetings, and their daily TV program,Today with Marilyn &amp; Sarah.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260619113000 +0000" stop="20260619120000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Joyce Meyer: Enjoying Everyday Life</title>
    <desc>Joyce Meyer, one of the world’s leading practicalBible teachers and New York Times bestselling author, shares encouragement andadvice to help people enjoy daily life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260619120000 +0000" stop="20260619123000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Good Morning LIVE</title>
    <desc>Good Morning LIVE is an engaging 30-minute program designed to inspire, inform, and connect viewers to the heart of meaningful living. Hosted by James Epperly, this dynamic show brings together a unique blend of inspirational devotions, thought-provoking interviews, and discussions on current events that matter most to you. Each episode offers uplifting messages to start your day on a positive note, insightful conversations with special guests, and a closer look at how current events align with faith and personal growth. Whether you're seeking encouragement, knowledge, or a deeper connection to today's world, Good Morning LIVE is your source for faith-filled and relevant content. Join us weekday mornings to experience a fresh perspective, inspired by truth and guided by hope.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260619123000 +0000" stop="20260619130000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Worldview Matters</title>
    <desc>David Fiorazo is an author,ordained pastor, truth proclaimer, media contributor, and podcaster. Since the1990’s David has been working in both TV and radio broadcasting and inChristian ministry. On Worldview Matters,Fiorazo and expert guests tackle current events, demonic agendas &amp;movements, and controversial topics including church &amp; state issues,religious freedom, the culture war, Bible prophecy, education, politics, media&amp; more.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260619130000 +0000" stop="20260619133000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Gospel Truth with Andrew Wommack</title>
    <desc>God called Andrew over 50 years ago toteach the truth of the gospel to the body of Christ with a special emphasis onHis unconditional love and the balance between grace and faith. To fulfil thatcall, Andrew teaches at conferences, in churches, on television, throughpodcasts, and by training people from all walks of life globally at CharisBible College.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260619130000 +0000" stop="20260619133000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Gospel Truth with Andrew Wommack</title>
    <desc>Thirty-two years ago a man had an encounter with God that changed his life forever. Today, he shares that experience with thousands of people all over the world. The goal of Andrew Wommack is to reach as many people as possible with the love of God and message of grace and faith. He doesn’t measure the success of the ministry by the number of tapes distributed, books sold or offerings received. The real rewards, and proof that God is alive and working in people’s lives, are the many testimonies he receives from the people impacted by his teachings. To find out more, please visit our website at: http://www.awmi.net http://www.awmi.net/ www.awmi.net</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260619133000 +0000" stop="20260619140000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Rick Renner</title>
    <desc>Rick Renner is widely known for his interpretation of the Greek New Testament and his engaging teaching style. His teaching is punctuated by a unique ability to draw vividly descriptive word pictures from the Greek that illuminate the Scriptures in a fresh, new way. Rick also distinctively shares Bible principles through contemporary illustrations set against an extensive cultural and historical backdrop of New Testament times. In each episode of “Rick Renner,” Rick teaches in-depth on a passage of Scripture verse by verse, centered around a specific theme that is vitally relevant to the lives of believers who are hungry to dig deeper into the treasures of God’s Word. For more information, visit http://www.renner.org.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260619140000 +0000" stop="20260619143000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Manna Fest With Perry Stone</title>
    <desc>Manna-fest is the weekly television program of Perry Stone that deals with in-depth prophetic and practical studies of the Word of God. As biblical prophecy continues to unfold, you will find Manna-fest to be a resource to help you better understand where we are now in light of Bible prophecy and what the Bible says about the future. Be sure to tune in each week!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260619143000 +0000" stop="20260619150000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The James Epperly Show</title>
    <desc>"The James Epperly Show" is a Christian television program that aims to inspire and uplift viewers through faith-based content. Hosted by Pastor James Epperly, the show features insightful sermons, engaging interviews with prominent Christian figures, and heartfelt testimonials from individuals who have experienced life-changing transformations through faith. Each episode is designed to offer spiritual guidance, biblical wisdom, and practical advice for living a Christ-centered life. With its friendly and welcoming vibe, 'The James Epperly Show' aims to support viewers' spiritual development and enhance their connection with God, making it a treasured part of their weekly viewing schedule.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260619150000 +0000" stop="20260619153000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The Winners Way with Mac Hammond</title>
    <desc>As our faith, courage, and discipline strengthen, we become vessels through which God can bring blessings to others. Discover more about this transformative journey—and our journey to plant fifty churches in five years—on The Winner's Way with Mac Hammond.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260619153000 +0000" stop="20260619160000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Joyce Meyer: Enjoying Everyday Life</title>
    <desc>Joyce Meyer, one of the world’s leading practicalBible teachers and New York Times bestselling author, shares encouragement andadvice to help people enjoy daily life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260619160000 +0000" stop="20260619163000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The James Epperly Show</title>
    <desc>"The James Epperly Show" is a Christian television program that aims to inspire and uplift viewers through faith-based content. Hosted by Pastor James Epperly, the show features insightful sermons, engaging interviews with prominent Christian figures, and heartfelt testimonials from individuals who have experienced life-changing transformations through faith. Each episode is designed to offer spiritual guidance, biblical wisdom, and practical advice for living a Christ-centered life. With its friendly and welcoming vibe, 'The James Epperly Show' aims to support viewers' spiritual development and enhance their connection with God, making it a treasured part of their weekly viewing schedule.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260619163000 +0000" stop="20260619170000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The Jim Bakker Show</title>
    <desc>The Jim Bakker Show is an hour-long daily Christian broadcast that is aired throughout the United States, Canada, and the entire world through multiple broadcasts on Pioneer Network, Directv, Dish Network and other world wide satellites, and the PTL Television Network. Join Jim and Lori as they bring to the stage today’s greatest prophets, health experts, and leaders of the Christian world to discuss and understand Biblical prophecy and the Revelations of Gods Word.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260619170000 +0000" stop="20260619173000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The Mondo Show</title>
    <desc>The Mondo Show is real, it’s raw, with an organicfeel to the conversation. Sometimes I will be talking directly to you theaudience, and at other times I will place you in the middle of theconversation, so you can experience what is really being said. The subject matter for the conversation and thequestions will be the things people are afraid to ask, even though it is whateveryone is thinking. I want you to meet the men and women who are making adifference in our communities, in our culture, and in our lives. It’s a journeyto understand the misunderstood. It’s The Mondo Show.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260619173000 +0000" stop="20260619180000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Samuel Rodriguez</title>
    <desc>New Season with Pastor Sam will usher in a "New Season" where individuals and families will no longer live in failure or merely survive but they will thrive for the glory of Jesus.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260619180000 +0000" stop="20260619190000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Great Awakening With Rodney Howard-Brown</title>
    <desc>Dr. Rodney Howard-Browne is the founder and pastor of Revival Ministries International in Tampa, Florida. In 1983, he pioneered a church in the Northeastern Cape and pastored there for two years. After that, Rodney taught classes in a leading Bible School for another two years. Rodney and his wife Adonica pastor a church in Tampa, Florida, The River at Tampa Bay, which they founded in 1996 and which now has 3000 members. These three things have remained constant since the church’s inception…dynamic praise and worship, anointed preaching and teaching of the Word, and powerful demonstrations of the Holy Spirit and power.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260619190000 +0000" stop="20260619193000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Victory With Paul Daugherty</title>
    <desc>Pastor Paul Daugherty and his wife Ashley lead a new generation with a practical, life-transforming message; a message of love, hope, healing and forgiveness.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260619193000 +0000" stop="20260619200000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Paula Today with Paula White-Cain</title>
    <desc>Paula Today Paula White-Cain along with her husband, Jonathan Cain discuss real life situations and offer practical, Biblical solutions. Down-to-earth, refreshing, sometimes unfiltered and always sharing the life-changing love of Jesus thru Paula’s in-depth teaching or Jon’s anointed music. About Paula Paula White-Cain is the President of Paula White Ministries and City of Destiny headquartered in Apopka, Florida, and the spiritual advisor to President Donald Trump. She hosts Paula Today, a nationally syndicated daily broadcast reaching a potential audience of 5.7 billion people in over 200 countries. She is a leading Pastor, a renowned life coach, bestselling author, and highly sought-after motivational speaker. Paula’s commitment to humanity is felt worldwide as she reaches out through numerous charities and compassion ministries, fulfilling her mission and call to transform lives, heal hearts and win souls. She lives in the Orlando area with her husband, Jonathan Cain.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260619200000 +0000" stop="20260619203000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Focus On The Family</title>
    <desc>Become a champion for your family in the time it takes to enjoy a cup of coffee! Every episode of the Focus on the Family Christian podcast helps you confidently guide your loved ones through the unique challenges faced by today’s Christian families. With over 40 years of trusted, compassionate stories of redemption, hosts Jim Daly and John Fuller connect you to biblically sound marriage and parenting help that is relatable, practical, and interesting. Listen/Learn/Apply/ThriveInChrist!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260619203000 +0000" stop="20260619210000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Coffee With Kim</title>
    <desc>COFFEE - Conversations of Friends of Faith to Encourage and Equip﻿﻿﻿ Do you know what happens when a few imperfect people gather around a table for real conversation? They discover they have the same questions about http://life...believe the same http://lies...and hide the same longings. They also discover that though they don't have all the answers, together they have so many more…and their wisdom is worth sharing. So come to our table for "COFFEE with Kim." Join us for conversations that are real…relevant…and right on time!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260619210000 +0000" stop="20260619213000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Joyce Meyer: Enjoying Everyday Life</title>
    <desc>Joyce Meyer, one of the world’s leading practical Bible teachers and NewYork Times bestselling author, shares encouragement and advice to help peopleenjoy daily life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260619213000 +0000" stop="20260619220000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Faith &amp; Law</title>
    <desc>Faith &amp; Law is a 30 minute variety program that focuses on the intersection of faith and law.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260619220000 +0000" stop="20260619223000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The Counter Culture Mom Show</title>
    <desc>Former Hollywood actress, pop culture expert, Tina Griffin, left her Wisconsin dairy farm at the age of 20 and headed to Hollywood, CA to earn a BA in Film and Television broadcasting from California State University - Los Angeles. She’s traveled globally for the past 20 years delivering her eye-opening show, Hollywood Exposed https://counterculturemom.com/adult-session/ , explaining the real agenda behind the entertainment industry and its impact on the foundational development of today’s youth. Besides being in countless movies, Tina has worked on TV shows such as Jimmy Kimmel Live!, Young and the Restless, Days of Our Lives, Lizzie McGuire, Drake and Josh, and Malcolm in the Middle, competed in the Miss America pageant and worked at the OSCARS. She was involved with the Film Society as well as Women in Film and an active member of the Screen Actors Guild (SAG) and the American Federation of Television and Radio Artists (AFTRA). She has opened for bands such as Colton Dixon, Third Day, and Jeremy Camp. As host of The Counter Culture Mom Show, Tina gives the latest pop culture news and features experts covering critical topics such as cutting, suicide, bullying, online chat room d</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260619223000 +0000" stop="20260619230000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Believer’s Voice of Victory</title>
    <desc>KCMis committed to keeping the Word of God before your eyes—teaching you how tolive victoriously—so that you are rooted and grounded enough to overcome yourown adversity, reach out to others and share those same principles. We endeavorto bring believers from the milk to the meat of the Word, and into fullmaturity in their walk with God. Oneword from God has transformed the lives of thousands who dared to hear andbelieve. And one word from God will do the same for you.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260619230000 +0000" stop="20260620000000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>ORU Chapel</title>
    <desc>Ranked as one of the Top 50 “Most DiverseColleges in America” and Oklahoma’s #1 university for diversity (Niche 2023),ORU https://oru.edu/ https://www.youtube.com/redirect?event=video_description&amp;redir_token=QUFFLUhqbllUSTZqTUJzVGRzTU90OV82YVVWc1liNEJrZ3xBQ3Jtc0tramk4WUVQcUNabmM5SGlNQklEX2JJSk9kMVJ5MmNJQWFFLWlfTTBULXY3WnF0T3g2LUtiV3JOaW1mR0o2N20tOS04N0ZqUUlNblRNTWhyWkx5QVVzemQ5VDNqNTUzM1BZc2o1S1hFOHVEZEFtYU1mbw&amp;q=https%3A%2F%2Foru.edu%2F&amp;v=rPj4d3Ei0EU is a multicultural, global campus withmore than 4,500 students representing well over 120 nations. And as a Top 10university for Engagement (Wall Street Journal/Times Higher Ed ranked), ORUworks closely with students to develop whole leaders for the whole worldthrough a unique Whole Person approach to college education. If you’re anon-campus student or if you’re seeking an online education, ORU offersbachelors, masters, and doctoral degrees in a global, Spirit-empoweredenvironment. Explore Oral Roberts University https://oru.edu/ https://oru.edu/</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260620000000 +0000" stop="20260620010000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>FlashPoint</title>
    <desc>Live program that addresses current events and issues facing America and the world. Often tackling topics that mainstream media does not, it delivers news and commentary under the anointing—encouraging evidence that God is indeed working to bring about His plans and purposes during these turbulent times. Hosted by Gene Bailey and joined by leaders in government, business, politics and the Church. FlashPoint’s rapidly become a trusted source of truth and hope. Wednesdays and Fridays at 8 p.m. ET/7 p.m. CT.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260620010000 +0000" stop="20260620013000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Paula Today with Paula White-Cain</title>
    <desc>Paula White-Cain along with her husband, Jonathan Cain discuss real life situations and offer practical, Biblical solutions. Down-to-earth, refreshing, sometimes unfiltered and always sharing the life-changing love of Jesus thru Paula’s in-depth teaching or Jon’s anointed music. About Paula Paula White-Cain is the President of Paula White Ministries and City of Destiny headquartered in Apopka, Florida, and the spiritual advisor to President Donald Trump. She hosts Paula Today, a nationally syndicated daily broadcast reaching a potential audience of 5.7 billion people in over 200 countries. She is a leading Pastor, a renowned life coach, bestselling author, and highly sought-after motivational speaker. Paula’s commitment to humanity is felt worldwide as she reaches out through numerous charities and compassion ministries, fulfilling her mission and call to transform lives, heal hearts and win souls. She lives in the Orlando area with her husband, Jonathan Cain.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260620013000 +0000" stop="20260620030000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Valor Christian College Chapel</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260620030000 +0000" stop="20260620040000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Brian &amp; Bobbie Houston - JesusFollowers.TV</title>
    <desc>"What greater honour and testimony is there than to be a devotedand passionate follower of the Lord Jesus Christ. Bobbie and I believe in the Church, thelocal church and the power and blessing of being planted (Psalm 92). We alsobelieve that in this day and age, God is creating multiple ways to water theseeds and greatness of calling within. Jesusfollowers.TV is here towelcome and extend our table of life and experience to you. This onlineplatform is here to love, encourage, and be a trustworthy voice of hope andinspiration in the days ahead. Our heart is to serve the God-given potentialwithin you and the Body of Christ. As Eph 2:21-22 says, we are all beingbuilt into a holy habitation for the Living God - brick by brick, stone bystone, with Jesus Christ as the Chief Cornerstone. May Jesusfollowers.TV be ablessing to you and those you care for” Brian and Bobbie Houston</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260620040000 +0000" stop="20260620060000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Raise The Standard Conference with Rod Parsley</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260620060000 +0000" stop="20260620063000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The Place For Miracles</title>
    <desc>The Place forMiracles is a half-hour broadcast hosted by Richard and Lindsay Roberts. Theprogram focuses on the power of prayer and biblical teaching by Richard andLindsay, plus occasional videos featuring classic sermons from Oral Roberts,praise and worship music, “Living Proof” miracle testimonies, including livecalls and video presentations, and frequent, special guest appearances.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260620063000 +0000" stop="20260620070000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Kingdom Connection with Jentezen Franklin</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260620070000 +0000" stop="20260620073000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Desire Of All Nations</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260620073000 +0000" stop="20260620080000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Samuel Rodriguez</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260620080000 +0000" stop="20260620100000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Valor Christian College Chapel</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260620100000 +0000" stop="20260620103000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Faithville</title>
    <desc>Fun-filled, action-packed 30-minute comedy set in the 1940's to teach God's Word! Something taught with pleasure is learned full measure!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260620103000 +0000" stop="20260620110000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Miss Charity's Diner</title>
    <desc>Miss Charity welcomes kids into her diner to learn about Friendship, Patience, Faithfulness, Creativity and more! Stop in to hear a story with Miss Geranium, visit with Farmer Shalom and Dusty the dog, or learn safety and responsibility from Constable Howie. A fun-filled lesson teaching God's Word in every show.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260620110000 +0000" stop="20260620113000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Seasons</title>
    <desc>Follow the journey of young Josh and sister Lexie who go to live with the grandparents when life becomes difficult for single mother Debbie. See that God is faithful even in the most difficult of circumstances and discover a show that gives hope to every generation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260620113000 +0000" stop="20260620120000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Gospel Time Square</title>
    <desc>Friends meet at Gospel Time Square, the corner of 7th St. and Narrow Way. Join Melody and the rest as they learn about some of life's biggest lessons! Respect, Family, Serving and more!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260620120000 +0000" stop="20260620123000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Lessons From The Bible, with Pastor Doug</title>
    <desc>Join Pastor Doug, Dusty, Amelia and all the characters as they learn about the Bible and how it applies to daily life. Games, songs, and some silly puppets will inspire kids to follow along and get into God's Word!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260620123000 +0000" stop="20260620130000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Faithville</title>
    <desc>Fun-filled, action-packed 30-minute comedy set in the 1940's to teach God's Word! Something taught with pleasure is learned full measure!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260620130000 +0000" stop="20260620133000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Miss Charity's Diner</title>
    <desc>Miss Charity welcomes kids into her diner to learn about Friendship, Patience, Faithfulness, Creativity and more! Stop in to hear a story with Miss Geranium, visit with Farmer Shalom and Dusty the dog, or learn safety and responsibility from Constable Howie. A fun-filled lesson teaching God's Word in every show.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260620133000 +0000" stop="20260620140000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Seasons</title>
    <desc>Follow the journey of young Josh and sister Lexie who go to live with the grandparents when life becomes difficult for single mother Debbie. See that God is faithful even in the most difficult of circumstances and discover a show that gives hope to every generation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260620140000 +0000" stop="20260620143000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Gospel Time Square</title>
    <desc>Friends meet at Gospel Time Square, the corner of 7th St. and Narrow Way. Join Melody and the rest as they learn about some of life's biggest lessons! Respect, Family, Serving and more!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260620143000 +0000" stop="20260620150000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Lessons From The Bible, with Pastor Doug</title>
    <desc>Join Pastor Doug, Dusty, Amelia and all the characters as they learn about the Bible and how it applies to daily life. Games, songs, and some silly puppets will inspire kids to follow along and get into God's Word!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260620150000 +0000" stop="20260620160000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>ORU Chapel</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260620160000 +0000" stop="20260620163000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The James Epperly Show</title>
    <desc>"The James Epperly Show" is a Christian television program that aims to inspire and uplift viewers through faith-based content. Hosted by Pastor James Epperly, the show features insightful sermons, engaging interviews with prominent Christian figures, and heartfelt testimonials from individuals who have experienced life-changing transformations through faith. Each episode is designed to offer spiritual guidance, biblical wisdom, and practical advice for living a Christ-centered life. With its friendly and welcoming vibe, 'The James Epperly Show' aims to support viewers' spiritual development and enhance their connection with God, making it a treasured part of their weekly viewing schedule.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260620163000 +0000" stop="20260620170000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Faith &amp; Law</title>
    <desc>Faith &amp; Law is a 30-minute variety program that focuses on theintersection of faith and law.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260620170000 +0000" stop="20260620190000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Valor Christian College Chapel</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260620190000 +0000" stop="20260620193000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Christian Music Countdown</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260620193000 +0000" stop="20260620200000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Worldview Matters</title>
    <desc>On Worldview Matters, Fiorazo and expert guests tackle currentevents, demonic agendas &amp; movements, and controversial topics includingchurch &amp; state issues, religious freedom, the culture war, Bible prophecy,education, politics, media &amp; more.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260620200000 +0000" stop="20260620203000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The James Epperly Show</title>
    <desc>"The James Epperly Show" is a Christian television program that aims to inspire and uplift viewers through faith-based content. Hosted by Pastor James Epperly, the show features insightful sermons, engaging interviews with prominent Christian figures, and heartfelt testimonials from individuals who have experienced life-changing transformations through faith. Each episode is designed to offer spiritual guidance, biblical wisdom, and practical advice for living a Christ-centered life. With its friendly and welcoming vibe, 'The James Epperly Show' aims to support viewers' spiritual development and enhance their connection with God, making it a treasured part of their weekly viewing schedule.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260620203000 +0000" stop="20260620210000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>VFI News</title>
    <desc>VFI News with Barry Segal brings you timely, insightful reports on Israel, the Middle East, andglobal events - analysed through a biblical and prophetic lens.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260620210000 +0000" stop="20260620213000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The Jim Bakker Show</title>
    <desc>The Jim Bakker Show is an hour-long dailyChristian broadcast that is aired throughout the United States, Canada, and theentire world through multiple broadcasts on Directv, Dish Network and otherworld wide satellites, PTL Television Network, and the Pioneer Network. Join Jim and Lori Bakker as they bring tothe stage today’s greatest prophets, health experts, and leaders of theChristian world to discuss and understand Biblical prophecy and the Revelationsof God’s Word.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260620213000 +0000" stop="20260620230000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Hope City Church</title>
    <desc>Join Pastor James Epperly and the congregation of Hope City Church for inspirational teaching and ministry.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260620230000 +0000" stop="20260621000000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>ORU Chapel</title>
    <desc>Ranked as one of the Top 50 “Most DiverseColleges in America” and Oklahoma’s #1 university for diversity (Niche 2023),ORU https://oru.edu/ https://www.youtube.com/redirect?event=video_description&amp;redir_token=QUFFLUhqbllUSTZqTUJzVGRzTU90OV82YVVWc1liNEJrZ3xBQ3Jtc0tramk4WUVQcUNabmM5SGlNQklEX2JJSk9kMVJ5MmNJQWFFLWlfTTBULXY3WnF0T3g2LUtiV3JOaW1mR0o2N20tOS04N0ZqUUlNblRNTWhyWkx5QVVzemQ5VDNqNTUzM1BZc2o1S1hFOHVEZEFtYU1mbw&amp;q=https%3A%2F%2Foru.edu%2F&amp;v=rPj4d3Ei0EU is a multicultural, global campus withmore than 4,500 students representing well over 120 nations. And as a Top 10university for Engagement (Wall Street Journal/Times Higher Ed ranked), ORUworks closely with students to develop whole leaders for the whole worldthrough a unique Whole Person approach to college education. If you’re anon-campus student or if you’re seeking an online education, ORU offersbachelors, masters, and doctoral degrees in a global, Spirit-empoweredenvironment. Explore Oral Roberts University https://oru.edu/</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260621000000 +0000" stop="20260621003000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The James Epperly Show</title>
    <desc>"The James Epperly Show" is a Christian television program that aims to inspire and uplift viewers through faith-based content. Hosted by Pastor James Epperly, the show features insightful sermons, engaging interviews with prominent Christian figures, and heartfelt testimonials from individuals who have experienced life-changing transformations through faith. Each episode is designed to offer spiritual guidance, biblical wisdom, and practical advice for living a Christ-centered life. With its friendly and welcoming vibe, 'The James Epperly Show' aims to support viewers' spiritual development and enhance their connection with God, making it a treasured part of their weekly viewing schedule.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260621003000 +0000" stop="20260621010000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Life In Christ With Pastor Joe Spence</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260621010000 +0000" stop="20260621013000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Christian Music Countdown</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260621013000 +0000" stop="20260621020000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Manna Fest with Perry Stone</title>
    <desc>Manna-fest is the weekly television program of Perry Stone that deals with in-depth prophetic and practical studies of the Word of God. As biblical prophecy continues to unfold, you will find Manna-fest to be a resource to help you better understand where we are now in light of Bible prophecy and what the Bible says about the future. Be sure to tune in each week!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260621020000 +0000" stop="20260621040000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Valor Christian College Chapel</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260621040000 +0000" stop="20260621060000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Be Made Whole Worldwide Prayer Cloth Service with Rod Parsley</title>
    <desc>Experience the powerful anointing of our Be Made Whole Worldwide Prayer Cloth Service featuring Harvest Music Live and our outstanding choir. The miracle-working power of God changed multiplied hundreds of thousands, and now you can reserve your anointed prayer cloth from this year’s altar. The tangible transferrable anointing can heal your body, produce deliverance, family restoration, financial breakthrough, whatever you need!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260621060000 +0000" stop="20260621063000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The Place For Miracles</title>
    <desc>The Place forMiracles is a half-hour broadcast hosted by Richard and Lindsay Roberts. Theprogram focuses on the power of prayer and biblical teaching by Richard andLindsay, plus occasional videos featuring classic sermons from Oral Roberts,praise and worship music, “Living Proof” miracle testimonies, including livecalls and video presentations, and frequent, special guest appearances.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260621063000 +0000" stop="20260621070000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Kingdom Connection with Jentezen Franklin</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260621070000 +0000" stop="20260621073000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Desire Of All Nations</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260621073000 +0000" stop="20260621080000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Samuel Rodriguez</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260621080000 +0000" stop="20260621100000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Valor Christian College Chapel</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260621100000 +0000" stop="20260621103000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Faithville</title>
    <desc>Fun-filled, action-packed 30-minute comedy set in the 1940's to teach God's Word! Something taught with pleasure is learned full measure!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260621103000 +0000" stop="20260621110000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Miss Charity's Diner</title>
    <desc>Miss Charity welcomes kids into her diner to learn about Friendship, Patience, Faithfulness, Creativity and more! Stop in to hear a story with Miss Geranium, visit with Farmer Shalom and Dusty the dog, or learn safety and responsibility from Constable Howie. A fun-filled lesson teaching God's Word in every show.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260621110000 +0000" stop="20260621113000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Seasons</title>
    <desc>Follow the journey of young Josh and sister Lexie who go to live with the grandparents when life becomes difficult for single mother Debbie. See that God is faithful even in the most difficult of circumstances and discover a show that gives hope to every generation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260621113000 +0000" stop="20260621130000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Valor Christian College Chapel</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260621130000 +0000" stop="20260621140000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>ORU Chapel</title>
    <desc>Ranked as one of the Top 50 “Most DiverseColleges in America” and Oklahoma’s #1 university for diversity (Niche 2023),ORU https://oru.edu/ https://www.youtube.com/redirect?event=video_description&amp;redir_token=QUFFLUhqbllUSTZqTUJzVGRzTU90OV82YVVWc1liNEJrZ3xBQ3Jtc0tramk4WUVQcUNabmM5SGlNQklEX2JJSk9kMVJ5MmNJQWFFLWlfTTBULXY3WnF0T3g2LUtiV3JOaW1mR0o2N20tOS04N0ZqUUlNblRNTWhyWkx5QVVzemQ5VDNqNTUzM1BZc2o1S1hFOHVEZEFtYU1mbw&amp;q=https%3A%2F%2Foru.edu%2F&amp;v=rPj4d3Ei0EU is a multicultural, global campus withmore than 4,500 students representing well over 120 nations. And as a Top 10university for Engagement (Wall Street Journal/Times Higher Ed ranked), ORUworks closely with students to develop whole leaders for the whole worldthrough a unique Whole Person approach to college education. If you’re anon-campus student or if you’re seeking an online education, ORU offersbachelors, masters, and doctoral degrees in a global, Spirit-empoweredenvironment. Explore Oral Roberts University https://oru.edu/ https://oru.edu/</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260621140000 +0000" stop="20260621153000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Hope City Church LIVE</title>
    <desc>Join Pastor James Epperly and the congregation of Hope City Church for LIVE inspirational teaching and ministry.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260621153000 +0000" stop="20260621163000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Brian &amp; Bobbie Houston - JesusFollowers.TV</title>
    <desc>"What greater honour and testimony is there than to be a devotedand passionate follower of the Lord Jesus Christ. Bobbie and I believe in the Church, thelocal church and the power and blessing of being planted (Psalm 92). We alsobelieve that in this day and age, God is creating multiple ways to water theseeds and greatness of calling within. Jesusfollowers.TV is here towelcome and extend our table of life and experience to you. This onlineplatform is here to love, encourage, and be a trustworthy voice of hope andinspiration in the days ahead. Our heart is to serve the God-given potentialwithin you and the Body of Christ. As Eph 2:21-22 says, we are all beingbuilt into a holy habitation for the Living God - brick by brick, stone bystone, with Jesus Christ as the Chief Cornerstone. May Jesusfollowers.TV be ablessing to you and those you care for” Brian and Bobbie Houston</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260621163000 +0000" stop="20260621170000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Christian Music Countdown</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260621170000 +0000" stop="20260621173000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Jentezen Franklin</title>
    <desc>Jentezen Franklin is the Senior Pastor of Free Chapel, a multi-campus church. Each week his television program, Kingdom Connection, is broadcast on major networks all over the world. A New York Times best-selling author, Jentezen has written ten books including his most recent Acres of Diamonds, Love Like You’ve Never Been Hurt, the ground-breaking Fasting and Right People-Right Place-Right Plan.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260621173000 +0000" stop="20260621180000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The James Epperly Show</title>
    <desc>"The James Epperly Show" is a Christian television program that aims to inspire and uplift viewers through faith-based content. Hosted by Pastor James Epperly, the show features insightful sermons, engaging interviews with prominent Christian figures, and heartfelt testimonials from individuals who have experienced life-changing transformations through faith. Each episode is designed to offer spiritual guidance, biblical wisdom, and practical advice for living a Christ-centered life. With its friendly and welcoming vibe, 'The James Epperly Show' aims to support viewers' spiritual development and enhance their connection with God, making it a treasured part of their weekly viewing schedule.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260621180000 +0000" stop="20260621183000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Joyce Meyer: Enjoying Everyday Life</title>
    <desc>Joyce Meyer, one of the world’s leading practical Bible teachers and NewYork Times bestselling author, shares encouragement and advice to help peopleenjoy daily life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260621183000 +0000" stop="20260621190000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Worldview Matters</title>
    <desc>On Worldview Matters, Fiorazo and expert guests tackle currentevents, demonic agendas &amp; movements, and controversial topics includingchurch &amp; state issues, religious freedom, the culture war, Bible prophecy,education, politics, media &amp; more.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260621190000 +0000" stop="20260621193000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Victory with Paul Dougherty</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260621193000 +0000" stop="20260621200000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The James Epperly Show</title>
    <desc>"The James Epperly Show" is a Christian television program that aims to inspire and uplift viewers through faith-based content. Hosted by Pastor James Epperly, the show features insightful sermons, engaging interviews with prominent Christian figures, and heartfelt testimonials from individuals who have experienced life-changing transformations through faith. Each episode is designed to offer spiritual guidance, biblical wisdom, and practical advice for living a Christ-centered life. With its friendly and welcoming vibe, 'The James Epperly Show' aims to support viewers' spiritual development and enhance their connection with God, making it a treasured part of their weekly viewing schedule.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260621200000 +0000" stop="20260621203000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Joyce Meyer: Enjoying Everyday Life</title>
    <desc>Joyce Meyer, one of the world’s leading practical Bible teachers and NewYork Times bestselling author, shares encouragement and advice to help peopleenjoy daily life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260621203000 +0000" stop="20260621210000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Kyle Winkler</title>
    <desc>Kyle Winkler is a practical Bible teacher, author of Silence Satan and Activating the Power of God’s Word, and creator of the popular Shut Up, Devil! app. Through his teachings, Kyle is known for using his own story to boast in the power of God’s Word for victorious living.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260621210000 +0000" stop="20260621213000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Christian Music Countdown</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260621213000 +0000" stop="20260621220000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Faith &amp; Law</title>
    <desc>Faith &amp; Law is a 30-minute variety program that focuses on the intersection of faith and law.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260621220000 +0000" stop="20260621223000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>On The Path with Cheryl Nembhard</title>
    <desc>Join host Cheryl Nembhard On The Path, along with notable guests as they share their stories of triumph, tragedy, and the big lessons they've learned along their journey of faith.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260621223000 +0000" stop="20260621230000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Life In Christ With Pastor Joe Spence</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260621230000 +0000" stop="20260622003000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Hope City Church</title>
    <desc>Join Pastor James Epperly and the congregation of Hope City Church for inspirational teaching and ministry.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260622003000 +0000" stop="20260622010000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Run The Streets with Debra George</title>
    <desc>Debra takes you to the darkest streets of America to win souls.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260622010000 +0000" stop="20260622013000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Christian Music Countdown</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260622013000 +0000" stop="20260622020000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The James Epperly Show</title>
    <desc>"The James Epperly Show" is a Christian television program that aims to inspire and uplift viewers through faith-based content. Hosted by Pastor James Epperly, the show features insightful sermons, engaging interviews with prominent Christian figures, and heartfelt testimonials from individuals who have experienced life-changing transformations through faith. Each episode is designed to offer spiritual guidance, biblical wisdom, and practical advice for living a Christ-centered life. With its friendly and welcoming vibe, 'The James Epperly Show' aims to support viewers' spiritual development and enhance their connection with God, making it a treasured part of their weekly viewing schedule.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260622020000 +0000" stop="20260622040000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Valor Christian College Chapel</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260622040000 +0000" stop="20260622060000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Be Made Whole Worldwide Prayer Cloth Service with Rod Parsley</title>
    <desc>Experience the powerful anointing of our Be Made Whole Worldwide Prayer Cloth Service featuring Harvest Music Live and our outstanding choir. The miracle-working power of God changed multiplied hundreds of thousands, and now you can reserve your anointed prayer cloth from this year’s altar. The tangible transferrable anointing can heal your body, produce deliverance, family restoration, financial breakthrough, whatever you need!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260622060000 +0000" stop="20260622063000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The Place For Miracles</title>
    <desc>The Place forMiracles is a half-hour broadcast hosted by Richard and Lindsay Roberts. Theprogram focuses on the power of prayer and biblical teaching by Richard andLindsay, plus occasional videos featuring classic sermons from Oral Roberts,praise and worship music, “Living Proof” miracle testimonies, including livecalls and video presentations, and frequent, special guest appearances.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260622063000 +0000" stop="20260622070000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Kingdom Connection with Jentezen Franklin</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260622070000 +0000" stop="20260622073000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Desire Of All Nations</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260622073000 +0000" stop="20260622080000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Samuel Rodriguez</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260622080000 +0000" stop="20260622083000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>The Jim Bakker Show</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260622083000 +0000" stop="20260622090000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Believer’s Voice of Victory</title>
    <desc>KCMis committed to keeping the Word of God before your eyes—teaching you how tolive victoriously—so that you are rooted and grounded enough to overcome yourown adversity, reach out to others and share those same principles. We endeavorto bring believers from the milk to the meat of the Word, and into fullmaturity in their walk with God. Oneword from God has transformed the lives of thousands who dared to hear andbelieve. And one word from God will do the same for you.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260622090000 +0000" stop="20260622093000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Paula Today with Paula Whie-Cain</title>
    <desc>Paula White-Cain along with her husband, Jonathan Cain discuss real life situations and offer practical, Biblical solutions. Down-to-earth, refreshing, sometimes unfiltered and always sharing the life-changing love of Jesus thru Paula’s in-depth teaching or Jon’s anointed music.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260622093000 +0000" stop="20260622100000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Christian Music Countdown</title>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260622100000 +0000" stop="20260622103000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Make Your Day Count with Lindsay Roberts</title>
    <desc>Lindsay Roberts hosts an uplifting program geared especially toward encouraging and equipping women through Bible-based teaching and testimonies.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260622103000 +0000" stop="20260622110000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Believer's Voice of Victory</title>
    <desc>KCM is committed to keeping the Word of God before your eyes—teaching you how to live victoriously—so that you are rooted and grounded enough to overcome your own adversity, reach out to others and share those same principles. We endeavor to bring believers from the milk to the meat of the Word, and into full maturity in their walk with God.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260622110000 +0000" stop="20260622113000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Today with Marilyn &amp; Sarah</title>
    <desc>Marilyn&amp; Sarah Ministries is a global, miracle ministry responding to God's callto cover the earth with the Word and connect every one with the heart of God.For nearly 50 years they have empowered ordinary people to tap into thelife-changing power of the gospel through prayer, Bible teaching, humanitarianand evangelistic outreaches, healing meetings, and their daily TV program,Today with Marilyn &amp; Sarah.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260622113000 +0000" stop="20260622120000 +0000" channel="ptn">
    <title>Joyce Meyer: Enjoying Everyday Life</title>
    <desc>Joyce Meyer, one of the world’s leading practicalBible teachers and New York Times bestselling author, shares encouragement andadvice to help people enjoy daily life.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>
